nBeastmen strive to become stronger by Evolving.
They take great pride in Evolution.
Fran's parents took their daughter with them
on their journey to Evolve.
But no Black Cat has ever been able to Evolve.
Fran's parents were no luckier. Their journey
came to an end before their reached their goal.
Now, Fran sets out to fulfill their dream of Evolution...
...by doing all she can to grow strong and powerful!
Plus...
...Fran's got a knack for battle.
Sword Art: Triple Thrust!
Name: Fran
Age: 12
Race: Beastman, Black Cat
Class: None
VIT:
INT:
STR:
AGI:
Whether it's sword arts or magic skills,
a little teaching's all it takes for her to master 'em.
Skills: Sword Mastery 1, Darkvision,
Expert Butcher,
Wayfinder
Create Water.
You're dirty, too, Teacher.
But more than anything Fran's such a sweet kid!
I'm so glad I have an amazing girl like her as my wielder!
I'm gonna dedicate my life—my NEW life—
to making her strong and powerful!
Fran, what is it?
Hey! Say something!
Dammit! Stay back! Get out of here!
EPISODE 2:
THE HELLISH TRIAL AT THE ADVENTURER'S GUILD
You didn't say we'd encounter goblins on this route!
Get rid of them, Randell!
How'm I supposed to-?
Gross!
Double Slash.
I got 'em!
Sword Art: Aura Blade. Creates a blade of mana
without needing to draw me.
It's not that powerful, but it's good for surprise attacks.
Okay, got it.
Thank the gods...
Fran, don't tell anyone I'm a talking sword.
You're the only one who can hear my telepathy.
Okay.
Thank you so much!
Could I thank you by giving you a ride?
We're headed to the city of Alessa.
You are?
Sounds like he wants you to guard his carriage.
Might as well take him up on the offer.
He seems like a stand-up guy.
Sure, I can keep you safe on the way to the city.
Oh, boy... Saw right through me, didn't you?
In the last month, some trouble on the Greatwolf Plain
has the monsters all riled up.
Where's the Greatwolf Plain?
It's an A-rank Haunt to the east.
I'm guessing some tough monsters
were having a turf war,
cause a bunch of weaker ones like goblins
have been spotted close to busy roads.
That was the Greatwolf Plain?
Guess that means this trouble was my fault...
Stories say the Plain is where
the S-rank monster Fenrir died.
People think the reason only weak monsters spawn there
is 'cause his mana still lingers.
Oh, so that's why the further out I went,
the stronger they got.
Fenrir, though. Damn...
Do you know anything about a sword
in the center of that plain?
Ooh, nice one, Fran! He might know about me!
Can't say I do.
Aw, man.
I know they're only a G-rank threat,
but you took those goblins out like they were nothing.
I'd say you were an E-Rank Adventurer. I guess right?
G-rank threat?
Adventurer?!
Huh? You've never heard that before? Oh, boy.
Each monster has a threat rank
that tells you how dangerous they are.
There are people who take requests
to hunt those monsters. We call them...
Adventurers!
That's right.
Adventurers go from legendary
S-Ranks to newbie G-ranks.
You might've heard of famous A-ranks
like Forlund of the Hundred Swords,
or Amanda the Great Mother.
Adventurers are so cool...
How do you become one?
Oh?
You just have to register at the Adventurer's Guild.
The Guild will also appraise and buy materials
obtained from slain monsters.
That means we can earn us some money.
You're gonna be eating well, Fran!
I want money...
Don't be ridiculous.
A weak Black Cat girl could never be an adventurer.
Look at this sleepyhead.
Not that I blame her. She was up late last night
practicing Skills and butchering monsters.
Teacher's cooking... Makes even grilled meat yummy...
Can kids just up and become adventurers here, though?
That's the city of Alessa.
I'll pay for you to enter the city.
Randell, you're so nice!
Here we are, Fran! Your first time...
...in a city!
See her with that big-ass sword?
Wow, what a joke.
First off, let's hit up the Adventurer's Guild.
Okay!
So these are the guild adventurers...
They've got all sorts of weapons.
Meh, none of them are as rare as me, though.
Let's check 'em out with Identify!
Name: Tempered Steel Longsword
Attack:
MP:
HP:
Mana Conductivity:
Mm-hmm, Attack: 398.
Huh?!
Name: Mythril Greatsword
Attack:
MP:
HP:
Mana Conductivity:
Skills: None
423...
That one, and that one too...
Attack
I thought I was super rare,
but everyone's swords are way stronger than me!
Attack
Teacher...
You're amazing, Teacher. You saved me!
And you're real pretty, too.
You have lots of skills. No other sword could compare!
Thank you, Fran.
No, thank you.
Fran is such a sweetheart.
That's it! I'm gonna support Fran with all my Skills!
That's my new purpose in life!
ADVENTURER'S GUILD
Piss off and die.
I know you can hear me, four-eyes!
Screw that bitch. Cheap-ass miser.
Ex-mercenary trash.
They can all piss off and die.
Oh, shoot! I need to smile, c'mon!
Bad day or not, I have to be Nell,
smiling receptionist of the Adventurer's...
'Scuse me!
Um...
This is the Adventurer's Guild, hun.
I know. I wanna be an adventurer.
She's just a child, and adventuring is dangerous.
She wouldn't last five minutes.
Okay, but we don't let just anyone register with us.
Okay.
You'd have to fight our examiner in a mock battle.
And you might get hurt.
Our guild will not take responsibility
for any injuries incurred.
Got it.
She's just another kid who needs to learn a hard lesson...
This way, then.
Damn, this is more legit than I thought.
You the person wantin' to register?
I'm the official examiner for Alessa's Adventurer's Guild.
THE GREAT AND POWERFUL DONADROND!
Donadrond sure does make his fellow Ogres proud
with his intense Intimidation.
Most would-be recruits turn tail and run when they're hit
with his Intimidation skill, let alone fight him.
That's the first trial that weeds out
anyone who doesn't have what it takes.
Huh?
She's not affected by his Intimidation!
Fran, you all right?
Yeah.
Let's Identify this guy.
Skills: Intimidate 4, Transport 3,
Incresed Recovery Speed 5
Increased Health Regen 4, Instruction 4,
Regen 5, Blink 6, Earth Magic 2,
Throwing Weapons 4, Poison Resistance 7, Woodcutting 3,
Axe Arts 6, Axe Mastery 7, Roar 3,
Revive, Spirit Manipulation, Muscles of Steel,
Auto Health Regen, Strength Up 1
Equipment: Blacksteel Battleaxe, Blacksteel Tortoise Armor,
Sabre-Tooth Mantle, Stone Dragon Boots,
Armband of Sacrifice
Name: Donadrond
Age: 46
Race: Ogre
Class: Warrior
VIT:
INT:
Donadrond the Ogre, eh?
That's a lotta Ds.
Hold up.
Skills:            Intimidate 4, Transport 3,
Incresed Recovery Speed 5
Increased Health Regen 4, Instruction 4,
Regen 5,           Blink 6,          Earth Magic 2,
Throwing Weapons 4, Poison Resistance 7, Woodcutting 3,
This guy is crazy strong...
Axe Arts 6, Axe Mastery 7, Roar 3,
Revive,            Spirit Manipulation,       Muscles of Steel,
Auto Health Regen,                   Strength Up 1
Equipment:               Blacksteel Battleaxe,                   Blacksteel Tortoise Armor,
Sabre-Tooth Mantle, Stone Dragon Boots,
Armband of Sacrifice
Name: Blacksteel Battleaxe
Attack:
MP:
HP:
Mana Conductivity:
Attack: 650?!
That's not important, Teacher.
I know.
I don't like holding back.
I'll come at you with all I got!
I'd like that.
Fran, he's definitely the toughest guy you've faced yet.
Don't you hold back either, okay?
Okay.
Let the test begin!
That little thing went in to take the test!
Bet she lost in two seconds flat.
Here he comes!
You dodged!
That was close!
Fran!
Slam Smash!
Nice, Fran! Good dodge!
Power Swing!
Watch out!
He's going way too hard on her!
I'll keep Fran safe!
You used your sword to weaken the blow.
Fran, don't take his attacks head-on with me!
But I can't just keep running away!
You're right. Lemme cast a buff on you.
It'll improve your attack power!
Okay!
Teacher cast a support spell.
Fran's STR and AGI have temporarily increased.
That's a high-level sword you got there.
But it's not enough!
His wounds are healing!
Donadrond don't stop!
I want...
...to be an adventurer!
What?! Earth magic?!
Leave the magic to me!
Fire Spell!
Tri Explosion!
No way... She cast several spells
without speaking them aloud?!
And that was a high-level fire spell just now!
I'll finish this.
Sword Art!
Dragon Fang!
She built up to that huge Sword Art
while also casting all those spells?!
She couldn't do that without having at least
two heads to think at once!
I've never seen even high-rank adventurers fight like that!
Do I pass?
Um, yes, it looks like it.
She beat me good!
GUILD MASTER: KLIMT
A loss is no laughing matter, Donadrond.
Uh! Sorry, sir.
Right then, Miss Fran.
Only twelve years of age,
but already using mid-tier Sword Arts,
and casting Level 10 fire spells
without saying the encantation aloud...
Wherever did you learn-
I'm not telling.
I see...
Don't tell anyone about us and what we can do.
If the wrong person finds out,
they might use it to spot our weakness.
My lips are sealed.
Good grief... Very well.
Identify.
You have Identity Protection, too?
Glad I used my Evolution Points on that one.
Knew we'd need it!
Are you gonna turn me down?
No, you pass. A few things still don't quite
make sense, but the spirits are calm.
Spirits?
Yes, they're very sensitive
to ill intentions or dark thoughts.
I can use them to tell if you harbor any ill will
towards us or others.
Skills: Swiftcast 7, Identify 5, Boy Mastery 3,
Gathering 5, Wood Magic 7,
Spirit Magic 8, Greater Earth Magic 6,
Alchemy 5, Earth Magic 10, Poison Resistance 3,
Paralysis Resistance 4, Water Magic 5,
Herbology 7, Cooking 4, Mana Manipulation
Child of the forest
Unique Skill: Favor of the Spirits
Titles:          Guild Master, Guardian of Alessa
Name: Klimt
Age: 136
Race: Wood Elf
Class: Spirit Sorcerer
VIT:
INT:
STR:
AGI:
He can use Spirit Magic...
And has tons of high-level skills.
Everything is in order.
Issue her a guild card.
Touch this crystal, please.
It will record your mana signature.
You'll also need to pick a class.
What's a class?
A class gives you different skills and abilities.
You should choose a class
that gives you the powers you're seeking.
The classes available to you are...
Huh?
Fighter, Swordsman, Spellword, Summoner...
And so many more!
You have so many possibilities!
Shoot, I might be sharing too many skills with her...
This is absolutely insane...
Though I suppose I shouldn't be surprised anymore.
A Spellsword sounds cool.
Why not grab it, then? Looks like you can use
both Sword Arts and spells that way.
I'll be a Spellword!
Wielder Fran's class is now Spellsword.
And that's that. Here is your guild card.
I'm an adventurer!
Something else you need?
I see. You'd like to sell us materials, then?
I gotta or I won't have money for a room.
Ah, yes...
Okay, Fran. Let's pull some stuff
out of our Pocket Dimension.
Pretend you're grabbing it from your item bag.
Okay.
We'll stick with low and mid-rank stuff for now.
Y-you butchered and prepared these yourself?!
Uh-huh.
Wow, uh, p-please give me a moment!
Your total payment comes out to 195,000 gold.
I've never seen so much gold before...
From the prices I saw in the market,
one gold is around 10 yen...
So we just made 1.9 million yen?! Holy shit!
Some materials came from F-Rank monsters,
and they were butchered extremely cleanly.
Thanks, lady. I can get a room now.
Please, call me Nell, Miss Fran.
Okay. Thanks, Nell.
Sweet, let's go find us a room!
Okay.
Hold up there.
Fran, just pretend you don't hear 'em.
Mm-kay.
HEY, YOU!
We told you to hold up!
You hear us, you little twerp?!
What?
You didn't earn that fair and square, did ya?
What? The hell are they talking about?
You reek!
I do not. I took a bath in the river this morning.
Gross!
Way to contaminate the water!
Underhanded shit's the only way
a stinky cat like you could get by!
This shit again?
Is this what Fran has to put up with all the time?
Fran...
We just sold a bunch of Twin-Headed Bear
shit, too, for cheap change!
That means you had to have done something dirty.
You make some kinda deal with that
four-eyed bitch over there, huh?!
Four-eyed bitch?
Give us what you made and we'll let you
and your underhanded shit slide.
Nothing underhanded took place in either transaction.
The materials you sold were badly damaged
and improperly butchered,
likely as a result of ganging up on the creature
and wailing upon it until it died.
And what's so wrong about that?
Adventurers who wish to sell materials for high prices
must slay the creature properly
and carefully dissect the materials!
Adventurers who use their own ignorance
as pretext for robbery...
...should piss off and die.
What?
Did you just tell us to piss off and die?!
Huh?
Dammit, Nell, you said it out loud this time!
You arrogant bitch...
Time for you to die instead!
I won't let you lay a finger on her.
Miss Fran...
Weak chickenshit beastman...
You dare talk back to a Red Dog?!
Can I stab him?
Whoa, you probably shouldn't
pull me on him inside the guild.
We're ex-mercenaries!
We ate kids like you for breakfast on the battlefield.
They're blocking the way out...
We'll beat the shit out of you then sell you to a slaver.
Not sure anyone will wanna buy
a Black Cat that stinks worse than shit, though.
Wha...?
My feet! My fucking feet!
Huh? I didn't do anything.
Don't insult Black Cats.
Wait, was that Fran?!
I didn't unsheathe you.
I used Vibrofang to sharpen my Aura Blade.
For real? She put those two together that fast...
You bitch!
Damn Black Cat!
We'll tear you to pieces!
Oscillation.
Y-you...
Good job, Fran. Oscillation destroys them
from the inisde out. He's not getting up anytime soon.
Yup.
Nice going, kid!
Good shit!
Good job, Fran.
Good job, my ass!
Call the guard! Arrest this little shit!
What? That was clearly an act of self-defense.
Despite being a "four-eyed bitch,"
it was clear as day to me.
Though we will need you to pay to clean up this mess.
100,000 gold will do.
We won't provide healing services
until that bill is paid. Understood?
Fran, we should try not to piss off Nell.
Yeah.
I'll handle the rest.
Okay. Thanks, Nell.
All right, let's find us a bed and buy you some new gear!
Gear? I want gear!
You can't deceive my Godsight.
That's an Intelligent Weapon.
NEXT EPISODE:
THE GRIZZLED OLD BLACKSMITH