I…
...seem to have died.
But I reincarnated in another world...
As a cutie with fluffy ears,
Except not...
I reincarnated as a sword.
EPISODE 1
A SWORD WHO MET A FLUFFY EARS GIRL
I reincarnated as a sword.
And that girl with the fluffy cat ears
is my precious Wielder.
We met by happenstance.
No, it was more than happenstance, it was a miracle.
Huh? I died, right?
Wait, hold on, where am I?
Did I get Isekai'd?! There's
even something flying up there!
No, wait a sec. I died…
...and reincarnated as a sword?!
Eh? Sword?! SWORD?!
Hey. You finally awake?
Who's there?
You're in for a rough ride, so do your best.
Eh? Hah?
All right, later.
Uhh... Hello?
That came through too clearly to be a hallucination...
But to be reincarnated as a sword, of all things?
No wait. Those who get reincarnated into
an Isekai, usually have broken powers...
Do I have any skills...?
O! Kanteigan!(Appraisal Eye)
Name:             Unknown
Registered Wielder:
None
Race:
Intelligent Weapon
Intelligent Weapon...
Race:
Intelligent Weapon
Okay, let's see...
HP:
Skills: Appraisal 6, Regenerate
Attack:
MP:
Telekinesis, Telepathy
Wielder Status Buff 1
Wielder Recovery Buff 1
Skill Sharing, Mage
Evolution Rank: 1
Skills: Regenerate, Telekinesis... Appraisal is at Level 6.
Skills:         Appraisal 6, Weilder Status Buff 1
Regenerate, Wielder Recovery Buff 1
Telekinesis, Skill Sharing,
Telepathy Mage
I'm freaking jacked!
Just looking at my design... if I were in an RPG, I'd be
the legendary sword that shows up near the end.
Whoa! Hey!
Name: Goblin Leader
Race: Mali-human
VIT:
MP:
STR:
AGI:
Skills: Sword Mastery 1, Survival 1,
Disassembly 2, Command 1,
Goblins?! Are they trying to pull me out?!
Wait, no! I don't wanna be wielded by goblins!
I look too legendary for them!
O～i, Oi ,  Aren't you
doing something really stupid?
Ah
This little shit. Okay, fine!
This means war.
Bring it, then!
Yes! I can use my Telekinesis skill to move around!
I thought I'd feel more guilty, but...
Huh?
I feel strangely satisfied.
Is that because I'm fulfilling my purpose as a sword?
I glowed again!
Attack:
MP:
HP:
Skills:           Identify 6, Regenerate
Telekinesis, Telepathy
Wielder Status Buff 1
Wielder Recovery Buff 1
Evolution Rank:
Skill Sharing, Mage
Equipped Skills
None
Skill Bank
Digging 1    Disassembly 1
Sword Arts 1 Club Arts 1
Command 1     Survival 1
Crystals:
Skill Slots:
Kobold Killer
Hey, there's new stuff popping up in my stats.
Crystals:
Skill Slots:
Mana Crystals? I glowed three times,
so that must mean three crystals.
And Memory Slots.
What exactly are Memory Slots?
Skill Bank
Digging 1
Disassembly 1
Sword Arts 1
Club Arts 1
Command 1,
Survival 1,
Kobold Killer
The skills added to the list
are the same ones from the goblin I killed.
Does that mean I absorbed its skills?!
Your current memory slots are 10.
Eh? What? Wait, who're you?!
Is this one of those things where only I can hear you?
Would you like to equip skills?
Eh?
Equipped Skills
None
Skill Bank
Aah, yes, l want to, I do!
Equipped Skills
Digging 1
Disassembly 1
Sword Arts 1
Club Arts 1
Command 1
Survival 1
Kobold Killer
Mana crystals and skills...
It's a little odd but...
guess I'll give it a go.
Stab! Stabbity-stab! Stab!
Hell yeah!
It's like the feeling you get when you stuff your
empty stomach with your favorite food!
Skill Bank
Vigilance
Poison Resistance
O! I've got new skills!
Crystals:
Skill Slots:
So breaking mana crystals does let me absorb their skills!
UNKNOWN used a Skill:
Digging
Thanks for the help.
Being a sword without someone
to wield me is kinda sad.
But now I've got a goal: absorb more skills!
Since I'm a sword now, I've gotta get stronger
for the person who's gonna wield me someday!
Pick up the pace, trash!
I want...
to be stronger.
Hey, no slacking off!
Black Cat weakling.
If I had power…
If I just had the power…
I want to have power.
I need power…
Using Telekinesis depletes my mana.
I can only use it for about 3 minutes.
Name: Air Floater
Race: Monster - Mali-plant
Your crystals are mine!
Gross!
MP
Whoa, it's absorbing my mana! That's not good!
I gotta have that skill, though!
Hell yeah, Drain Mana is mine!
Skills Obtained:
Mana Drain 1
Hawkeye
Float
I also got... Float?
Whoa! Combining Telekinesis and Float
lets me fly for 5 times longer!
And I can probably improve
that more by absorbing more skills!
With Telekinesis and Float, I can use…
Free Fall!
Crystals absorbed!
Thanks for the grub!
Your abilities have Evolved.
You have acquired 10 Evolution Points.
Attack Power:
Mana Capacity:
Durability:
Evolution Rank:
Crystals:
Skill Slots:
Points:
So if I get enough crystals, I could totally become
the strongest sword in the world!
Bonus Point Allocation
Improved Attack 1
Improved HP 1
Improved Telekinesis 1
Improved Telepathy 1
Improved MP 1
Expanded Skill Slots 1
Increase Skill Level
Identify Creature
Identify Plant
Identify Mineral
I get to pick a bonus skill, I guess?
Spend 5 Evolution Points to obtain Improved MP 1?
Yup!
HP:
Evolution Rank:
Crystals:
Skill Slots:
Attack:
MP:
Points:
You have obtained Improved MP 1.
Yes, I got 100 more MP!
Okay, lemme grab Improved Attack 1!
You have obtained Improved Attack 1.
Sweet! And it went up by 50!
My wielder's gonna love that.
Well, future wielder.
I'm so lonely! System Gal, am I doing a good job?
C'mon, I need positive reinforcement!
Well, well. Found me a Goblin nest!
Makin' Goblin mincemeat and grabbin' those crystals!
Thank you, gentlemen!
Yup, Gobbies are chock-full of yummy skills.
UNKNOWN used a Skill:
Stealth.
Name: Goblin King
Race: Mali-human
VIT:
MP:
STR:
Astuteness:
Skills: Intimidation 2, Swordsmanship 2, Sword Arts 4, command 4
Morale Boost 3, Shield Arts 2,
Provoke 1, Throwing Weapons 1
Ambition
Willpower Manipulation
Bingo!
Here comes my…
Telekinetic Catapult attack!
Whoops, that was kinda overkill.
I know, you weren't expecting
a sword to fly in here on its own.
Name: Goblin Mage
Race: Mali-human
VIT:
INT:
STR:
Atuteness
Fire Magic 3,
Improved MP 1,
Mana Manipulation
Skills: Minerology 1, Command 1,
Staff Arts 2, Battlestaff Arts 1,
Rest in Gob-pieces, crystal fleshbags!
Yes! I finally got Fire Magic!
Skills Obtained:
Improved MP 1
Battlestaff Arts 1
Fire Magic 3
Mana Manipulation
Minerology 1
Command 1
Staff Arts 2
Rest in pieces, Gobbies.
Sword Arts 3
Hey, my Sword Mastery's up to three!
So when I absorb crystals for skills
I already have, that levels them up.
Guess that means whoever wields me
will instantly be a master swordsman!
That's gonna be awesome!
My wielder is gonna freak!
Shut your filthy mouth, and keep it shut!
What do you want, Black Cat?
Down!
Don't make me laugh, weakshit.
Black Cat, for that, you get no dinner tonight.
Stop movin' slow! Load 'em up faster!
I'm trying.
Did I give you permission to speak?!
And gods, you stink!
Godsdamned beasts who can't even Evolve.
What's that look for, huh?!
D-down!
You'll never be able to fight back.
So get used to it.
I'm going to get stronger.
I know I can Evolve.
Nothing like home, sweet pedastal…
So, the further I get from my pedastal,
Name: Lesser Wyvern
Race: Monster, Lesser Sub-Dragon
the stronger the monsters I encounter.
No way…
That's a freakin' dragon!
And the stronger the monster,
the more crystals they've got.
Skills:  Intimidation 2, Stealth 2
Fire Resistance 3, Control Air 3
Poison Resistance 3, Hardened Scales
Enhanced Olfaction, Enhanced Drain,
Enhanced Sight
Skill: Regenerate!
After absorbing a bunch of skills, I was strong enough
to handle all the monsters in Area 4.
That meant…
I can handle it now… at least, I should be able to!
The southern boss of Area 5, the Gluttonous Slimelord!
Name: Gluttonous Slimelord
Race: Monster, Slime
VIT:
INT:
STR:
AGI:
Skills: Evasion 3, Enhanced Evasion 4, Mimicry 6,
Drain 8, Harden 8, Instant Regen 7,
Status Ailment Resistance 7, Jump 5,
Soften 8, Slime Mastery 7, Slime Arts 8,
Physical Resistance 7, Predation 9,
Mana Sense 7, Pocket Dimension,
Spirit Manipulation, Enhanced Drain,
Acid Slime, Enhanced Digestion, Mana Manipulation
Gotta watch out!
Aw, crap!
I gotta finish this battle fast, or else…
Skill: Identify Creature!
The final evolution of a Gluttonous Slime.
Consumes every living thing in its vicinity and grows
exponentially without limit.
Stores away defeated prey  in a pocket dimension
for later consumption, making it capable of some
degree of spacetime magic.
Some speculate it is capable of preying upon dragons
when there are no smaller creatures to consume.
Kingdoms dispatch entire squadrons
to deal with this threat.
Crystal location: Center of its mass.
Okay, found the crystals!
Let's give my new attack a try.
Combining my Telekinetic Catapult
with my Wind Shooter spell...
into the most powerful attack I've got right now:
Heavenly Slash!
If someone was wielding me, they might not've survived.
I'd better get even more powerful, then.
Your abilities have Evolved.
You have acquired 30 Evolution Points.
Attack:
MP:
HP:
Evolution Rank:
Damn, talk about timing!
Skills Obtained:
Mimicry 1
Harden 1
Instant Regen 1
Soften 1
Pocket Dimension
Skill: Instant Regen?
Hell yeah! Uses up a ton of mana,
but I can fix my whole blade in a flash.
I'm gonna get good use outta this.
Next up, Skill: Pocket Dimension.
Whoa!
Guess this is your stereotypical magical inventory.
Area 5's got good shit!
Next, I went after the eastern boss, the Doppel Snake,
Name: Doppel Snake
Race: Monster, Serpent
VIT:
INT:
STR:
AGI:
and though its duplication was a pain in the ass,
I took it out pretty easily.
Skills Obtained:
Doppelganger
Ungodly Poison Fang
Split Mind
I was excited to get its Doppleganger ability,
but it turned out to be pretty weak,
and for some reason, it turned me naked. Total bust.
Next up, the north part of Area 5.
Name: Blast Tortoise
Race: Monster, Tortoise
VIT:
INT:
STR:
AGI:
Skills: Digging 2, Stealth 4, Control Air 5,
Pressurize Air 6, Air Bullet 7,
Vigilance 2, Harden 2, Shock Resistance 4,
Molting 3, Throwing 6, Poision Resistance 4
Bite 4, Superior Olfaction,
Enhanced Olfaction, Enhanced Carapace,
Carapace Regeneration, Diminished Pain,
Fortitude, Mana Manipulation
I'll try leveling up mid-battle…
Skill: Split Thinking!
Let's put these Evolution Points
into Earth Magic to bump it up a level!
Earth Magic 4
Let's do this! Earth Wall!
…into a Heavenly Slash!
Crystals are all mine!
Skills Obtained:
Pressurize Air
Air Bullet
Thanks a bunch!
I'll hit the next one tomorrow.
Area 5 Western Boss:
Tyrant Saber-Tooth
It can jump in mid-air?!
It's gotta have a weakness.
Oh, there we go.
Spending 15 Evolution Points to upgrade
Superior Poison Fang to Demonic Poison Fang.
Superior Poison Fang
Demonic Poison Fang
It doesn't have much Poison Resistance,
but it makes up for it with a high Defense.
If I stack on the poison damage,
and drag out the fight for a few hours…
Victory is mine!
Your abilities have Evolved.
Hell yeah!
Name:        Unknown
Registered Wielder:
None
Race:
Intelligent Weapon
Sweet. My stats went up,
Attack:
MP:
HP:
Evolution Rank:
Crystals:
Skill Slots:
Points:
and Evolving topped off my HP and MP.
And that means no more enemies to fight out here.
Skills:         Identify 6,
Enhanced Attack 1,
Rapid Regenerate,
Wielder Healing Boost 1,
Wielder Stat Boost 1,
Telekinesis, Improved Telekinesis 1
Telepathy, Improved MP 1,
Identify Creature, Mage,  Expanded Skill Slots 1
That means if I wanna find tougher monsters…
It's time to head outta Area 5 and explore the forest!
Doesn't look like there are
any tough monsters out here…
Looks like any ordinary forest.
Guess I'll fly up and take another look…
Huh? My Telekinesis isn't working!
Then I'll use Skill: Vibrofang!
Air Bullet!
Fire Arrow!
C'mon…
Every time I use a skill,
my mana gets absorbed into the ground!
You gotta be kidding me…
3 days later
Not only that, but my MP isn't regenerating!
That must be why there aren't any monsters out here.
What I wouldn't give for a gorgeous
elven huntress to stumble upon me…
10 days later
Hell, I don't care if they're not human.
I'll take a kobold or even a zombie. Someone, anyone!
1 month later
I don't care who you are!
Come and grab me, I'm begging you!
I'm a top-quality sword, here!
I'm a magic sword that'll grant you
tons of abilities just by equipping me!
I even know how to cook!
Hell, I'll even max out the skill!
Your Cooking skill has reached Level 10.
You have unlocked skill and status bonuses for Cooking.
I can deconstruct stuff, too! See, it's at Level 10!
I've got Sword Mastery and Sword Arts at Level 7,
and Fire Magic, too!
Your Fire Magic has reached Level 10.
You have acquired a new fire spell.
You hear that?! And I can appraise stuff, too!
Let's level that up while we're at it!
You have obtained the effect Wielder Stat Boost 2.
Now whoever wields me will get really frickin' strong!
I might be doomed to be a strong-ass sword
that no one ever wields…
I don't want that. Please, someone…
Anyone, please!
Get it off us already!
I-I can't!
Get them to carry the goods!
Move it, you lot!
A Twin-Headed Bear…
Don't you run! Buy us some time by givin' him a snack!
I'm gonna die?
I don't wanna die.
Now we can…
Move! Move!
No, no, no!
I can move!
Let's run!
Move, Black Cat!
I can't die…
I'm gonna die.
Use me.
I can't die.
Use me!
I'm gonna be strong!
A sword?
I want power.
I'll give you power!
Who's there?
You can hear me?!
So I can use my Telepathy if you're touching me!
Who are you?
I'm the sword! The sword you're grabbing right now!
I'm shocked.
You don't really look shocked.
I am.
Guess she's the quiet type
that keeps her emotions hidden.
Forget that, though, grab me, catgirl!
Okay.
C'mon, hurry!
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
I'm out!
You're pretty.
Thanks!
Admire me all you want later!
Do you know how to fight?
A little.
Name: None     Age: 12
Race: Beastman; Black Cat Tribe
Class: None
Status: Slave
VIT:
INT:
STR:
AGI:
Skills: Sword Mastery 1, Darkvision,
Expert Butcher, Wayfinder
She's not kidding. But don't worry!
Equip me!
I already did.
Think harder about equipping me!
Okay.
UNKNOWN registered as Wielder.
Skill Sharing activated.
UNKNOWN has aquired new skills.
Sword Mastery 7, Sword Arts 7, Fire Magic 10…
Wow…
I'll make you strong!
Let's go!
Let's go.
Whoa…
I'm moving like I'm a warrior
who's already killed tons of monsters…
Sword Mastery 7…
And her stats have been buffed, too!
There's no way we can lose!
Kill it, catgirl! Think about killing it!
Okay, got it.
Good girl.
Whatcha think? You killed it.
Because you helped me?
Yep. You better be thankful.
Yeah, thanks.
Wait a sec. Keep holding onto me.
Okay, but…
He's gonna take you away.
Only one left alive?
I should've never taken this shortcut
through the Withering Woods!
What now? Going to run?
I can't with this collar.
I've tried to kill him lots of times but it stops me.
Your collar?
Why do you have a sword?
Did you use that to kill that monster?
Don't move!
Give me the sword.
No.
Try all you want,
but as long as I have your contract
and you wear that collar, there's nothing you can do!
Telekinesis into…
Flare Arrow!
All right, my skills are back, too.
The collar…
Okay, calm down.
I am calm.
Yeah. Maybe a little too calm, actually!
Thanks.
If you wanna thank me,
you could decide to be my Wielder, but…
...are you, uh, even interested in wielding me?
Yeah, thought not.
I am. I'm very interested.
Huh? But you know you're signing up
for a dangerous journey, right?
I want to be stronger. I gotta.
What's the big reason?
No Black Cat has ever Evolved.
I'm assuming that's what you are.
So I want to Evolve.
My parents always wanted to Evolve, but never could.
Is that right? Okey-dokey.
Good backstory! I'm in!
I'll train you and get you stronger 'till you Evolve!
You mean it?
Hell yeah I do!
Oh, right, what's your name?
They took my name when they captured me.
What was it before, then?
Fran.
Okay. I'll call you Fran from here on out, then.
You sure?
You don't like it?
I do!
I'm Fran.
And you're happy about that, right?
What's your name?
Huh? Me? I'm, uh…
You don't have one?
Nope.
Then I'll give you one.
Sure, I guess. You are my Wielder, after all.
I got it.
Oh?
Teacher.
T-Teacher?! Why?!
Because you said you were gonna teach me
how to be strong. You're my Teacher.
Your name is now Teacher.
Wait, really?! I'm Teacher now? For real?
You don't like it?
It's fine. No, it's perfect!
Okay!
And so began my journey to see Fran Evolve.
Teacher…
I'm gonna get strong… strong…
Everyone's gonna want a piece of her
once she grows up...
No! I don't think so!
Anyone who gets within ten feet of Fran
is gonna get slice and diced by yours truly!
NEXT EPISODE:
THE HELLISH TRIAL AT THE ADVENTURER'S GUILD