~ MEBUKI FOREST ~
Noma...
Where are you, Noma?
What the hell is that?
You gotta be kidding me!
We must go back to the city for now!
Damn it!
How the hell are we supposed
to beat that monster...
...if we're still separated from Noma?!
Odoroki mo hentetsu mo nai
Even easy daily missions,
Iijii deirii misshon datte
That don’t involve surprises and unexpected,
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Urutora shiikuretto ruuto ga
If there was Some ultra secret route,
Sonzai shiteru to shitara kimi wa ittai
I wonder how you would break out
Dou susumu no?
through it?
Hitamuki ni hitasura ni
Even if, completely surrendering to it,
Tada ikkyo ichidou ii koto shitatte
I stubbornly did good deeds with every step,
Tanabota ni yokoku nashiteki
Unexpected luck is an unforeseen thing.
Furachi moodo ni enkaunto shitatte
Even if we was encounter in rough mode,
Shuuten wa dochira mo kitto onaji
The end point for both of us is definitely the same.
Yume no naka ja kasanari aeru futari
We were able to sneak into each other’s dreams,
Kyuuten Chokkou Konya
so we suddenly became honest.
Futoku na doa no kagi wo akete!
So open the door of immorality tonight!
Aa hotobashiru kodou ga
Ah, your gaze, dancing with a frantic heartbeat,
Samayou shisen kogashite haimawaru
Slides over my body and burns me.
Sono te de furete mukidashi no subete wo
Touch with your hand everything, which is bare in me.
Ima sugu
Pierce me
hone made
right now
tsuranuite
to the bones.
Coming up!
Mezameru sono mae ni
Before we wake up…
Before we wake up...
~ GUILD ROOFTOP ~
MISSION
MISSION IMPOSSIBLE
It's quite a bit larger than I had imagined.
It's even bigger than a person.
That repel spider was discovered yesterday
during a search in the Mebuki Forest.
Repel Spider?
REPEL SPIDER
It's a monster that can sense
the hostility and killing intent of an opponent.
And it can dodge any attacks.
So that's why it called "Repel Spider"...
That's right.
So, if you're a warrior like me,
BLACK MAGICIAN
YOU SMITH
WARRIOR
SENLIK TESTAILE
you'll be exposed to their hostility
when you approach them.
So if you're in the vanguard,
you're at a disadvantage...
Could it be that I get called up because of this?
It's originally a monster
that hunts small animals...
...with a body length of about 30 centimetres,
Hey, wait a minute, Master...
but with such a huge body,
its prey will be bigger, huh?
Even though it can't hit you,
Wait...
one bite is enough to kill you with its deadly poison...
Its threads are tougher than iron,
and on top of that, it's got a lot of power!
What a fearsome thing
to have as an enemy!
Kikuru-kun, do you think we have a chance to win?
It's a tricky enemy because of its special abilities.
But...
There should be someone
to take care of it, right?
Wait, I don't want to fight
with this strongest monster with that child's idea.
That's right! Don't do it!
It's impossible for you!
Its sensing abilities have more
range than any other Repel Spider!
It can see you from the range of a bow!
You can't beat it!
You're an "Ace,"
but you're still "Top in Kills"...
...because you've been hunting little
things from the shadows, right?
This big monster is not suited for you!
Even Noma...
You can't even rescue our friends!
Stay out of this!
I heard that you're a first-class evader, too, but you're not!
You don't have a single advantage over them
in terms of strength or ability!
Don't get carried away!
I want you to know,
DON'T GET CARRIED AWAY
DON'T HAVE A SINGLE ADVANTAGE
HUNTING LITTLE THINGS
FROM THE SHADOWS
KEPT HUNTING SMALL THINGS
that I can't avoid the knife of words.
My ace mentality is weak, so can you stop it?
DON'T GET CARRIED AWAY
DON'T HAVE A SINGLE ADVANTAGE
HUNTING LITTLE THINGS
FROM THE SHADOWS
KEPT HUNTING SMALL THINGS
MENTALLY WEAK
~ MEBUKI FOREST ~
I see. I understand the situation.
There are still some stragglers
from that party left in the forest,
and we're going to go rescue them, right?
Yeah. This time, the monster
is not a good match for you guys.
Besides, it's important to save lives.
Hitamuki will search for the guard
while avoiding the monster.
I'll do my best with dedication!
I just need to find the owner
of this scent, right!
Maidena is to heal
the guards if they are injured.
Y-Yeah!
Hanabata, you take care
of the emergency guard.
Roger that!
I should have made
the ideal division of roles...
I should have done it, but...
AS USUAL
FAILURE
Comin' at ya with full power!
FLOWER
But I couldn't imagine...
...things going according to the ideal plan.
Hanabata, you've got to get your act together!
And don't use Frenzy at all!
I-I understand!
FIDGET FIDGET
If you're so worried like that,
why don't we just work together?
Still, it's safer than over here.
Fighting with four newcomers
is indeed a heavy burden.
I would be nice if I was in the rescue group.
NODDING
That monster is strong,
can avoid any attack,
has a lethal poison, and tricky trap
with the thread that was unmatched.
I don't feel like I can be of any use here...
Give yourself some thought before you give up.
The reason it can avoid attacks so accurately...
...is because it can sense
where in your body you are focused.
If that is the case,
then your "massive firepower...
...that even I don't know where it will hit" attack...
...is a threat to the Repel Spider,
which relies on the thoughts of its opponents.
Seriously?
I never thought I'd see the day
when my lack of combat sense would shine.
I guess we'll just use the "hunting"
method and hunt it down from the surroundings.
HUNTING
Hunting?
If you surround them with flames,
you can block their escape route, right?
Since you're not directly targeting that monster,
you don't have to worry about them reading your hostility.
Don't be fooled by the catalog specs,
there are many ways to do it.
Master, you know,
you don't look very impressive for an ace.
for
for the
--------------------
for the ace
--------
I
I love
I love this
I love this game
I love this game so
I love this game so much
it's
it's so
it's so fun
it's so fun to
-------------------------------------
it's so fun to play
And you don't look very strong either.
-------------------
It
It looks
---------------------
For the ace.
---------------------------------------
I love this game so much
it's so fun to play
It looks like
---------------------
For the ace.
---------------------------------------
I love this game so much
it's so fun to play
It looks like great
It looks like great and
It looks like great and strong.
--------------------------
I
I don't
I don't even
I don't even feel
I don't even feel it.
It looks like great and strong.
------------------------------
I don't even feel it.
------------------
For the ace.
I love this game so much
it's so fun to play
It looks like great and strong.
------------------------------
I don't even feel it.
------------------
For the ace.
I love this game so much
it's so fun to play
It looks like great and strong.
------------------------------
I don't even feel it.
------------------
For the ace.
I love this game so much
it's so fun to play
It looks like great and strong.
------------------------------
I don't even feel it.
------------------
For the ace.
I love this game so much
it's so fun to play
It looks like great and strong.
------------------------------
I don't even feel it.
------------------
For the ace.
I love this game so much
it's so fun to play
It looks like great and strong.
------------------------------
I don't even feel it.
------------------
For the ace.
I love this game so much
it's so fun to play
It looks like great and strong.
------------------------------
I don't even feel it.
------------------
For the ace.
I love this game so much
it's so fun to play
It looks like great and strong.
------------------------------
I don't even feel it.
------------------
For the ace.
I love this game so much
it's so fun to play
It looks like great and strong.
------------------------------
I don't even feel it.
------------------
For the ace.
I love this game so much
it's so fun to play
It looks like great and strong.
------------------------------
I don't even feel it.
------------------
For the ace.
I love this game so much
it's so fun to play
It looks like great and strong.
------------------------------
I don't even feel it.
------------------
For the ace.
I love this game so much
it's so fun to play
It looks like great and strong.
------------------------------
I don't even feel it.
------------------
For the ace.
I love this game so much
it's so fun to play
YOU'RE NOT AN ACE AT ALL, ARE YOU?
You're not an ace at all, are you?
Can you stop hurting me twice...
for that one fluffy compliment?
YOU'RE NOT AN ACE AT ALL, ARE YOU?
Good grief, I'm not even in the mood for it.
I wonder if the other side is safe?
I never thought I'd be more anxious
than in a fight with a powerful enemy.
SLIMY
Hitamuki! Geez, what are you doing?
"There are no demons nearby,
but there are nests everywhere, so be careful!"
You said that, right?!
Why did yourself fall for it?
I'm sorry...
Give me your hand so I can pull you out.
Hold on, Maidena!
That spider's web is so strong and elastic!
Mede-chan, let go of my hand!
Me too?!
SLIMY
I can't pull it off...
Mede-chan... Please don't move too much...
Even if you said that...
We have to do something about this situation...
W-Wait、S-Sto—
Your shaking is a little too... Stop it...
I'm... Sorry... but I can't control it...
G-Geez... I can't believe this is happening...
Hitamuki! I told you don't move!
Even though there are no monsters involved...
...the two of them are entangled
in each other's bodies!
I... I have to stand firm!
It might get a little hot,
but I'm going to burn the web,
so just stay still.
I don't know if my fire magic
can handle the nest.
Spider's web is said to exceed
the strength of iron,
but its main ingredient is protein.
Now you know why I brought you here, right?
We're almost at the point where
Hitamuki had sensed before.
The process is the same
as we discussed earlier.
I'll attract them and act as a decoy.
While I'm at it, you will burn
the surrounding with flames.
After that, once the area is established,
fire with Voltega in the center of it,
and if there's no escape route,
it doesn't matter if they notices your hostility.
Somehow, I'm starting to lose
confidence in my role—
I was worried that in case it went for us,
THE REPEL SPIDER HAS APPEARED!
but it was worth burning the nests from one side...
to the other and provoke it.
Tokishikko, let's go with the plan!
Don't be afraid of it, just burn the area!
O-Okay!
It's kind of impossible to target precisely
only the area around the spider...
Tokishikko, you don't have to care about me,
just lock me in here!
I got it!
Please hesitate for a bit.
Fire magic...
Ignite!
It can evade before the spell is chanted?!
Master... I'm sorry.
So that's why...
It is impossible to look at this human-sized
poisonous spider and not be wary of it.
I guess they had read our intent to trap them.
Let's try again with another plan...
Ge-Get away from my Master! Ignila!
Master, hang in there!
I was aware of it...
The Repel Spider is gone!
That I have a bad habit of imposing my ideals on others...
Master! Master!
Master! Hang in there! Master!
Tokishikko had said many times,
that she had no confidence in me...
But I kept pushing my ideals onto others...
Master... Master!
Now, what should I do...
Master! Master!
...about this situation?
Immoral Guild.
~ GUILD ROOFTOP ~
MINT
Laia, Leia!
MINT ICE
MINT ICE CREAM
I'm home!
I have a bad feeling...
Noma, are you okay?
Yeah...
I may have spoken a little too harsh to him...
I'm sure he'll be back soon to ask for help.
And when that comes, let's apologise to him.
Are Kikuru-kun and the others all right?
Eh?!
Master! Master! Open your eyes!
Don't die on me!
Master, give me all the straight man comments
in the eye like you always do.
Here, one, two...
What the heck!
I've never said that...
I won't forgive you if you die, you know?
If you die, I'll tell everyone
that you has violated me!
------------------------------------------------------------------
THE ACE OF MEBUKI FORCED A MINOR TO DRINK
I will say you forced me to drink alcohol...
and then pushed me down!
How's that?!
You don't want to die, right?!
Wh-What the heck?!
You trying to make a dying person shout...
Are you a demon...?
And don't try to dirt my name with that...
I thought it was a lethal poison,
how can you still move?
Just before I was stabbed,
I applied the antidote
I'd planted in my teeth right away.
There's no healer, so I'm not going
to take on this mission unprepared.
I prepared your portion too.
As expected from Master...
But the poison seems
to be more potent than I thought...
The fever and numbness effect
still remains in me...
PUSH FORWARD
RETURN TO CITY
Then, let's get back to the city right now!
No, I want to settle this today.
Did you see any monsters on the way here?
I think they're all afraid of Repel Spider,
so they've moved their dwellings.
Then, where do the monsters
go after being chased out of the forest?
Moreover, where did that spider
go now that it has no prey?
The city...
We have end this as soon as possible,
before the conditions become worse...
B-But you can't do that with that body!
10 minutes... I can recover in 10 minutes...
Ice magic, Coldra.
This will give us some
protection if it comes back.
And people won't be able to see us.
What I'm about to do is an experiment,
and it's my first time doing this.
Whatever the results,
don't be awkward afterwards, okay?
To-Tokishikko...
Master...
Have you ever heard of "Curse Name"?
Curse Name,
CURSE NAME
That is a rare example of how a person's
name itself can be used to activate a spell.
The person can receive the blessing of the
word or spirit that the name holds.
That's the reason why...
parents giving a name to their children,
while thinking "I want to grow up like this".
This is perfect form of...
"the name represents the person".
Tokishikko... Toxic...
I see, "Poison"!
Yes.
But mine is a name that spells "poison"
and "detoxification" for poison.
POISON NULLIFICATION
In short, it's a passive skill to nullify poison.
I see.
Tokishikko-san, you're amazing!
I can't believe you've never fallen sick before!
So that's the reason why you're never sick...
How did you know that?
I-I saw it on TV...!
------------
BREAKING
NEWS:
----------------------------------------------------------------------
TOKISHIKKO HAS NEVER BEEN SICK
Which channel was it?
In other words,
"You conquer poison with poison".
By coming in contact with me
or by pouring my fluids into your wounds,
I may be able...
...to draw out the poison from your body.
Please do it.
Woah...
What a nice body.
Your body right here,
so stiff, and pounding hard,
so hot... and hard...
Can you stop saying
such a misleading expression like that?
When she does it without saying a word,
only the sound stands out,
it only makes me feel strange...
I'm sorry, but removing poison from this part
of the body is out of my area of expertise.
Shut up.
How is it? Do you feel better?
Honestly, I don't feel any different...
Just this part is feeling better?
Please, don't tease me like that.
Well, then,
let's try it from "inside".
Ki-Kissing is embarrassing...
So I'm going to...
...drop my saliva to your mouth from here.
You must swallow it right away, okay?!
Don't even try to taste it!
O-Okay...
I haven't eaten anything
after I brushed my teeth this morning,
so it should be okay...
But...
I should've chewed some gum...
Tokishikko...
Isn't this...
...more embarrassing than kissing?
It tasted...
...slightly like mint.
I can move.
The fever is gone.
Master, the poison is...
Thank you.
I'm saved by you.
I was slightly regretting, thinking,
"I wouldn't have had to defend this girl...
...if I'd known she has poison nullification".
But with this, the negative thinking has gone.
Somehow I know the reason
why you're not popular.
I mean,
my name comes from "Poison".
I don't want anyone else
to know this and hate me.
I'm a girl after all...
So, the problem starts now.
How we can beat that Repel Spider?
Even if we don't directly
target the main body,
it reacts to indirect hostility,
such as setting a trap.
INDIRECT HOSTILITY
----------------------------
------------------------
DOES NOT INVOLVE
HUMAN WILL!
In other words, the trap must be an installation...
...type that does not involve human will.
I don't like the idea of setting a trap...
...that can catch up with such
a huge monster like that,
but there's no other choice.
There is a place that I want to go to.
Place you want to go?
ON THE OTHER HAND,
THE RESCUE GROUP...
Purifying magic,
Purifull.
----
MAIDENA HAS CHANTED PURIFULL
The poison is gone!
Thank you.
Thank God.
I can use white magic too,
RED MAGICIAN
NOMA RUNE
but my purification magic is not enough to detoxify it.
All I could do was to hide here and wait for help.
I feel like I'm doing a prefer job for once!
It's all thanks to Hitamuki-san
that we could find you.
I've put you all in danger because of me,
I'm really sorry!
No, that's...
It's hard to imagine how tough
it must have been on the way here,
by looking at your both condition.
Y-Yeah...
It was a journey...
...filled with many strong enemies...
Maidena...
~ WATERFRONT SHELTER ~
A hut?
It's a shelter.
If the quest takes long enough until night,
guards can lodge at this place.
Lodge... Could it be, Master...
You're planning to have a
one-night stand with me...
...just because you couldn't get over
how horny you were earlier?
How many times
do you want to bring that up?
Even though they have protection against monster,
people rarely sleep in a den of monster.
We will use this shelter as a trap.
Using this as a trap?
I see!
If it is a cramped place, there is no escape
even if it can read our attacks.
So Master will lure the monster
into the hut and I will set it on fire!
ARGH
Hey, am I not still inside?!
Your sacrifice won't be forgotten.
I'll curse you for eternity.
Well, we will use fire,
but not like that.
First of all, that spider
can't get through here, can it?
I've got a another plan.
The furniture and floors are wood,
the door steel,
the wall stone.
I don't think we have to worry
about it collapsing before the plan starts.
Master?
There's only one window.
I think the size is not a problem.
And,
it's facing south.
So that's my lifeline.
All right.
Master?!
What's "all right"?! The guild will be
mad at us if we break the amulet!
Because with that thing in place,
the spider won't come, right?
Well, that's true...
But...
And now we're going to
do something outrageous.
Tokishikko,
burn this hut.
To be continued.
TO BE CONTINUE
Ijippari ni kakuzatou wo tokashitara
If you stubbornly dissolve the sugar cubes
Sunao no mahou
Magic of honesty
Doji ni wa chotto oome no shinamon
Clumsy and a little too much cinnamon
Yarisugite daddadubada
Too much daddadubada
Mata mebunryou no kimagure to yasashisa de
In addition, with the whims and gentleness of mebenryo
Himitsu no reshipi wo mou kakimidasanaide
Don't disturb the secret recipe anymore
Oh don’t call my name
Oh don't call my name
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Amai dake janai
Not just sweet
Mune no oku no tokimeki iroiro
Heart-pounding feelings deep in my chest Various things
Watashi dake no baransu wo
I have my own balance
Wakatte hoshikute
I want you to understand
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Karai dake ja iya
I don't like it
Mune no oku no tokimeki wa
just because it's spicy
Mochiron desho namida to koi no mariaaju...
Of course, if it's tears, it's a marriage of love
...Yappari wakaranaide!
…I don't know!
NEXT
NEXT EPISODE
THE
THE PERFECT
THE PERFECT COMBUSTION
THANKS