Odoroki mo hentetsu mo nai
Even easy daily missions,
Iijii deirii misshon datte
That don’t involve surprises and unexpected,
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Urutora shiikuretto ruuto ga
If there was Some ultra secret route,
Sonzai shiteru to shitara kimi wa ittai
I wonder how you would break out
Dou susumu no?
through it?
Hitamuki ni hitasura ni
Even if, completely surrendering to it,
Tada ikkyo ichidou ii koto shitatte
I stubbornly did good deeds with every step,
Tanabota ni yokoku nashiteki
Unexpected luck is an unforeseen thing.
Furachi moodo ni enkaunto shitatte
Even if we was encounter in rough mode,
Shuuten wa dochira mo kitto onaji
The end point for both of us is definitely the same.
Yume no naka ja kasanari aeru futari
We were able to sneak into each other’s dreams,
Kyuuten Chokkou Konya
so we suddenly became honest.
Futoku na doa no kagi wo akete!
So open the door of immorality tonight!
Aa hotobashiru kodou ga
Ah, your gaze, dancing with a frantic heartbeat,
Samayou shisen kogashite haimawaru
Slides over my body and burns me.
Sono te de furete mukidashi no subete wo
Touch with your hand everything, which is bare in me.
Ima sugu
Pierce me
hone made
right now
tsuranuite
to the bones.
Coming up!
Mezameru sono mae ni
Before we wake up…
Before we wake up...
~ MEBUKI FOREST ~
Kik-kun, Mede-chan, and I are doing a quest today.
MAIDE
Toki-chan is having a special physical training,
mentored by Hana, apparently.
For now, you should start with three hundred reps
of push-ups, sit-ups, and squats respectively.
Goodbye, current world.
I don't think I can come back home alive.
Today's not like your usual monster hunting.
We're here on a quest to gather
the Lupinusilence flower.
Lupinusilence?
LUPINUSILENCE
It's a troublesome flower that disperses pollen with a silencing effect
when the petals are strongly agitated.
So we won't be able to speak, then?
Not being able to speak is no problem to me
and Hitamuki, since we use physical attacks,
but someone who uses magical attacks
like you won't be able to chant.
While we're gathering them as materials
for equipment and medicine,
they're in the way of the guards,
so we're also getting rid of them.
So we don't need to fight monsters today?
No, we don't have to take
the initiative to attack them now.
Hitamuki, be on guard
for our surroundings.
Sure, I'll do my best with dedication
so that you can do your job safely—
THUNK!
Hitamuki?!
Endure...
Geez, what are you doing?
Just focus half your attention on other people
and the other half on yourself, okay?
I'm sorry...
I'll fix you up, so stay still.
Oh, you don't have to.
Actually, I've been doing a special training,
and finally obtained a new arte!
A new technique?
Yes!
It's a healing method using chakra.
I can control my mana and use it
to increase my healing power...
And just like this, I'm all good now!
Right...
RECON
COOKING
HEALING
She becomes better at all the skills
that have nothing to do with attacks.
What is a martial artist, actually...
It'd be great if I could heal other people too,
but too bad I can't.
Of course you can't heal someone else.
Why's that?
Hitamuki, can you reattach this
snapped branch with your own power?
Of course I can't!
Exactly.
In other words, people can imagine
and carry out the action to "destroy someone",
but they lack the ability to interfere
with the "restoring of someone".
They can only heal their own wounds
and illnesses using natural healing.
That's why people use medicine and tools.
I see.
Huh? But you can heal other people too, right?
Us white sorcerers
--------------------------------------
HOLY BIRD PHOENIZASK
are borrowing the power
of the Holy Bird Phoenizask,
who regulates the restoring of humans.
I see... so that holy crest
is the source of power, huh...
That holy crest...
you sound like you've seen one in person.
I-I saw it on TV!
All right, time for us
to catch some lupinusilence!
Huh...
I already told you earlier,
but take care to not touch the petals, okay?
Okay!
I'll do my...
...best with dedication.
Even though we don't have to intentionally fight,
there's still a chance that we'll
still be attacked by the monster...
Kikuru's gone pretty far, too...
N-Not like I want him
to stay close to me, though!
That must means he really trusts
Hitamuki's recon, huh...
Don't worry.
She's more cautious to her
surroundings than normal people.
Wait, was there an ivy hanging around here?
A STUFFPECKER HAS APPEARED!
Kiku—
MAIDENA HAS BREATHED THE LUPINUSILENCE'S POLLEN
Where's Hitamuki?!
She doesn't know that a monster's here?!
This flower smells so strong,
my nose has stopped working...
If it comes to this, I'll search around
for enemies with my ears and eyes!
Mede-chan?
Help me, Hitamuki!
MAYDAY!
Heeeelp!
HELP!
Hitamuki!
Help me!
Nooo!
Looks like Mede-chan's having
so much fun with this job!
I should do my best too!
She's really innocent...
for better or for worse...
Why does it have to be me today
and not Hitamuki in the first place?
A stuffpecker should have a habit of collecting
and playing with shiny objects...
It's the precious church wand,
but if this gets it off me...
It's not going for my wand, but me?!
No... You can't touch me there...!
It's too tight...!
No... please... stop!
I'm being toyed by the thing!
It's going to paralyse me
and bring me to its nest...?
I'm scared... What will happen to me now...
Someone help me...
Someone...
Kikuru!
Mede-chan!
I'm sorry! I didn't know there was a monster!
I was also responsible for leaving
the lookout to you, Hitamuki.
I've always left it to you these days,
my senses are getting dull.
Mede-chan, you're bleeding internally...
I guess you can't heal until
the Silence effect wears off, huh?
Sorry, but you gotta suck it up
until we reach the city.
Kik-kun...
There's something I want to try.
C-Could you... leave us for a second?
Okay.
W-Well, then...
Excuse me...
Huh?! Wait.
What is this?!
Huuuuuh?!
S-So soft...
If our skins touch each other
my chakra healing might also
be transferred to Mede-chan's body!
A-As if I could be...
I'm healed?
I'm healed!
I-I did it!
I'll dub my chakra "physchakra" now!
--------------------
PHYSCHAKRA
Huh? She's healed?
No way... she healed me with her own power...
You got in danger again
because of me, Mede-chan...
I'm...
...really glad you're healed now!
Which one is younger here, again?
You see,
I've been thinking that your innocence
makes you cut out to be a white sorceress.
And today, I know that
you have the quality for it.
You're definitely suited best for a support role
in terms of your personality and abilities!
Huh? What?
You're not cut out to be a martial artist!
She finally said it...
Things may not turn into what I had hoped,
but she's definitely getting
better in her own way.
Kik-kun.
I still have some room for growth... right?
Right... I could use a sub-healer now too.
Immoral Guild!
A
A NEW
A NEW FAMILY
A NEW FAMILY MEMBER
Hey, Kikuru. Are Hitamuki
and the others not coming today?
Nope.
They're all getting another
medical check-up at the hospital.
It's not because my fishy
check-up got busted, right?
So I'll be hunting
for monsters on my own today.
I've been spending my time and energy on them,
so I couldn't find my own gig.
Oh, come on! You can rest for a day!
Let's go on a date around the city!
A date...
Hey, stop clinging to me so much.
Kikuru's all mine today!
You really like Kikuru-kun,
don't you, Esyne-chan?
Yeah! He's so reliable and cool, I love him!
But don't cause him too much trouble, okay?
I won't!
Girls often perceive admiration
for older people as infatuation...
I remember seeing and hearing about this.
After all, they see the boys
of their age as kids too...
Hence, the "older age" criterion by itself would
make their judging criteria more lenient.
Before I hurt her in the future,
it's an adult's job to correct
this misunderstanding, I guess.
Esyne, I'm glad that you're liking me,
but that's not romantic love at all.
What you're feeling toward me is just—
Huh? What do you mean?
Huh?
I don't see you that way, you know?
Wow... I want to die now...
But you always said that you love me!
And you also said earlier that
you want to go on a date with me!
AN ADULT MALE PRESSING A PRIMARY SCHOOL GIRL
Kikuru-kun, calm down!
You'll cause a huge misunderstanding from the people around!
Of course, it's true that I want to go on a date.
With you and Mama, the three of us!
Huh?!
I want you to become Mama's new husband...
In other words, become my new papa!
Esyne-chan, I've never heard of that!
Kikuru-kun and I are getting married...
That's not happening!
Not happening...
Huh?! What's wrong with you, Kikuru-kun?!
I'll just go home and get some sleep today...
B-Besides...
I'm still... registered...
Enome-san?!
Mama!
CLINIC
Sorry to make you worry about me, you two.
You must have been exhausted, right?
Please stay in bed.
You've been working late these days too.
I'll handle the reception desk,
so get some rest.
But before that, let's change
into something more comfortable.
Kikuru, help me undress her.
Sure.
Sure, I won't!
Stop trying to set me up
with Enome-san as a fluke.
With one side not in top form now,
it's the perfect chance for you two to hook up...
Even though her mother has fallen sick,
she still turns anything to profit...
Still...
Never mind helping her change,
thinking about the scandal
that once caused me to reach beyond her clothes...
Yeah, I'll just take that secret
with me for life.
She's done changing!
Okay...
N-Naked... shirt?
Even though I'm just going to sleep,
to think I'm dressed like this in my workplace...
I thought if she wore her underwear,
she'd feel uncomfortable...
She's pretending to be innocent, but I bet
she knows what she's doing with this.
So I wanted to check Mama's temperature,
but I couldn't find the thermometre...
Huh? It's a clinic, though?
Yeah.... so, Kikuru...
Can you check her temperature
with your forehead?
You're hiding the thermometre, aren't you?
You can just do that yourself...
Sorry! Gotta go back
to the reception desk now! Adieu!
Hey!
Uh...
Y-Yes?
It'll be really bad if you have a fever, so...
Do you mind if I check?
I'm sorry for troubling you...
Here goes...
Yeah... I-can't-tell-at-all!
Her sexy scent makes it impossible
to measure her temperature!
In fact, I'm feeling somewhat feverish myself!
Oh, no! You're the one
with an actual fever, Kikuru!
Well, look at that...
I guess it's only natural...
My burden is nothing compared
to what you have to carry every day...
I-It's not that...
I'm feeling fine now,
so get some rest.
That's not it, Enome-san!
You should calm down—
E-Enome-san your shirt...
is drenched in sweat...
Kikuru-kun...
I'm sorry...
No, this is nothing.
No, not for this...
Wait, actually, for this too...
You see, recently,
I'd requested skilled guards in other cities,
but in the end I didn't get a response
from any of them...
You did that for me...?
The monsters in this area are less
dangerous than in other cities,
so we are inevitably given a lower priority.
But, even though they're not skilled,
I don't regret introducing those girls to you, okay?
You've become brighter ever since
you've met with those girls, after all.
Thanks to you,
they'll be able to improve themselves,
and become reliable, matured guards.
Enome-san, I'm sorry to interrupt this thankful talk,
And that won't be in the far future...
but most of your words
just go over my head.
Even though you're facing away from me,
your being naked is still driving me crazy.
You should be more aware
of the sex appeal you give off.
Still... I can't develop a conscience of pointing out
the lack of a sense of danger, unfortunately.
If she's willing to show
only the back of her body,
I'd like to support that statement
to the fullest extent now.
I can't believe you've made this
much progress for only a few minutes...
Enome-san, you can't dress like
that in front of a guy.
It's too late.
Oh, my. It's your workplace,
but you're already raring to go here in the noon?
R-Resumisu-san?
Sensei, thank you for the other day!
Sensei?
D-Don't call me that...
Come to think of it,
you're starting today, right?
How tall are you?
One Hanabata.
1 HANABATA = 110 CM
Actually, we were also recruiting more staff alongside guards.
One Hanabata...?
And only the staff part went well...
Well, it was outrageous that you'd been working
on your own the whole time, too, so that's fine.
But why Resumisu-san?
To put it short,
the hospital found out
about the incident, and I got fired!
----------------------
THE BAD FEELING
CAME TRUE
Well, she's behaved in a way that's unbecoming
of someone involved in healthcare.
Resumisu.
I didn't recall seeing this dynamite body.
Shock!
MEDICAL CHECK-UP FORM
The presence of a K-cup was really bad, huh?
You should say Hanabata instead.
But I've managed to hide your identity
until the end, so rest assured!
H-Huh...
I've been complicit
with a nasty person, apparently.
The guild doesn't seem to have
a resident health doctor, too.
Don't worry, I'll help you with the office work
in normal hours and when you're sick!
Resumisu-chan, you're so reliable!
Yes!
Anxiety!
Let's go now, Esyne-chan!
Yeah!
Whoa!
Resumisu-san!
I'm sorry, you two!
Hang on!
The steam is hot!
I have learned first-hand that an increase
in staffing does not necessarily translate
into a reduction in the workload.
I have to go...
Calm down, Enome-san!
Let's have faith in Esyne's backing for now!
Even though she's still young,
she's capable enough!
But what if Esyne-chan collapses as well?!
I... I...!
Y-Your chest...!
I'm sorry!
If I recall correctly, she's now...
Not wearing...
Ki...Kikuru...kun...
Mama! Resumisu-san overwrote
the new data with the existing data!
Looks like Kikuru has overwritten
your data too, Mama...
Esyne-chan?!
I'd love to have a younger brother!
Esyne-chan!
Since then, Esyne started calling me Papa.
To be continued...?
TO BE CONTINUE
Ijippari ni kakuzatou wo tokashitara
If you stubbornly dissolve the sugar cubes
Sunao no mahou
Magic of honesty
Doji ni wa chotto oome no shinamon
Clumsy and a little too much cinnamon
Yarisugite daddadubada
Too much daddadubada
Mata mebunryou no kimagure to yasashisa de
In addition, with the whims and gentleness of mebenryo
Himitsu no reshipi wo mou kakimidasanaide
Don't disturb the secret recipe anymore
Oh don’t call my name
Oh don't call my name
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Amai dake janai
Not just sweet
Mune no oku no tokimeki iroiro
Heart-pounding feelings deep in my chest Various things
Watashi dake no baransu wo
I have my own balance
Wakatte hoshikute
I want you to understand
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Karai dake ja iya
I don't like it
Mune no oku no tokimeki wa
just because it's spicy
Mochiron desho namida to koi no mariaaju...
Of course, if it's tears, it's a marriage of love
...Yappari wakaranaide!
…I don't know!
NEXT
NEXT EPISODE
MISSION
MISSION IMPOSSIBLE
MINT
MINT ICE
MINT ICE CREAM