Odoroki mo hentetsu mo nai
Even easy daily missions,
Iijii deirii misshon datte
That don’t involve surprises and unexpected,
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Urutora shiikuretto ruuto ga
If there was Some ultra secret route,
Sonzai shiteru to shitara kimi wa ittai
I wonder how you would break out
Dou susumu no?
through it?
Hitamuki ni hitasura ni
Even if, completely surrendering to it,
Tada ikkyo ichidou ii koto shitatte
I stubbornly did good deeds with every step,
Tanabota ni yokoku nashiteki
Unexpected luck is an unforeseen thing.
Furachi moodo ni enkaunto shitatte
Even if we was encounter in rough mode,
Shuuten wa dochira mo kitto onaji
The end point for both of us is definitely the same.
Yume no naka ja kasanari aeru futari
We were able to sneak into each other’s dreams,
Kyuuten Chokkou Konya
so we suddenly became honest.
Futoku na doa no kagi wo akete!
So open the door of immorality tonight!
Aa hotobashiru kodou ga
Ah, your gaze, dancing with a frantic heartbeat,
Samayou shisen kogashite haimawaru
Slides over my body and burns me.
Sono te de furete mukidashi no subete wo
Touch with your hand everything, which is bare in me.
Ima sugu
Pierce me
hone made
right now
tsuranuite
to the bones.
Coming up!
Mezameru sono mae ni
Before we wake up…
Before we wake up...
Take care!
---------------
KIKURU
-----
NA
KKO
ATA
AMU
------
ENA
IKKO
BATA
AMU
DENA
HIKKO
BATA
TAMU
DENA
HIKKO
ABATA
ITAMU
IDENA
SHIKKO
ABATA
ITAMU
AIDENA
SHIKKO
NABATA
HITAMU
AIDENA
ISHIKKO
NABATA
HITAMU
NAIDENA
ISHIKKO
ANABATA
HITAMU
MAIDENA
KISHIKKO
ANABATA
-------------
HITAMU
MAIDENA
KISHIKKO
ANABATA
HITAMU
-------------
MAIDENA
OKISHIKKO
HANABATA
HITAMU
MAIDENA
OKISHIKKO
HANABATA
-------------
HITAMU
MAIDENA
TOKISHIKKO
---------------
HANABATA
HITAMU
---------------
MAIDENA
TOKISHIKKO
----------------
HANABATA
HITAMU
----------------
MAIDENA
TOKISHIKKO
---------------
HANABATA
--------------
HITAMU
----------------
MAIDENA
TOKISHIKKO
-----------------
HANABATA
HITAMU
----------------
MAIDENA
TOKISHIKKO
----------------
HANABATA
HITAMU
MAIDENA
-----------------
TOKISHIKKO
HANABATA
-----------------
HITAMU
MAIDENA
------------------
TOKISHIKKO
HANABATA
HITAMU
-----------------
MAIDENA
------------------
TOKISHIKKO
HANABATA
HITAMU
------------------
MAIDENA
-----------------
TOKISHIKKO
------------------
HANABATA
HITAMU
------------------
MAIDENA
-----------------
TOKISHIKKO
------------------
HANABATA
Welcome back!
Good work with the quest today, everyone.
I
I DON'T
I DON'T WANT
I DON'T WANT TO
I DON'T WANT TO GO
I DON'T WANT TO GO HOME
I DON'T WANT TO GO HOME NOW
And here you go.
SALARY
Y
RY
Your salary for this month!
SALARY
LARY
It marks your first now!
It's been a month since I became a guard...
Wait, it's only been a month?
It feels like forever with all the screw-ups
and too reckless stunts...
Now that's one long, hectic month.
Enome-san, can I really take this money?
I've never been able to take down
any single monster...
Of course you can.
Thank you!
SLEEPING LIKE A LOG FROM THE DAILY FATIGUE
You're the one who accompanied Kikuru-kun on quests the most,
and he said he really appreciated your help.
SILENCE
B-But I'm the one he's been helping!
SLEEPING LIKE A LOG FROM THE DAILY
Here you go, Hanabata-chan.
Thank you.
You don't have yours, Mede-chan?
I'll get mine from the church.
Look at the list of particulars in that sheet.
You can find "White Magic Insurance"
in the deduction column there, right?
The money for white sorcerers
comes from there.
White Magic Insurance...
I think I saw it when I signed
the guard contract.
I don't know what this is,
but I can just stamp it, right?
No, you should know, okay?
STAMP
White magic is almost the exclusive method of healing anywhere, and it's crucial to a party.
It's like a forced insurance
that all guards must subscribe to.
Forced... insurance?
White magic sure is awesome!
I really can't understand the meaning
behind her physchakra...
Salaries are broken down
into a fixed salary for each job,
and a percentage from exterminations.
So each person may receive
a different amount...
It's still a large amount of money for me!
I'll use it wisely!
Hitamuki-chan...
I'll throw it all on entertainment!
I'll show you how unplanned I am,
making the most of the advantages of living at home!
How can you say that
in front of a pure girl like her?
Just give 90% of your money to Hitamuki.
I want to pay Kik-kun back somehow.
The reason I made it out alive every time...
is that he never gave up on me
and always helped me.
You're right.
Excluding Hanabata,
the three of us wouldn't be
talking here if he weren't there for us.
Well, yeah, I admit that he's saved me
from dire situations a few times.
I've also caused Senpai a lot of trouble,
and I want to make up for it!
But how do we please him now?
Maybe we can do a Hitamuki
leg sandwich to his head?
So soft!
I can't do anything so rude like that!
He won't be happy about it!
I think it's the best solution to this, though.
He said he wants a quiet youth,
so he's been trying to quit being a guard, right?
If that's the case...
...then why don't we just
present him his youth?
Youth?
Present his youth?
But how?
What do you... want?
Wait, Maidena?!
I-I'm sorry...
Please... don't hurt me...
What are you doing here?!
And what are you doing?!
I'm looking forward to the evening paper.
Sorry for suddenly barging in on you!
We were so determined to make you happy that we lost our way, Senpai.
Make me happy?
Wait, how did you get inside?
MUEEEEEEH
We thought we'd present your youth to you,
since you've always helped us.
Present my youth?
First,
We thought a situation where the "childhood friend wakes you up in the morning" would work well...
How long are you planning on sleeping, Kikuru?
--------------------------------------------------
HOAAAAM...
HOAAAAM... JUST
HOAAAAM... JUST FIVE
HOAAAAM... JUST FIVE MORE MINUTES~
But you never let your guard down,
so it's a total flop.
MAIDEEE...
So that's why you guys
are wearing school uniforms?
We were still young maidens
in high school just one-two months ago.
Come on, feast your eyes on us~
MAIDEE
I don't have my uniform,
so Toki-chan lent me a set.
But...
We were too preoccupied with thinking
what we should do to
not consider the dangers caused.
Sorry.
I know you guys don't mean harm, so it's okay.
But you sure you want to come to the house
of a man who lives alone in those outfits?
I think we might have caught
the public's attention earlier.
Tokishikko.
Maybe we should plan
our service menu more meticulously?
We can add options around that,
depending on what he wants, right?
I'll do any requests
as long as it's within my power!
I-If I could make him happy,
then maybe I could stretch myself a bit...
If he gets overboard and puts up extreme requests,
then I'm heading straight home.
I bet you'll have so many NG
moments when we're there.
And so we came here smiling,
-------
SERV
ERVI
RVIC
VICE
ICE -
CE - M
E - ME
- MEN
MEN
MENU
ENU -
NU - O
U - OP
- OPT
OPTI
PTIO
TION
ION
ON
N
---------------------------------
SERVICE MENU - OPTIONS
---------
E
EX
EXT
EXTR
EXTRE
XTREM
with a nice little talk to avoid being obnoxious.
TREME
REME R
EME RE
ME REQ
E REQU
REQUE
---------------------------------
EXTREME REQUEST
----------------
STRETCH
RETCH
ETCH
TCH
CH
------
S
H
ST
STRE
STRET
TRETC
RETCH
ETCH
TCH
CH
H
S
----------
ST
-----------
STR
STRET
STRETC
STRETCH
TRETCH
S
--------
RETCH
---------
ST
ETCH
-----------
STR
TCH
-------------
STRE
CH
---------------
STRET
H
-----------------
STRETC
-------------------
STRETCH
-------
---------------------
STRETCH
-----------------------
------
STRETCH
---------------------
-------------------
-----------------
TRETCH
---------------
RETCH
-------------
ETCH
-----------
TCH
---------
CH
S
-------
H
-----
ST
Your miraculously chosen words only led to obnoxity!
-----
STR
How am I supposed to face
the neighbor from now?!
I don't really get what you mean,
but we can clear up any prejudice by going
about the city together in a healthy fashion.
I don't want to be seen
together with you three!
Besides, I'm meeting someone today,
so I don't have time to humor you guys.
Wait... really?
Them's the breaks, then.
I guess we'll just cook and clean
the house together while you're gone.
Wait, did I just hear a word
that sounds close to "choke" there?
Choke?
What do you take our cooking for?
The ultimate poison.
Now that's funny...
Hang on, I gotta take this.
Hello?
All right, I'll be in your care today.
Sorry for taking your time.
Huh? Bring Hitamuki as well?
No... sure, she's available,
but if Hitamuki comes with me,
my house will become a living hell...
Ah, I understand.
I'll take her with me. See you there.
I'm meeting a scholar guard who's been
helping me since I was a kid today.
I decided to ask him for his wisdom,
hoping to gain some insight
into how the monsters behave,
and why they target women,
especially Hitamuki, so relentlessly.
I've been wondering about that too.
So that's why you need me!
I'll go with you!
Yeah.
So I'm sorry, guys, but could you three just go home for toda—
All right! I'll make you the ultimate cooking
that you'll never forget with my girlpower!
I'll use my girlpower to send you straight
to heaven with my superior cooking as well!
Third time's the charm...
I shall awaken the girlpower
buried deep within me!
I'm going straight to my grave
with their girlpower!
I don't want to go home now...
Come on, don't be scared.
What do you take our cooking for?
A crime that cannot be judged by law.
You're making me cry.
We didn't come here unprepared, after all.
Hitamuki has taught us how to cook
for hours yesterday!
We've learned a surefire way
for a perfect cooking...
Or rather, a trick for an absolute
100% chance of perfect cooking!
A trick?
That's...
To be faithful with the recipe!
You just realised that?!
Okay, okay.
If you insist so much,
then I'll believe in you guys.
Now, Hitamuki.
We'll go together once I finish preparing.
Okay!
Wait...
It'll be bad if you're wearing
that around the city.
You should change into your casual outfit...
PLUMP
Casual...
Oh, never mind what I said.
We're off, then.
Off we go!
Take care!
Immoral Guild!
RIDDLE-
RIDDLE-SOLVING
RIDDLE-SOLVING LITTLE
Kik-kun, we're about to meet a guard now, right?
Yeah, but he's also the owner of this antiquarian bookshop.
FOUNTAIN OF KNOWLEDGE
Rather, because of his age,
he's more focused on this shop these days.
Stop treating me like an old man
right after you come here.
I simply got bored
of researching the monsters.
It's been a while, Kikuru.
You're already looking different
after only a while.
I've had my fair share of experiences...
I can't believe you took
advantage of her baby face...
...to dress her in a sailor uniform
and take her around in broad daylight.
You're already behaving different
after only a while.
It's a negative opinion now?!
You've got the wrong idea
about her uniform!
Even this is a hundred times
better than her usual outfit!
So you're Hitamuki?
You really are a cute girl.
That's not true!
If Kikuru didn't tell me about you,
I thought you'd still be in primary
or middle school...
Forgive my manners,
you really are a pretty lady.
That criterion is more disrespectful
than anything else.
Oh, I haven't introduced myself, have I?
My name is Iz Mean Mill.
Despite how I look,
I'm actually around forty.
Papa, Uncle, Master.
Feel free to call me whatever you like.
If you're giving her three choices,
you should prepare the right answer too...
Sorry, Mister Iz, but can we just go—
Kikuru.
Can we just go straight to the point?
Why are you making it look like
I'm impeding our progress?
So you wanted me to examine every inch
of her body very carefully, correct?
Careful with your expression.
Nevertheless, what you
and Enome-sama have told me so far...
...speaks volumes about her nature.
To put it short,
Hitamuki-sama is connected to the world.
Um, could you not put it that short yourself?
Don't skip the main point when
you put in unnecessary preliminaries.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I have a bad habit of thinking inside
and speaking it out loud.
But...
For me to go out of my way
to speak of known information...
It's too much work.
Stop joking with me!
I'm connected to the world?
So I can still talk to people from
the another world without a phone?
Mede-chan...
I'm now speaking to you through the air!
Wow!
See? You gotta explain it properly,
or this innocent girl will hold on
to a faint dream forever.
And explain it properly I shall.
Mana's not part of your
expertise after all, Kikuru.
And you, who have never shown
any interest in your surroundings,
are now acting to get to know someone.
You've grown in a delightful way
that I can't imagine since we met.
Why are you dragging the chit-chat?
This is good.
Yeah.
It's plain good.
I guess we can make decent stuff
when we follow the recipe.
I mean, it's a recipe.
But I think we've made too much...
Should we call Noma here?
Sure, it's tasty,
but we still don't need
high level of skills for this.
Hey... if we make something
exactly based on a recipe,
doesn't it mean that the author
of this cooking will be the recipe's owner?
Wait, you're overthinking things!
This stew is without a doubt handmade by us!
That's in the case of amateurs.
Aren't we ready to move
to the next stage now?
Hang on...
I thought we had it already,
but I'm not sure anymore...
What's the definition of
handmade cooking, anyway?
I-Isn't that a cooking made by hand?
We just followed the recipe blindly,
no improvising, and what three of us made
was fully backward compatible with Hitamuki's.
This cooking...
...doesn't have our own unique "colours".
All right! I will upgrade this
mediocre cooking with my own hands!
I've got the hang of this
after all we've been through now!
I'll show you my great adaptability!
Now that's my comrades!
I can see his surprised face
when he gets back now!
Do you guys know how mana depleted
by skills and stuff is recovered?
I don't know!
By absorbing the seithr
in the air into the body, right?
I know that much.
Correct.
SEITHR
MANA
Humans absorb seithr and convert it to mana.
All things, not just people,
possess mana to a greater or lesser extent.
There are creatures that feed on such mana.
Do you know what they are?
I-I don't know!
The monsters?
Correct. They really suck
at converting the seithr to mana.
Even though they desire mana the most,
but this is just an irony.
So that's why they take mana directly
from other creatures?
I'll get us back a chapter.
Each person has their own recovery speed.
If there's someone who takes a day to do that,
there'll be someone who does in just half a day.
Do you know the cause for this?
I-I don't know...
Our skins are always touching seithr.
The absorption rate is very slow.
Different people have different affinities with seithr.
It may be referred to collectively as mana,
but its nature and purity vary enormously.
Now, onto the case of Hitamuki-sama...
You don't change your expression at all, do you?
I-I'm listening to you seriously!
No, that's not what I mean...
Could you move out of the way?
-------------------------------------
『 SCHOLAR ARTE 』 BREATHING FORM
Actually, I've been casting a skill to her that continues to sap her mana.
I-I didn't realize this!
A normal person would've tripped
without knowing why.
They'd also breathe heavily.
That was dangerous!
People's seithr absorption rate
doesn't even come close to 1%.
But she's in a different dimension.
Her rate is 100%.
The mana you've lost...
...is instantly recovered
by the seithr around you.
I know that it's a rare occurrence!
Even I'm too afraid to put it that way.
You are subverting human history.
The reason you can recover instantly...
is that your mana and the seithr
around have the same nature.
Do you know?
When the seithr becomes mana,
SEITHR
MANA
a small number of mixtures and characteristics peculiar to the substance are produced.
But you don't possess that.
BURU PREFECTURE PRODUCT
A5 GRADE
Your mana fully preserves the purity of seithr.
And when it's inexhaustible,
it's nothing short of
the finest food for the monsters.
The finest food?
Have you ever thought that you're
more sensitive than most people?
That's because the seithr
in the air and your mana...
are constantly drawn to each other
to connect because of their affinity.
Furthermore, because of the match
between the seithr and your nature,
you are nebulous to what
extent your body is your own.
For instance, are there times when you
can't predict the distance and trip yourself?
All the time!
THUNK!
So...
All that has a meaning, huh...
She's an honest and polite lady, isn't she?
I don't sense intelligence from her,
but I do sense decency.
Right.
She's a good, caring person.
But you know, fish will not live in water that is too clean.
For a cynical person like me,
her innocence is a little dazzling.
That pureness of hers reeks of lies.
Not having lies reeks of lies.
But the moon will reflect
in water that is too clean.
Oh, you're covering for her?
Not really...
Don't be so mad.
My impression toward her
is not disgust, but awe.
Hey, Iz-san.
I know why the monsters are infatuated
at Hitamuki's mana now.
But other than that, there's a clear difference
in the way they treat men and women.
Do you know anything?
The good and bad side of mana
and the reason why...
they prefer younger girls
are two different things.
But there's no point for you
in knowing that.
I don't see the current situation
as a problem too.
You can think of it as a profitable situation
if they don't eat the girls alive right away.
You know, but you're not telling me?
I know a lot of things
that I'm not telling you.
An adult's job is to tell the answer,
and not tell the answer.
Stop treating me like a child.
Kik-kun.
You took your time to find out
about me on your day off.
How should I make up for this?
Don't say that my finding out
about you is a waste of time.
I did this because I wanted to know.
You guys also acted for me today as well, no?
I'm grateful.
Kik-kun...
Even though I've been pickpocketed, trespassed,
and disturbed from a good night's sleep.
But I'm still grateful.
Are you not angry?!
Now, let's go back fast
and make fun of their cooking.
Kik-kun! You can't say something so mean!
No... Don't look..., Senpai...
It's not the stew...
...I know... at all...
When I get home,
the girls in my class...
will be naked in a failed stew,
trying to stage the cooking of a stew...
No way I'm having such a petulant youth.
Kikuru-kun, everyone, have a safe day.
Take care!
Off you go!
Kikuru!
Help me, Master!
Don't look at me, Senpai!
Uh... Master!
Kik-kun...
Is this really the youth I want?
Thank you for watching!
Till we meet again someday!
Ijippari ni kakuzatou wo tokashitara
If you stubbornly dissolve the sugar cubes
Sunao no mahou
Magic of honesty
Doji ni wa chotto oome no shinamon
Clumsy and a little too much cinnamon
Yarisugite daddadubada
Too much daddadubada
Mata mebunryou no kimagure to yasashisa de
In addition, with the whims and gentleness of mebenryo
Himitsu no reshipi wo mou kakimidasanaide
Don't disturb the secret recipe anymore
Oh don’t call my name
Oh don't call my name
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Amai dake janai
Not just sweet
Mune no oku no tokimeki iroiro
Heart-pounding feelings deep in my chest Various things
Watashi dake no baransu wo
I have my own balance
Wakatte hoshikute
I want you to understand
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Karai dake ja iya
I don't like it
Mune no oku no tokimeki wa
just because it's spicy
Mochiron desho namida to koi no mariaaju...
Of course, if it's tears, it's a marriage of love
...Yappari wakaranaide!
…I don't know!