Here it comes.
I'd assumed it was waiting
in the distance for an opportunity...
But then there's a black sorceress
with nasty firepower on one side...
...and a wounded hunter who
has suffered a fatal blow on another.
If we were to fan out,
of course it'd go for me.
Though, I've arranged so that Tokishikko
won't have to encounter any other monsters.
Either way, I've successfully
made contact with the enemy.
Now...
...is just the question of whether I can
shake it off until I reach the shelter.
With a hole on my stomach...
Odoroki mo hentetsu mo nai
Even easy daily missions,
Iijii deirii misshon datte
That don’t involve surprises and unexpected,
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Urutora shiikuretto ruuto ga
If there was Some ultra secret route,
Sonzai shiteru to shitara kimi wa ittai
I wonder how you would break out
Dou susumu no?
through it?
Hitamuki ni hitasura ni
Even if, completely surrendering to it,
Tada ikkyo ichidou ii koto shitatte
I stubbornly did good deeds with every step,
Tanabota ni yokoku nashiteki
Unexpected luck is an unforeseen thing.
Furachi moodo ni enkaunto shitatte
Even if we was encounter in rough mode,
Shuuten wa dochira mo kitto onaji
The end point for both of us is definitely the same.
Yume no naka ja kasanari aeru futari
We were able to sneak into each other’s dreams,
Kyuuten Chokkou Konya
so we suddenly became honest.
Futoku na doa no kagi wo akete!
So open the door of immorality tonight!
Aa hotobashiru kodou ga
Ah, your gaze, dancing with a frantic heartbeat,
Samayou shisen kogashite haimawaru
Slides over my body and burns me.
Sono te de furete mukidashi no subete wo
Touch with your hand everything, which is bare in me.
Ima sugu
Pierce me
hone made
right now
tsuranuite
to the bones.
Coming up!
Mezameru sono mae ni
Before we wake up…
Before we wake up...
THE
THE PERFECT
THE PERFECT COMBUSTION
The hardest things to deal with when fighting
against a repel spider are its venom and threads.
It must be due to the lack of information,
not in terms of competencies
such as muscle strength or sensing,
but in terms of not knowing
the full extent of its capabilities.
Normal repel spiders are monsters
around 30 cm long that hunt small monsters,
and are half-useful insects.
Many guards have never
thought of fighting them.
Hence, all the missing information
has to be found out by trial and error.
But in this guy's case,
one error...
...would likely mean no more trials.
I hope there's no more
new information on that thing...
I'll die if I take another hit!
It didn't only react
to direct attacks to its body,
but also to indirect hostility
from the flames surrounding itself.
They seemed like flawless
abilities at first glance,
but I've deduced that these two
have something in common.
Line of sight.
Both of them must require proper line of sight.
In fact, I'm running
with the aim of luring it to a trap,
but it's not reacting.
At times,
I've also let out my murderous intent,
but it's showing no attempts to evade.
Maybe I can land a hit without looking...
But I can't get a lock on the thing,
and my power's entirely lacking.
Above all, it would be a disaster if,
as a result of provoking it badly,
it's alerted and try to run away.
The first attack
on the thing must be crippling.
I don't think it's an important
thing to mention, but...
I think I have a knack for parkour...
When I come back here,
close your eyes and prepare
to cast an advanced spell.
I'll install some talismans around you,
so don't worry.
You don't have to worry
about being attacked inside these.
Hey, what if I have to use the toilet?
Just do it over there.
Come back soon, okay?
Your bladder really picks up the moment
you know that you can't use the toilet...
Not to mention I have a rather
suggestive name too...
It won't be funny if I wet myself here.
I hope he comes back soon.
Here they are!
Master, just wrap it up quickly!
I'm losing blood and becoming dazed...
I wonder if my act of being pushed into
a corner has developed a sense of truth.
Now... for the final stage...
just one more blow...
If I can parry one more blow...
We can't have it in our sights.
The key to evasion...
...is the shadow!
30 minutes ago
A backdraft?
To put it very simply, it's an explosive phenomenon
that occurs at the scene of a fire.
Burning meat and house...
what is my magic for actually, I wonder?
It's your fault for the former.
This in itself is not a decisive factor.
However...
A gap has arisen where
it can't deal with our hostility!
I've sealed his overwhelming movement now!
Now! Do it!
I'll defeat you and rush to the toilet!
Ignica!
Wha—
Unforgivable!
You too?!
It's finally over...
Master...
Tokishikko...
You okay?
I am...
Other than my clothes...
How do I go home now?
I'll lend you my coat.
Sorry, but could you call for help
while you're wearing it...
T-Tokishikko?!
I ran out of energy and mana,
my legs gave in...
I'm at my limit...
Even so, you shouldn't be collapsing on me!
I guess we're not moving
until I can walk, huh?
Aren't you embarrassed?
Well, you can call it a free service...
You've done your best today, after all.
You were so cool.
My dear Master.
Oh, no... what do I do?!
Huh? Hey, what's wrong?
I forgot that I'd been holding it...
Hold up.
Master...
It's like... water under the bridge, okay?
More like over the bridge!
Immoral Guild...
THANKS
I'm still tired...
The wound I got from that spider...
Even though it'd been detoxified,
the wound still remained.
And I moved around like
a park our master yesterday too.
G-Good afternoon!
Hitamuki? What's up?
Uh... I heard you pushed yourself yesterday,
and are still sick today...
So I came here to look after you!
Tasty as always, huh?
Sorry for troubling you.
I just got up, so I haven't eaten yet. Thanks.
Oh, you don't have to.
This is all I can do to help now.
It's amazing that you can cook...
If it were those three instead,
I'd have fallen into yet another deep sleep.
Um... is your wound okay now?
Yeah. I had Maidena patch me up yesterday.
I'm still tired from moving around like crazy,
but the wound is no longer there.
I heard you were fatally injured,
so that's a relief.
By the way, Toki-chan's been concerned
about who should take the credit.
She's wondering if it's really okay
that she's the one who defeated the repel spider.
I don't mind.
In the end, she was the one
delivering the final blow.
Also, I'm about to retire as well.
If I get popular now, I won't be able to do that.
Achievements are just another burden.
Achievements are a burden...
Kik-kun!
W...Want to go shopping with me now?!
SUKUSUKU SHOPPING
DISTRICT
Do you have something you want to buy?
Err...
Shopping for dinner!
Let me cook for you tonight as well!
Well, I appreciate it...
Oh, really?
Hitamuki, welcome!
Hello, Mister!
Hitamuki! Shopping for dinner?
Be sure to drop by our meat store too later!
Sure!
Hitamuki-san, thank you
for the stew the other day.
Oh, it's nothing!
This familiarity...
You haven't moved to Mebuki for long, right?
That's right! It'll soon be a month
since I started living here!
We have fresh bitter gourds coming.
I'll put some in free of charge.
Thank you!
She even gets bonuses?
I've lived here for ten years, but I've never
had pleasant chats with the citizens even once.
What do you think, Hitamuki?
It's still not the season yet,
but it's got quite the bump, right?
You're right!
You can use it for cooking,
any other business...
I'm sure it'll come in handy...
The mister's ----------...
So big... ----------...
This is so good!
Any other business?
You can return this if you use it for that.
And she's getting sexually harassed, too!
Hey, Hitamuki.
Those guys aren't doing
anything strange to you, right?
Strange?
They speak things I can't
understand sometimes,
but they're so kind to me!
Hitamuki, you should polish that meat on your chest
under those one-size-fits-all gym shorts...
Aren't they maturing even more now?
I want to cultivate her meat with mine!
Want to taste my ultimate rod?!
I can sense their perversion at first glance!
Maybe you should, uh...
Try getting to know them better too?
Huh? You're surprisingly pushy today, I see?
But, yeah...
I should probably greet them
as a good manner...
Hello there...
Mister.
You seem close to Hitamuki, eh?
Huh?
Hey, there...
Who are you...
To Hitamuki?
Never mind getting to know them,
they're getting eager to strike...
Wait!
He's the ace of this city,
and has been helping me all the time too!
Oh... I thought you were some bastard
looking at her with perverted eyes.
Hey.
My bad.
We don't see the city's ace on paper or TV.
Sorry for not recognising you.
It's okay...
Here you go, Hitamuki!
Thank you!
You take some too, Mister!
Huh?
Thank you for protecting our city!
Thanks!
Merci!
Why, thank you, Hitamuki.
Here.
Oh, you don't have to.
You want some too, Mister?
He's the one, right?
The one you're always talking about.
In the end, we keep getting
freebies with you around.
People also thanked me
for the extermination of monsters.
Yes! I can't wait to think
about what I should cook for them!
So you're not only getting freebies,
but also giving them...
No wonder you're so popular.
I could make lots of offerings!
Offerings?
I always visit the fox idols
in the neighbourhood every day!
Oh, Onee-chan!
Hitamuki-oneechan!
The twin siblings!
Let's play together, Onee-chan!
B-But...
I don't mind it. I'll go take a rest.
I'm sorry.
They're my neighbour's sons,
and we sometimes play hero!
Play hero?
Yes! I always act as the evil woman general!
I can't imagine you doing evil things...
Prepare yourself, evil woman general!
Are you okay?!
It's just pain, don't worry.
It doesn't hurt.
It doesn't hurt, okay?
That kid... don't tell me...
Um...
You can't touch those lewd... things!
What's "lewd"?
Huh?
I'm innocent, so I don't know.
You wouldn't hear that
from someone actually innocent!
A-Anyway, please get off my boob—
Wait, huh?!
Skipping rope?!
We got the evil woman general!
No way!
Justice will prevail!
What an evil method of justice!
I hate to admit it, but I lost, so...
Why...?
I said... I give up...
Our country will not take kindly to traitors.
We have the authority to decide
whether you live or die.
Huh?!
You...
...normally wouldn't do something like this...
What do you mean "something like this"?
PUZZLED
Acting all innocent when you have to, huh?!
What are you...
Stop... it's cold!
I... can't...
No...
Not there...
Pwease sphare mhee...
(Please spare me...)
TWITCH TWITCH
SPLASH
Well, what can I say...
This is really a monstrous sight!
They are worse than monsters
because I can't touch them!
I have a lot to say to those kids,
but you shouldn't lose yourself, Hitamuki.
When I first met them...
...they weren't like this at all...
What has made them change...?
Maybe it's you.
They were normal kids
before meeting you, right?
Then it's you.
You're still bad for cultivation
of aesthetic sensibility...
Ah, no...
So, I've been wanting to ask this,
but why did you take me around the city?
You're acting a bit strange today.
I want you to be aware
of the things you've saved.
The things I've saved?
Kik-kun, you want to retire
from being a guard, right?
I don't think I will, and can,
stop you from doing that.
But I want you to
at least retire with a smile!
The lives of the people...
And their smiles...
You've protected them all,
so I want you to be proud
of your excellent achievement.
If you finish doing the job
that almost cost your life...
...with a sour face and troublesome memories,
won't it be sad?
Today was the first time people
from the city ever thanked me.
It's not like they're neglecting the guards.
I just never bothered talking to them.
I never intended to approach them,
and grumbled and complained
about being alone...
I was under the illusion that
a change of location will yield me something...
But ultimately, Hitamuki got concerned of me...
Kik-kun?
Looking back, I never said anything
about this job being worthwhile.
Sorry for making you worry.
Also...
Thank you...
Sure!
Besides, I can't just quit even if I want to
until you guys are properly trained.
Until then, I'll just have to work hard
for the people's smiles and whatnot.
For the people's smiles...
For the...
Huh? Wait, what is this?
They don't inspire me to protect them...
COMBUSTIBLE TRASH
------------------------------
INCOMBUSTIBLE TRASH
I mean, they still can live strong enough without me...
Kik-kun?!
By the way, what do you
want to eat as a side dish?
Ham...
You really love ham, I see!
To be continued.
TO BE CONTINUE
Ijippari ni kakuzatou wo tokashitara
If you stubbornly dissolve the sugar cubes
Sunao no mahou
Magic of honesty
Doji ni wa chotto oome no shinamon
Clumsy and a little too much cinnamon
Yarisugite daddadubada
Too much daddadubada
Mata mebunryou no kimagure to yasashisa de
In addition, with the whims and gentleness of mebenryo
Himitsu no reshipi wo mou kakimidasanaide
Don't disturb the secret recipe anymore
Oh don’t call my name
Oh don't call my name
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Amai dake janai
Not just sweet
Mune no oku no tokimeki iroiro
Heart-pounding feelings deep in my chest Various things
Watashi dake no baransu wo
I have my own balance
Wakatte hoshikute
I want you to understand
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Karai dake ja iya
I don't like it
Mune no oku no tokimeki wa
just because it's spicy
Mochiron desho namida to koi no mariaaju...
Of course, if it's tears, it's a marriage of love
...Yappari wakaranaide!
…I don't know!
Yesterday, I went for a walk with Kik-kun
around the shopping district,
and the people there were so kind!
This city's full of nice people!
I'm so glad I moved here!
NEXT
NEXT EPISODE
GOLDEN
GOLDEN EGG
SOMETHING
SOMETHING SOFT