Odoroki mo hentetsu mo nai
Even easy daily missions,
Iijii deirii misshon datte
That don’t involve surprises and unexpected,
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Urutora shiikuretto ruuto ga
If there was Some ultra secret route,
Sonzai shiteru to shitara kimi wa ittai
I wonder how you would break out
Dou susumu no?
through it?
Hitamuki ni hitasura ni
Even if, completely surrendering to it,
Tada ikkyo ichidou ii koto shitatte
I stubbornly did good deeds with every step,
Tanabota ni yokoku nashiteki
Unexpected luck is an unforeseen thing.
Furachi moodo ni enkaunto shitatte
Even if we was encounter in rough mode,
Shuuten wa dochira mo kitto onaji
The end point for both of us is definitely the same.
Yume no naka ja kasanari aeru futari
We were able to sneak into each other’s dreams,
Kyuuten Chokkou Konya
so we suddenly became honest.
Futoku na doa no kagi wo akete!
So open the door of immorality tonight!
Aa hotobashiru kodou ga
Ah, your gaze, dancing with a frantic heartbeat,
Samayou shisen kogashite haimawaru
Slides over my body and burns me.
Sono te de furete mukidashi no subete wo
Touch with your hand everything, which is bare in me.
Ima sugu
Pierce me
hone made
right now
tsuranuite
to the bones.
Coming up!
Mezameru sono mae ni
Before we wake up…
Before we wake up...
THE
THE SECRET
THE SECRET BEHIND
THE SECRET BEHIND FRENZY
We've sparred longer than I thought.
This made for good exercise for me too.
After all, compared to the magic group yesterday,
the physical team followed suit
without complaining.
The training went on smoothly, to my surprise.
Still, I'm really no match against you.
In the end, I couldn't land
a single blow on you.
Yeah...
One strike from you would be fatal to me...
So I was desperate too.
In terms of pure strength,
you've already surpassed the average knight.
But...
I can't land a blow...
I'll use Frenzy, then!
Wait, no, don't!
You have a tendency to rely on your Frenzy
when you're outnumbered or emotional.
Party members getting out of control
lead to a breakdown in formation.
Refrain from activating it
when you have your comrades around.
N-Now that you mentioned it...
Sorry...
This is fine.
If I can't tell the details
about Frenzy to her,
I can point out her flaw
and get her to take care of herself.
My safety will be assured this way.
It's no exaggeration that today's training
was meant for me to tell her this!
Hana-chan!
If you want some more water,
you can have my tea if you like.
But then you'll get less to drink...
You're out of water?
Just take mine, then.
Hitamuki, you make sure
to stay hydrated yourself.
O-Okay!
I only have a mana bottle...
Mana bottle?
I trained the complaining team—I mean...
The magical team yesterday, after all.
If we had time, I'd let her replenish her mana,
and do some target shooting...
MISSION
IMPOSSIBLE
But in the end, I ended up not using it.
Well, this will still quench
your thirst, no problem.
Thank you, Senpai.
This is my first time drinking it...
So sweet... tasty...
Next are some general remarks
about you, Hitamuki.
You move around too much,
you're wasting your energy.
Waste?!
Even though you have more stamina than me,
that's the reason you get tired now.
Don't go for the win immediately,
but instead try to learn...
...how to make your opponents
move and tire themselves out.
Okay! I'll do my best with dedication!
I'm recommending a tactic
you'd consider rather dirty, though,
but do you really get it?
Whew...
Comin' at ya with full power!
Why? How?!
That state...
Frenzy?!
Where's Senpai?
Hitamuki, where's Senpai?
Uhh... He went to pick flowers...
I mean, he went to buy drinks!
No, wait! He went on patrol!
She's a lousy liar!
But what's the meaning of this?
The moment she drank that,
she started acting weird...
Please ask about Hanabata-sama
from her friend, Tokishikko-sama.
Hello, Master?
Yeah.
Yeah...
She's activated Frenzy
after drinking a mana bottle?
Oh, she's just drunk from mana.
Drunk?
In short, she got intoxicated
by an overdose of magic.
But that would mean her usual Frenzy
would be that she's drunk from mana too...
Right...
You see, Frenzy is...
...normally a process of sending mana
from the body to the brain,
then removes one's autosuggestion and limiters.
That's what it's supposed to be, but...
In her case, the stage of collecting mana
in the brain causes overcapacity...
Comin' at ya with full power!
...and she gets drunk before
the skill's even activated.
So she couldn't remove her autosuggestion?
------------------
FRENZY
X
INTOXICATION
O
Her power and toughness are first-class,
--------------
STAMINA
MAGIC ATTACK
-----------
ATTACK
MAGIC DEFENSE
------------------
DEFENSE
but her magic resistance is so low
that she can't even withstand her own mana.
What an unbalanced status...
So the thing she'd been using
wasn't Frenzy all along?
Nope. As for her servants...
FRENZY
They'd call it Flower Frenzy from the off-season flowering.
FLOWER FRENZY
That name fits her perfectly.
The mana that's lost control circulates fast
and reinforces the whole body,
so it's less taxing than
the reckless Frenzy with the limiter off.
She's using mana rapidly,
so the duration should be short.
The beautiful flower has a short life, huh...
Hitamuki, you're so soft!
You can't do that, Hana-chan!
I'm drenched in sweat...
You smell nice...
No...
An overdose of mana, huh...
The effect's longer than usual.
Hitamuki, you're so kind and warm...
I love you~
I'm... so happy...
But this is too embarrassing!
Two big assets colliding
with each other... Wowzer...
Hey, I can hear Hitamuki screaming there.
What are you doing?
You're so tasty, just like that juice.
That juice...?
I want more!
Nothing will come out of these!
I can't produce milk yet!
Kik-kun's here too! Please stop!
Wait, is Senpai here?!
Kik-kun...
He's not here!
A paragon of someone
who won't sell out her friend!
You're a liar!
Hana-chan...
I'm not your mama...
Hey, Tokishikko.
Hm?
Can I hang up now?
I'll bet you want to record some
boob videos after this, right?
No way.
I'd love to help Hitamuki, who has defended me
and is getting attacked by Hanabata now,
but unfortunately, I still want to live.
I love you!
For some reason,
it's only me that she'd give a bear hug to.
Maybe because you're special,
and she has an uncontrollable feeling within...
Could it be not "like" but "love"?
I don't recall her showing
that kind of emotion to me.
Besides, she's been like that
since we first met.
I don't know...
Despite being rotten,
you're still Mebuki's ace,
so there's also the pattern
that she's already found out about you first.
How am I rotten? I'm working myself to the bone, you know?
How about trying to face her
with full wounds for now?
Huh? Why?
The fact that she likes you
still doesn't change at least.
If she sees you hurt,
she won't be able to do anything reckless.
Okay, thanks.
I guess I should try it out
for future reference.
Senpai!
Senpai, what happened?!
I went to buy drinks...
when I was attacked by another hunter!
What do we do?!
Wait, you shouldn't be fooled, Hitamuki.
That's why... I'll be dead if I get hit by you...
That looks painful...
GRAB
U-Uhh...
Sh-She's licking my... thumb...
Her warm, soft tongue crawls
around my thumb stickily...
Wait!
No, I can't! I'm afraid of what comes next!
Have you healed?
I think I'm still hurt... over here!
Senpai...
Wait, wait, wait.
I didn't have any other choice.
If I'm fit and healthy,
I could be squeezed again with tremendous force.
Don't get the wrong idea.
This is the best method
to manage this situation.
Y-Yes! You're right!
I'm glad it's Hitamuki who's with me now.
If I could find a way to resolve this,
Frenzy is actually not a bad technique.
As long as she doesn't
do damage to friendlies,
we can get rid of the only demerit
from this technique.
Besides, the sober Hanabata would never allow
herself to have this much physical contact.
In the meantime, I'll break away
when the time is right, before she sobers up.
I'll just go with the flow until then...
Err...
What was it, again?
Frenzy?
I...
I hate this technique.
THE
BEST
METHOD
Immoral Guild!
MEAT
MEAT FEAST
The elimination of monsters by only
those four novices, without my assistance,
ends with twists and turns.
In retrospect, they didn't take
advantage of each other's strengths,
and dragged each other down
with our weaknesses.
Voltage!
Ah...
First, due to Tokishikko's friendly fire,
the only proper DPS we had,
Hanabata, was downed.
The plan fell apart right from the get-go.
Hana-chan!
Are you okay?!
Let go, please!
Hitamuki, who tried evacuating Hanabata,
didn't pay attention and was grabbed by the enemy.
This is bad... I'll be hitting Hitamuki too.
Kikuru! I can't take it anymore!
Maidena's demoralised cries
echoed through the forest,
resulting in enemy reinforcements incoming.
MEGASLIMES HAVE APPEARED!
ROOTCATS HAVE APPEARED!
And the meat feast began.
No... you can't...
Why is everyone...
No!
It's in my mouth...
Why, you...!
Ultimately, the great firepower coming from
a snapped Tokishikko closed the curtains...
But I don't know if I could call this a victory...
PUSH FORWARD
RETURN TO CITY
~ MEBUKI CITY ~
~ KIKURU'S HOUSE ~
Uh, okay, then...
To celebrate our first victory as novice guards...
Cheers!
She called it a victory...
What did you say about the MVP
who defeated three monsters at once?
I know that you are the root of all evil!
But thanks to Toki-san, we could survive the day!
There, there.
I haven't been able to defeat any monsters,
and even today I wasn't much of a help.
That's not true!
You tried to save me, right?
That's right!
We even have a healer who,
after crying and calling...
...a lot of enemies toward us,
decided to keep quiet!
Shut up!
You took down Hanabata in the first place,
so the whole thing happened, right!
Come on, don't bite each other,
bite your own food when eating dinner.
I guess they still need me to lead them
for the time being, after all.
Looks like it'll still be a long way
before my retirement.
Who made this?
I did. D-Did it taste okay?
It's so tasty...
It's the bearlion we hunted today
for the quest, right?
I never thought peculiar
game meat would taste this good...
Yeah, it's delicious! You can't feel
the hardness or the smell from this!
I'm glad you liked it!
The only thing I could call my special skills
were housework, after all.
Hitamuki, your housewife skills are too OP!
Hey, if you're dating someone,
do you prefer she can cook?
Huh?!
Well... There's nothing better
than being able to do everything.
Then, shall we try cooking for you now?
Huh?!
Let's see who scores first!
Why?!
Really, why?
First of all, you don't give out the impression
that you can cook with that laziness!
Correct.
You two have people around you cooking for you,
and you're far from cooking for yourselves,
so you can't.
Don't make light of me, Kikuru.
Please don't underestimate me, Senpai!
Just because I'm a beginner
doesn't mean my cooking's not good!
Then I'll make light of you
and underestimate you!
We still have some meat, right?
No looking up the recipe
on the Internet, okay?
Fine by me!
My casual remark seemed
to provoke the maidens' pride...
And suddenly, the cooking
competition between those three began.
Which should I pick?
I've never used a knife before,
I guess I'd choose the parts that are as tender
and easy to cut as possible...
This one looks like it's got a bone in it,
so I can just use it as it is.
As for the seasoning...
Nothing but ham...
We can't look it up on the Internet...
So...
As for how much soy sauce
and sugar I should put in here...
I see...
Are they making proper food there?
I'll go check them out.
S-Sure.
M-Maidena?!
Is that amount okay?!
It is, though?
The pot is so big, so it must have been
designed to hold this amount of sauce.
BOUNCE
Soy sauce isn't meant to be used solo!
Right... Cooking is about...
...reasoning!
Apologize to all the cooks
and detectives in the world.
SCHOOL UNIFORM - 1
APRON --------------- 1
BLACK TIGHTS ------ 1
PONYTAIL ----------- 1
NAPE ----------------- 1
Maidena's dressed in a uniform and apron,
an outfit that tickles men's interests.
Her own cooking methods are faultless,
yet the essential ingredients
are riddled with mistakes.
This is the first time I've ever had
the feeling that the pot is hurting.
Tokishikko and Hanabata went outside...
...but I wish they'd fare better than Maidena.
Huh? In the garden? What is she...
Wait, wait, wait!
Oh, Master.
I've never seen anyone cook with a welding mask on!
Are you building something?!
I am cooking.
Now, now, cool your jets.
I'm only reducing the cooking time
by grilling over an open fire.
Right... Cooking is about...
...efficiency!
All the newbies keep teaching me how to cook...
That...
...won't do...
Tokishikko!
Cooking...
...is not about maths or efficiency!
The first thing you need in cooking is...
...sincerity!
Uwooogh!!
What you're saying is so girly, but the insanity
shown is on par with the other two!
Rather than using a knife I'm not used to,
I thought this'd suit me better...
Yeah... if we perceive this
as the meat dough for Salisbury steak...
I'll put red bean paste in this
to create a yeast bun!
What are you planning to feed me?
Inviting four girls to your house
and having all of them cook for you...
How normie can you be, Master?
If what comes out... is food, then...
REQUIEM
SHOOM
'S REQUIEM OF
MAIDENA'S REQUIEM OF BEAR
SCORCHED STYLE
BURNT
HAND, SCORCHED STYLE ~PRAISE
BEAR HAND, SCORCHED STYLE ~PRAISE BLACK
TOKISHIKKO'S BEAR HAND, SCORCHED STYLE ~PRAISE BLACK MAGIC~
BLOB
HANABATA'S BEARBUN
I thank you for making these for me,
but I have one condition
before eating each of these.
Th-The smell...
You should take responsibility
and taste your own cooking yourself.
What do you mean taste?
That's rude, Master.
Agreed.
I'd love for you to thank me
for not putting it as poison testing,
and also, you'd normally
sample your own food...
What's the logic behind this?!
Your clothes are blown away, what are these?!
Are they offensive items?!
We should find some clothes for them!
It was so awful...
my mana just spurted out of my whole body!
Is this what our bodies do,
depending on what we taste?!
They no longer have the look
of someone who's had a meal!
It's the moment when
the deleterious drug was born!
So... Senpai... Who won...?
It's hard to say which is which!
There's no first and second ranks, after all!
Thanks...
All of you just wasted precious food...
Tokishikko used a bear's hand,
but Maidena used the precious part...
Hey, Hitamuki. Is that the precious part?
Which part?
Uh... Err... Ah...
I don't know... either!
You're obviously lying.
What? You could just tell me if you know.
Wh-What you cooked was...
Was...
The bear's...
The bear's?
D...
D...?
...k.
Huh?!
So what I ate just now was...
Dick! Dick! Dick!
Senpai! Maidena is...!
Are you okay?! Mede-chan!
A bear's asset has a horn, huh?
The culinary showdown closed with Hitamuki
snatching the win in every category.
TO BE CONTINUE
To be continued.
Ijippari ni kakuzatou wo tokashitara
If you stubbornly dissolve the sugar cubes
Sunao no mahou
Magic of honesty
Doji ni wa chotto oome no shinamon
Clumsy and a little too much cinnamon
Yarisugite daddadubada
Too much daddadubada
Mata mebunryou no kimagure to yasashisa de
In addition, with the whims and gentleness of mebenryo
Himitsu no reshipi wo mou kakimidasanaide
Don't disturb the secret recipe anymore
Oh don’t call my name
Oh don't call my name
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Amai dake janai
Not just sweet
Mune no oku no tokimeki iroiro
Heart-pounding feelings deep in my chest Various things
Watashi dake no baransu wo
I have my own balance
Wakatte hoshikute
I want you to understand
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Karai dake ja iya
I don't like it
Mune no oku no tokimeki wa
just because it's spicy
Mochiron desho namida to koi no mariaaju...
Of course, if it's tears, it's a marriage of love
...Yappari wakaranaide!
…I don't know!
NEXT
NEXT EPISODE
MAIDE
A NEW
A NEW FAMILY
A NEW FAMILY MEMBER