The church that worships the Holy Bird Phoenizask, who regulates "restoring",
THE PHOENIZASKAN CHURCH THAT
WORSHIPS THE HOLY BIRD PHOENIZASK
the Phoenizaskan Church.
And the temple that worships the God
of Thunder Zenith, who regulates "knowledge",
----------------------------------
THE ZENITH TEMPLE
THAT WORSHIPS
THE GOD OF THUNDER ZENITH
the Zenith Temple.
They both are organisations run
by white and black sorcerers, respectively.
The representatives
of "restoring" and "destruction",
they major in opposing fields of magic,
and they have long disliked each other,
and sparked hatred inside their minds.
even if they never put it
into words, apparently.
And right now...
The ugly epitome of the relationship
between the two sides...
WHITE SORCERESS
BLACK SORCERESS
...is unfolding before my eyes.
Odoroki mo hentetsu mo nai
Even easy daily missions,
Iijii deirii misshon datte
That don’t involve surprises and unexpected,
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Urutora shiikuretto ruuto ga
If there was Some ultra secret route,
Sonzai shiteru to shitara kimi wa ittai
I wonder how you would break out
Dou susumu no?
through it?
Hitamuki ni hitasura ni
Even if, completely surrendering to it,
Tada ikkyo ichidou ii koto shitatte
I stubbornly did good deeds with every step,
Tanabota ni yokoku nashiteki
Unexpected luck is an unforeseen thing.
Furachi moodo ni enkaunto shitatte
Even if we was encounter in rough mode,
Shuuten wa dochira mo kitto onaji
The end point for both of us is definitely the same.
Yume no naka ja kasanari aeru futari
We were able to sneak into each other’s dreams,
Kyuuten Chokkou Konya
so we suddenly became honest.
Futoku na doa no kagi wo akete!
So open the door of immorality tonight!
Aa hotobashiru kodou ga
Ah, your gaze, dancing with a frantic heartbeat,
Samayou shisen kogashite haimawaru
Slides over my body and burns me.
Sono te de furete mukidashi no subete wo
Touch with your hand everything, which is bare in me.
Ima sugu
Pierce me
hone made
right now
tsuranuite
to the bones.
Coming up!
Mezameru sono mae ni
Before we wake up…
Before we wake up...
Huh?
What's going on?
What happened while Noma and I were patrolling?
TAKING
TAKING A
TAKING A TOLL
Let go, okay?
Let go and let it out.
Come on, one, two.
It's not a sign to pinch stronger!
They seem to be in sync instead...
Anyway!
What happened here?
Right... It was when you and Noma
were patrolling the area.
I meant to offer a topic so that it wouldn't
get awkward to talk with someone younger...
...as the older one.
That's so condescending...
That's new...
I know that you love
comic books and games,
but even Hanabata also reads
girls' comic books, huh?
That's how we became
closer in the first place.
Despite her looks,
she's quite the maiden.
Huh...
Do you have a hobby or something, Maidena?
I think I love novels.
Especially the mystery ones.
I'm currently reading the one
that just got the Newcomer Award the other day.
Oh, the one that's
getting popular these days?
The one where the MC
turned out to be the bad guy?
She had to spoil me at the genre
that condemns spoilers the most!
MAIDE~
Maidena, calm down!
A trivial quarrel, as I expected.
It's a sad story, sure,
but mind the place, will you?
Maidena, just forgive her already, okay?
Condemn the offense,
but not the offender, right?
What do you mean?!
I've never heard of that!
I'll condemn the offense and the offender!
I've never heard of that...
She's always like this, anyway...
Tokishikko, you started this.
Apologise to her.
Maidena.
Sorry.
That was a lie.
The MC isn't the bad guy.
Don't rule him out!
"The MC isn't the bad guy"
is also a major spoiler!
You've been doing this
on purpose, haven't you?!
I'm not...
Huh?!
I haven't even read
that novel to start with.
No people would be sane enough to spoil
who the bad guy is in mystery stuff, right?
But you're nowhere near sane!
I can see you do that already!
What have we been talking about, then?!
I feel stupid raising my voice
in a place like this!
I bet you guys didn't realise it,
but we've been attacked three times now.
Sheesh... Now Noma will think of me
as someone weird because of Tokidiot!
Tokidiot...
Noma, you've got it wrong!
I'm always sincere to people
with common sense, okay!
You two can already speak up
your minds to each other.
I think that's wonderful.
But it's dangerous out here,
so mind the place next time, okay?
Sorry...
Didn't I say the same thing to her?
Isn't the way she treats us
so different compared to with Noma?
Maidena must've ranked us inside her head.
Red sorcerers, who can use
both white and black magic,
are apparently made to become
the mediator between the two sides at odds.
The very epitome of peace bringer.
I know she longs for someone older
with intelligence and grace,
but I never thought that a fellow guy could
be treated so differently from me by her.
Huh? A guy?
Wait, you're a guy, Noma?!
A guy? Now that's rude.
Ah... Someone's mistaking me
as a girl again, I see.
Yeah.
I'm a guy.
You're kidding me!
Her hopelessness is nowhere near
what it was when she got spoiled.
No way...
And here I am, thinking we could get along...
Well... That's a factor to like about him...
I'M HERE,
THOUGH
I never thought you're a guy...
A guy, huh...
IT DOESN'T HIT HER HARD AFTER ALL THIS TIME
IN FACT, SHE THINKS OF HIM AS THE IDEAL WOMAN NOW
Noma's a special case!
I can just treat him
as a fellow girl friend from now!
Problem solved!
It's a big deal in my book...
The pack is coming closer from a distance...
I'll go face them, so no infighting, okay?
Today was supposed to be
a training day for the sorcerers...
But he'll end up hunting them all now?
That screaming earlier was a madboar.
He must want to leave the small fry to us.
Then we could've just had Hitamuki come here
to find us the perfect monsters...
If we let him look after the untrained trio,
which means us, all at once,
he'll die of overwork.
Hey! Don't lump me together with you guys!
You both are way more talented than me,
so if you keep practicing,
eventually you will...
Can't I just be strong the easy way?
A monster!
Noma?!
It blended in with the other monsters
earlier and approached us?
This monster is a burreap,
A BURREAP HAS APPEARED!
and it camouflages as a plant to approach its prey!
There may be more of them,
~ FAZE ~
so keep alert of your surroundings!
Anyway, aren't you in danger there?!
The monster won't go easy on a dude!
Wait! No!
He really has it...
It looks cute, though...
W-Wait!
T-T-T-T-T-T-Tokishikko!
Take it down with your magic!
I'd love to, but when it's sticking to him
that close, I'll hit him too...
You bastard! Get off him, stupid monster!
Oww!
Ah...
What are you doing?! You hit him!
Then you figure out something, damn it!
F-Fine, then!
D-Don't shout...
Oh, right!
Just trade blows with that thing
while I heal you non-stop!
Are you an idiot?!
What was that?!
If you take Noma's place and sacrifice yourself,
it'll be win-win!
Who will win in this?!
My body and my mind!
Could this be... that I'd be better off
staying behind and fighting...?
Since it's come to this,
there's only one way, then.
Right...
We'll wait for Kikuru!
They're in perfect sync
when giving up, unlike before!
With all the commotion,
he would have noticed.
He'll fly straight here
once he's done sending that pack flying!
Oh, Kikuru!
Well, with all the commotion,
surely this would happen too...
Nooo...!
Damn it!
I only left them for a few minutes!
Let this be a lesson to you,
and listen to my words next time!
Master...
Sorry for troubling you...
No.
I could figure out
the situation from far away.
If anything, I'm the one causing you trouble.
But this time you got
to see it firsthand, didn't you?
That this job tends to take
a toll on serious people.
S-Sorry...
But I never thought that monster
would attack a guy like that as well.
I've shown you something you didn't want to.
That's not true.
Your thing was so childish,
and a lot cuter than Master's.
Stop saying it like you've seen mine already!
So you two do that...?
She's fooled you so many times already,
and you still believe her?!
Oh, right.
I just touched it with your pants on.
Hey!
Cut it out! I won't be fooled anymore...
Okay...
Oh, a rhino beetle.
Wait, Maidena! Don't! Wait!
You creep!
SCREAM
Happiness never comes,
and things are taking a toll on me.
Immoral Guild!
NEW
NEW WORLD
Ten years ago...
I aspired to be a guard,
and I committed myself to training to the death.
Then, two years after I've become a hunter,
I've never got injured once,
except during the repel spider incident.
And yet... it's taking every fibre
of my being to dodge her attacks!
It's like... I can't see inside her mind!
I wuv you, Senpai!
Lullaby magic, Lullabide!
LULLABIDE
COPYRIGHT-FREE MAGIC USED
-------------------------------------
TO PUT CHILDREN TO SLEEP
THE NUMBER ONE MAGIC MASTERED
BY MOTHERS NATIONWIDE
Senpai... I wuv you...
Thanks, Enome-san.
So this is the Frenzy
you've been talking about...
I can't believe she'd push you so far,
despite you having trained in evading...
I've learned the hard way that enemies
without hostility are the most terrifying...
She's strong, but those indiscriminate attacks are dangerous...
In terms of extermination count,
Hanabata-chan's got the highest number...
I've seen a few parties lately that want to use her as the vanguard.
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
--------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
--------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
---------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
---------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
----------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
----------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
-----------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
-------------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
-------------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
-------------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
-------------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
-------------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
-------------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
-------------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
-------------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
------------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
-----------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
-----------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
-----------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
-----------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
-----------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
---------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
---------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
---------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
---------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
---------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
---------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
---------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
---------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
---------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
---------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
---------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
---------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
---------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
--------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
--------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
--------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
--------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
--------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
--------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
--------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
--------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
--------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
--------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
--------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
--------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
--------------------------------
MONSTER EXTERMINATION
COUNT
But as a guild staff member, I can't allow her
to operate elsewhere as she is now...
She's also racking up her friendly kill count
alongside her monster kill count, so yeah...
But... the only time
she does that to her friends...
...is actually to me exclusively.
Huh?!
Come to think of it, she always said
that she loves you during Frenzy...
She seems to have adored me since long ago.
I guess the mana intoxication
brought her strong emotions to the surface.
Huh?
But I wonder if she really just admires you.
She only saw me in pictures
until we actually met,
so there must be nothing else.
But she keeps saying
she loves you like that!
Even with that massive body,
she's still a child inside.
The word "love" spoken by a child
can't possibly have that meaning, right?
I don't see you that way, you know?
The scar my daughter left
inside his heart must be so deep...
Huh? Mama's out?
Yes. She said she wanted to see Kikuru-san
and Hanabata-san's training,
so they all went to Aoba Plains.
Papa and Hana-chan too?
Looks like there's something she wants
to figure out about Hanabata-san.
Amazing stuff, huh?
Only in that space the average
female chest measurement is over 9,000.
An unseen world...
DATA    LOST
DATA    LOST RE
A new world!
DATA    LOST RECOVERY
I think it'll be bad
if Hana-chan's with them too.
Why's that?
Hana-chan's character is just...
Or rather, her body and Mama's
are on top of each other!
That's the first time
I've ever heard of that phrase.
If Papa sees the charm in Mama's body...
...then he might also be
attracted by Hana-chan as well!
No, no, he would never judge someone
by their physical appearance...
I also love soft things...!
What are boobs to men, I wonder?
I'll go check on them!
Resumisu-chan, don't touch the data for work, okay!
Now... how do I turn back time?!
It's been a while since
I chanted the lullaby magic.
This reminds me of Esyne-chan when she was little.
Esyne's grown up well now, hasn't she?
And so have you, Kikuru-kun.
KIkuru-kun, I thought you were the type that wouldn't let her use a dangerous skill like that,
but you've chosen the path
to accompany her in overcoming this, I see.
If I can have her control her skill,
the returns will be great to me,
and, ironically, Hanabata in her Frenzy...
...makes for the perfect
sparring against me.
Though, it's a bit annoying
if I'm the only one on the edge.
If my assumption is right,
maybe you can still instruct her in her Frenzy state,
even if she can't regain self-control.
Really?
I think it might actually be that simple...
You're finally awake, Hanabata.
Sorry, but I want you
to use Frenzy once more...
Senpai?
I wuv you, Senpai!
The Frenzy hasn't worn off yet?!
So her mana's not burning
when she's asleep?!
But the conditions are that limited...
That means when she's not moving,
it's safe to assume that she's
not letting out her mana, huh?
How eco-friendly...
So in order for Frenzy to wear off,
I need to make her move around.
Senpai!
Don't dodge me!
Are you crazy or what?!
We should use words that are concise
and attracting when talking to a child...
Hanabata-chan!
Kikuru-kun said he loves a ladylike girl!
A ladylike girl...
I love!
Quiet...
She got it!
Understood, understood!
She's so lively and cute!
I didn't think she'd calm down
with that one sentence...
Senpai... If I become ladylike,
will you pat me in the head?
Yeah. If you listen to what I say,
I'll pat you as many times as you want.
But you can't hug me, okay?
It hurts so much.
I'll keep my promise!
We finally understood each other!
Good for you.
Kikuru-kun, your right cheek's bleeding.
This much is nothing.
Come on, stay put now.
Thank you...
Senpai! Let me heal you!
No, I'm good.
Also, don't stand behind me.
Why can Enome-san do
that but not me?!
STOMP
You're the one who caused this scratch!
Like hell I'd let someone who sliced me
with wind pressure patch me up!
Can't you tell that this happened
because you couldn't control your strength?!
I can, okay! I can control my strength!
It's the same lethal force as before!
Shit!
You... Cut it out, Hanabata!
She didn't do that on purpose!
Don't be so hard on her!
I'll ask her to calm down!
That's so mother-like of you!
I'm sorry, Enome-san...
I'll strip as an apology!
Hey, stop it! Combined with
your mental age, it reeks of crime!
Senpai... don't hate me!
Hanabata, I told you not to hug me
because it hurts, right?
What happened to our promise?
I'm not hugging you! It's just my boobies!
Boobies are soft, so they can't hurt you!
Boobies are soft, so they can't hurt you.
Boobs are soft
so it won't
hurt you.
Quoted by Hanataba
What are you, a genius...?
Wait, don't quibble with me!
Hanabata-chan, you're a good girl,
so get off him, okay?
No!
TITS ON THE FRONT
Tits on the front!
TITS ON THE BACK
Tits on the back!
I feel... strange...
Hanabata-chan...
Kikuru-kun said he loves a ladylike girl...
But is this what...
a ladylike girl would do...?
You hate someone who shoves
her boobies to you, Senpai?
Kikuru-kun?
Oh, yeah. I-I hate her.
I'm sorry! I'll listen to what you say,
so don't hate me...
My, my.
What if Papa got distracted by Hana-chan?
Hana-chan's breasts are bigger than Mama's,
and she's still in her teens...
Don't be a wimp!
I need to do my part
for my new family as well!
When it comes to Mama's charm,
it's incomparable to Hana's childish aura.
I won't let her get in our way!
Mama Enome's so kind and soft... I wuv you!
Wow! She called me Mama just now!
Can't definitely let Esyne see this.
SHOCK
Looks like it was me all along...
...who was in the way of a new family...
E-Esyne-chan, you're getting
the wrong idea about something?!
I never thought my position
would be threatened...
Esyne-chan is mama's only daughter.
What did I just do...?
I'm glad she didn't come here
when they were pinching me.
ESCAPING REALITY
Ijippari ni kakuzatou wo tokashitara
If you stubbornly dissolve the sugar cubes
Sunao no mahou
Magic of honesty
Doji ni wa chotto oome no shinamon
Clumsy and a little too much cinnamon
Yarisugite daddadubada
Too much daddadubada
Mata mebunryou no kimagure to yasashisa de
In addition, with the whims and gentleness of mebenryo
Himitsu no reshipi wo mou kakimidasanaide
Don't disturb the secret recipe anymore
Oh don’t call my name
Oh don't call my name
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Amai dake janai
Not just sweet
Mune no oku no tokimeki iroiro
Heart-pounding feelings deep in my chest Various things
Watashi dake no baransu wo
I have my own balance
Wakatte hoshikute
I want you to understand
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Karai dake ja iya
I don't like it
Mune no oku no tokimeki wa
just because it's spicy
Mochiron desho namida to koi no mariaaju...
Of course, if it's tears, it's a marriage of love
...Yappari wakaranaide!
…I don't know!
DIAGRAM GUILD
The flowers coming out of Hanabata
during her Frenzy aren't real flowers,
but the overflowing mana
that's taken shape of flowers.
That's why we can't see the flowers
when she doesn't burn her mana.
I see.
NEXT
NEXT EPISODE
I
I DON'T
I DON'T WANT
I DON'T WANT TO
I DON'T WANT TO GO
I DON'T WANT TO GO HOME
I DON'T WANT TO GO HOME NOW
RIDDLE
RIDDLE SOLVING
RIDDLE SOLVING LITTLE