---------------------
WILL TALE
Thank you for your help until today.
Please come visit us anytime.
A senior hunter of mine, Will Tale.
He will retire as a guard
to take over his family's apple farm.
Kikuru.
Do you hate losing me that much?
Of course...
STAY HERE
If the main hunter retires,
I won't be able to retire now!
STAY HERE
I can tell what's on
his mind even from here.
Odoroki mo hentetsu mo nai
Even easy daily missions,
Iijii deirii misshon datte
That don’t involve surprises and unexpected,
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Urutora shiikuretto ruuto ga
If there was Some ultra secret route,
Sonzai shiteru to shitara kimi wa ittai
I wonder how you would break out
Dou susumu no?
through it?
Hitamuki ni hitasura ni
Even if, completely surrendering to it,
Tada ikkyo ichidou ii koto shitatte
I stubbornly did good deeds with every step,
Tanabota ni yokoku nashiteki
Unexpected luck is an unforeseen thing.
Furachi moodo ni enkaunto shitatte
Even if we was encounter in rough mode,
Shuuten wa dochira mo kitto onaji
The end point for both of us is definitely the same.
Yume no naka ja kasanari aeru futari
We were able to sneak into each other’s dreams,
Kyuuten Chokkou Konya
so we suddenly became honest.
Futoku na doa no kagi wo akete!
So open the door of immorality tonight!
Aa hotobashiru kodou ga
Ah, your gaze, dancing with a frantic heartbeat,
Samayou shisen kogashite haimawaru
Slides over my body and burns me.
Sono te de furete mukidashi no subete wo
Touch with your hand everything, which is bare in me.
Ima sugu
Pierce me
hone made
right now
tsuranuite
to the bones.
Coming up!
Mezameru sono mae ni
Before we wake up…
Before we wake up...
A BOLT
I sent a veteran off because I thought
having him leave would trouble me so much...
A BOLT OUT
A BOLT OUT OF THE
A BOLT OUT OF THE BLUE
Hey, Kikuru-kun.
We have another two members joining us,
so don't worry about manpower.
Two of them?
They're all girls in their teens, too!
A dude's fine too,
just give me a veteran, damn it!
So you want me to look
after them as well, I bet?
We'll be getting more friends!
And more work to my pile...
The new members now are a knight
and a black sorceress.
A knight has high offensive and defensive stats,
and is also versatile.
A black sorceress has elemental
and AoE attacks.
Well...
I wouldn't expect too much from me, though.
SHOOM
Are you telling me she's the one...?
Uhh...
She's the black sorceress, Tokishikko Dana.
Hello, nice to meet you...
BLACK SORCERESS
TOKISHIKKO DANA
Forget her abilities,
I can't feel any motivation coming from her.
I-I'm sure a burning passion
is buried somewhere deep inside her heart.
I don't want to work.
She doesn't even show
any intention of starting!
She's too chill, inside and out!
But if she doesn't even want to go herself,
then we can just leave her here.
I don't have time to train novices
who don't even want to improve themselves.
Hold on, Master.
Though I hate it,
I must work to make a living.
I won't be in your way,
so take me with you.
You want work, work properly.
I just want my share.
I'll knock you down before that.
TOKISHIKKO HAS JOINED YOUR PARTY!
~MEBUKI FOREST~
Now, according to Enome-san,
we were supposed to be joined by another new guy,
LACKING SKILL
but the current situation
is already too much for me,
LACKING SKILL
LACKING MOTIVATION
so we'll be going with this formation.
LACKING SKILL
Okay! I'll do my best with dedication!
Hitamuki. I'll leave my job to you too.
Two sides of a coin...
Kik-kun, is Mede-chan not coming today?
She has school, after all.
Also, seems like she's still tired from yesterday.
You've been working for three days straight, but are you okay?
Yes! I have confidence in my stamina!
I suppose that's just the natural ability
of a beast human, huh?
Oh, right. You've been working
for three days straight too, Ki-kun...
Good girl, Hitamuki.
Toki-chan?
You're so bright and full of motivation,
I can't really see you as being
the same age as me.
Your lethargy is also remarkable, though.
I sense a monster nearby!
Leave this one to me!
Hey!
You just rest for a while, Kik-kun!
I'll do my best to meet
your expectations today!
Yeah, you did meet my worst expectations!
As if it were no longer an inevitable future...
Allowing progress to be sucked
into the outcome...
It's not the way I planned it,
but it's time to see your abilities now.
Tokishikko?
You can't start running out of the blue...
You're down just by running?!
You're kidding me!
Just how much are you lacking stamina?!
Do you really imagine
sorcerers having high stamina?
Us black sorcerers are a group of people
who stay indoors all year round and study hard.
If you're aware of it,
you should reflect...
Anyway, does that look okay to you?
Hitamuki's in rather...
lewd danger over there.
I forgot...
I'm sorry...
You told me to rest earlier, didn't you?
Ah, yes...
Was it because I've been working
outside as much as you have?
You might be fine, but I'm tired.
That's...
Don't get too cocky.
Only those who can do their job have
the right to look after others.
If you can't do your job properly yet,
doing that will instead be a bother.
I'm really sorry...
Hey, that's enough...
Just as you care about those around you...
Even I... also care about you in my own way.
So you should take care of yourself more.
Kik-kun...
I'm here too, you know?
Trying to show off in front of someone else?
Sho—
That's all for the lecture! Also, Tokishikko!
I don't plan on sending you home
until I see what you're made of.
Uegh...
I share the same responsibility
for letting Hitamuki push ahead on her own.
I guess I'll just work my wage.
Um...
Hey, if you want to contribute,
now's the chance.
And why's that?
Behind your is a monster's den.
We're in danger...
-------------------------
ZIPPYRABBITS
HAVE APPEARED!
Zippyrabbits, huh?
They're so cute!
Do they also attack people?
I once heard that rabbits are cowards.
They're quite rabid, so be careful.
Also, they're fast, and despite their looks,
they possess some strength too.
You should've told us earlier.
I'm scared...
But they look so pissed off.
Were they stressed because the bearlion
had taken over the area around their den?
They're stamping so much...
But it's hard to deal with them
when you know what's going on inside of their minds.
Also, I used to look after the rabbits back in primary and middle school.
All the more reason to no—
Flame, ice, or thunder...
Which one do you like?
I'll slaughter you all with your
favorite elements, you beasts!
Well, wasn't that a short conflict?
Now, time to see what's she made of.
Thunder Magic, Voltage!
TOKISHIKKO HAS CHANTED VOLTAGE
Voltage!
Voltera!
Stop dodging my attacks!
SULK
Don't be unreasonable.
Her power is perfect,
but her reaction is slow.
To put it short, she has slow reflexes.
Hey, you should fight too, Master!
Predict the enemy's movements
and try again now!
I look after novices because I'm looking for a successor,
and maybe training them as well.
Huh? What's that?
I want you to work hard as well
for my campus life I've dreamed of.
What the heck?!
What a surprise...
I thought you were a caring brother,
but you turned out to be a big egoist...
Hitamuki, we should work together for thi—
Every time I see her...
she's always being groped!
------------------------------
FIDGETY - KIKURU HAS
BECOME FIDGETY
------------------------------
FIDGETY - KIKURU HAS
BECOME FIDGETY
------------------------------
FIDGETY - KIKURU HAS
BECOME FIDGETY
If you're worried about her, just go save her!
Or rather, I beg you!
B-But she needs to get better herself...
Their fluffy fur... rubbing against me...
Hey! What are you thrusting
your hips for?! Stop it!
I don't want to see you rabbits like that!
Get off me!
I'm not into this kind of thing!
You little...
Volta—
As part of my teaching policy,
I meant to be a spectator
for their training today, but...
---------------------------------------------------------------------------
THE YOUNG ADULT MAN WATCHING FROM THE SIDE AS THE GIRLS ARE OVERRUN BY THE MONSTERS
From an outsider's perspective,
what I'm doing is just perverted.
Oh, well. I guess I should—
Don't get... too cocky...
If I can't catch you one by one...
I'll just catch you all at once!
FWISH FWISH
I'll burn the whole area!
Don't! The rabbits are already go—
Voltega!
---------------
TOKISHIKKO
HAS CHANTED VOLTEGA
HITAMUKI:
--------
DOWN
TOKISHIKKO:
DOWN (BY OWN SPELL)
KIKURU:
(DODGED EVERYTHING)
------------------------------------------
GIRLS IN TATTERS
Sure, I wanted you to get closer
with one of the girls here...
YOUNG MAN UNHARMED
But you didn't have to
force them to do that...
What are you talking about?!
What was on your mind?!
You're the worst, Kikuru!
Even though we cried for help,
he just silently watched as the monsters
were playing with our bodies...
Don't just leave out the main point!
That's unfair!
UGH...
Wait!
You're back, Tokishikko.
You went on without me,
so I was worried about you.
While you three were out there doing the quest,
the knight girl had arrived here.
KNIGHT
HANABATA NOHKINS
Nice to meet you. I'm Hanabata, a knight.
I'm Tokishikko's childhood friend.
N-Nice to meet you...
SHE'S SO BIG IN MANY WAYS
Nice to meet you too, Senpai.
I'm looking forward to your guidance.
Same here.
I feared that there might be
another slacker in my team,
but it's a relief that she seems
to have the capacity for labour.
Nice to meet you too,
my martial artist fr—
Nice to meet you.
Hey, you two are pretty beat up!
Did the monsters get you?!
Senpai. I can't turn a blind eye after
they've done so much to my friends!
The culprit was your friend.
As you can see, Hanabata can be too serious
and easily get fired up.
But her fighting skills are high, for real.
What?
I'm proud to say that I'm second to none
of the adults when it comes to close combat.
You may appoint me to the front line.
I've finally found a friendly
and proper potential candidate...!
My retirement...
...is just up ahead now!
HANABATA HAS JOINED YOUR PARTY!
Immoral Guild.
Weight equals sturdiness.
Size equals strength.
Muscle-brains master race!
Nohkin Sports.
I never thought that our new recruit...
A
A DYING
...was the heiress of the equipment company...
A DYING HUNTER
Nohkin Sports' president's...
The president's daughter...
Hana-chan... Hanabata-sama!
Sama?! Please, don't call me that!
I don't have any status or power myself.
I'd be happy if you could treat me
as your equal, as your friend.
Equal, huh...
Have a safe trip, Milady!
Wh-Wh-What are you...?!
Feels like if I jokingly poked at you,
I'd be erased from existence, no joke.
L-Let's go now!
Sorry for surprising you.
It's okay.
Master Kikuru Madan.
We do not possess qualifications as guards...
Hence, we cannot accompany
you all in your quests.
Therefore, we ask you...
To please...
Take care of Hanabata-sama!
All I can feel from them is pressure!
Please ask about Hanabata-sama
from her friend, Tokishikko-sama.
That very person is here with me,
so I'll just ask straight from the source.
Well... there's one side of hers
that only the people around her may realise...
~MEBUKI FOREST~
Ask her friend, huh?
--------------------------------
-------------------------------
FROM : TOKISHIKO
RE : COME HERE QUICK
I got an errand to do,
so I'll skip for today
And the said friend is absent...
FROM : TOKISHIKO
RE : COME HERE QUICK
I got an errand to do,
so I'll skip for today
Gotta go save the world RPG
I got an errand to do,
so I'll skip for today
Gotta go save the world RPG
She skipped work just to play a game?!
I'm sorry. I'll have her make up for this.
So please let this slide.
Well... I think you can get better,
more normal friends than her, though.
She may look like that, but she's actually
a kind, caring, gentle girl.
Though, she's already not being kind
to me right from the get-go.
Now, Hanabata.
It's not fair to ask you
to fight just to see what you can do.
For now, I'll...
TODAY
FOR
SURE!
Hitamuki will show you the ropes.
What's up with the pause?
GLOOM
I'll do my best with dedication!
Kik-kun, there's a slime over there!
Leave it to m—
Kik-kun?
My hands... just slipped...
Oh, they did?
All right, let's start over...
There's a slime ove—
Kik-kun?!
My feet...
Your feet what?!
My feet just slipped!
Kik-kun!
Why?! Why didn't you leave
the fighting to me?!
I can't...
I can't imagine you
winning against that thing!
Th-That's...!
But without real combat experience,
I'll stay a novice forever!
Yeah, it'd trouble me too, but...
Kik-kun!
Yeah!
A MADBOAR HAS APPEARED!
You two, stay ba—
What monstrous strength...
I'm sorry, Senpai.
I went ahead without asking
for instructions out of danger.
No, that was a good call.
You're so amazing, Hana-chan!
You beat that big monster in one strike!
As the shield of the party,
I have to eliminate the enemies first.
I'm a knight, so I just carried out
my proper role as the front line.
Proper role....
HAS NEVER BEEN
ABLE TO CARRY
IT OUT
I've never been able to do my proper role!
Your recon ability is amazing too!
Thanks to that,
I could deal with the monster quickly.
I don't think attacking the enemy
is the only thing contributing to the party.
Hana-chan...
I'll work harder to find more monsters!
It's not a martial artist's job, though.
A lot of monsters are coming our way!
A pack of them?
Come!
Senpai?
Here they come!
------
A BACK ATTACK!
Senpai, are you sure about letting
the monsters have the high ground?
Animals with longer hind legs
have difficulty going downhill.
Should they trip, we can strike them.
Why are you tripping?!
This is bad, Senpai!
The madboards are surrounding Hitamuki!
I'm part of the martial arts community, too!
I'm not going to allow myself
to be their punching bag!
There you go again!
You've never once struck a blow!
Is all you're good
at is being a punching bag?!
I've always been...
a punching bag... for the monsters...
I always let the monsters
have their way with me...
That has a slightly different implication!
Wh-Wh-What is that?!
Does fighting with monsters
include perverted stuff like that?!
Beats me!
At the very least,
it will attack for an instant death.
It's always a fight for life...
Though I've prepared to lose myself,
I never thought we could get something
embarrassing like that instead...
Incorrigible!
I'll finish them all of with my "Frenzy"!
Frenzy?
A skill that trades reason for power, huh...
-------------------
COMBAT SKILL
FRENZY
While my memories during
Frenzy might get vague,
I can still tell between friends or foes,
so don't worry.
Here I go!
This power...
Hanabata's real power...
Comin' at ya with full power!
Who the heck are you?!
Huh? What are you looking at?
Got a bone to pick with me?!
Badoom!
ONE MADBOAR WEIGHTS
ABOUT 400 KG
Up, up, and away!
It's not the Frenzy I know...
It's not Frenzy... but rather Intoxication...
------------------
FRENZY
X
INTOXICATION
O
The stronger my power is...
The bigger it is, the better!
Hana-chan...?
So hot...
Hey, Hanabata! Do you recognise me?
Can you even tell what I'm saying?!
Senpai...
I got 'em all!
Get off me!
Praise me! Pat my head!
Ugh...
You've done well.
You've been more than up to the task.
I love you!
Kik-kun?!
Let go! My back will snap, damn it!
What do you mean you can tell
between friends or foes?!
You're either hostile or you're gracious,
but the consequences are the same!
Still...
Depending on how you look at it,
this might be a valuable experience...
Though it seems like
a once-in-a-lifetime experience!
Hana-chan, Kik-kun is hurting!
I remember using Frenzy...
What happened, Senpai?!
Did a monster get you?!
Yeah... I was attacked
by a monster disguised as my party member...
PUSH FORWARD
RETURN TO CITY
Mimicry?! How despicable!
PUSH FORWAR
PUSH FORWA
PUSH FORW
PUSH F
PUSH
PU
Aahh...
RE
RETU
RETURN
RETURN TO
RETURN TO CI
RETURN TO CITY
Way to go!
The madboars have been injuring
a lot of guards, so thank you!
Hanabata took most
of the screen time today.
Hana-chan, you're so strong!
R-Really? I'm glad I could be of help.
MY
BREASTPLATE
IS
GONE
AGAIN!
I think I might've shown a disgraceful display during my Frenzy,
HERE'S
YOUR
BREASTPLATE!
MY
BREASTPLATE
IS
GONE
AGAIN!
HERE'S
YOUR
BREASTPLATE!
but I hope you can turn a blind eye to that.
She thinks she must be
fighting fiercely during Frenzy,
FRENZY
and all the people in her house
would just say "yes" to that.
YOU'RE SO TOUGH!
DID I DO OKAY?
But they can't just keep lying forever.
They all went flying, it was so amazing!
Maybe I should tell this to her
for her own sake and mine...
But... yeah...
WHOOOOOSH! WHOOOOOSH! WHOOOOOSH! WHOOOOOSH! WHOOOOOSH! WHOOOOOSH!
Let's just wait and see for now...
Thank you for your cooperation.
Wh-Why are you all here again?
I've looked after four new recruits,
after a lot of mental grind...
But gained nothing from that...
We've got a lot of boars, though!
To be continued!
TO BE CONTINUE
Ijippari ni kakuzatou wo tokashitara
If you stubbornly dissolve the sugar cubes
Sunao no mahou
Magic of honesty
Doji ni wa chotto oome no shinamon
Clumsy and a little too much cinnamon
Yarisugite daddadubada
Too much daddadubada
Mata mebunryou no kimagure to yasashisa de
In addition, with the whims and gentleness of mebenryo
Himitsu no reshipi wo mou kakimidasanaide
Don't disturb the secret recipe anymore
Oh don’t call my name
Oh don't call my name
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Amai dake janai
Not just sweet
Mune no oku no tokimeki iroiro
Heart-pounding feelings deep in my chest Various things
Watashi dake no baransu wo
I have my own balance
Wakatte hoshikute
I want you to understand
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Karai dake ja iya
I don't like it
Mune no oku no tokimeki wa
just because it's spicy
Mochiron desho namida to koi no mariaaju...
Of course, if it's tears, it's a marriage of love
...Yappari wakaranaide!
…I don't know!
NEXT
NEXT EPISODE
LET'S
LET'S PLAY
LET'S PLAY TOGETHER
YOU
YOU ARE
YOU ARE MY
YOU ARE MY FIRST