In order to take precautions against large monsters
such as the repel spider the other day,
I tried enlarging our scope
to the deeper part of the forest...
Wait... I can't run anymore...
Nooo!! Don't come near me!
Don't spread out, guys!
The usual scene unfolding...
I guess her recon can't keep up
with this many monsters.
Tokishikko! Set Hitamuki free with your magic!
I'm beat...
You're beat already?!
Maidena! Cover them with support magic!
I'm scared...
You're scared already?!
This is an emergency!
Allow me to use Frenzy, Sir!
Huh? Wa—
Comin' at ya with full force!
Damn it! I need to hide...
It's dangerous, so stay close to me~
It's dangerous, so let me go...
Hanabata "also" defeated
the monsters after this.
Kaboom!
Odoroki mo hentetsu mo nai
Even easy daily missions,
Iijii deirii misshon datte
That don’t involve surprises and unexpected,
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Urutora shiikuretto ruuto ga
If there was Some ultra secret route,
Sonzai shiteru to shitara kimi wa ittai
I wonder how you would break out
Dou susumu no?
through it?
Hitamuki ni hitasura ni
Even if, completely surrendering to it,
Tada ikkyo ichidou ii koto shitatte
I stubbornly did good deeds with every step,
Tanabota ni yokoku nashiteki
Unexpected luck is an unforeseen thing.
Furachi moodo ni enkaunto shitatte
Even if we was encounter in rough mode,
Shuuten wa dochira mo kitto onaji
The end point for both of us is definitely the same.
Yume no naka ja kasanari aeru futari
We were able to sneak into each other’s dreams,
Kyuuten Chokkou Konya
so we suddenly became honest.
Futoku na doa no kagi wo akete!
So open the door of immorality tonight!
Aa hotobashiru kodou ga
Ah, your gaze, dancing with a frantic heartbeat,
Samayou shisen kogashite haimawaru
Slides over my body and burns me.
Sono te de furete mukidashi no subete wo
Touch with your hand everything, which is bare in me.
Ima sugu
Pierce me
hone made
right now
tsuranuite
to the bones.
Coming up!
Mezameru sono mae ni
Before we wake up…
Before we wake up...
~ MEBUKI CITY ~
THE
THE WAVERING
THE WAVERING EMOTION
Kik-kun...
I'm sorry I wasn't much of a help.
No, it was also caused
by a misjudgement on my part too.
That can't be true...
Don't sweat it!
Let's make the next one count!
I really can't forgive you.
I don't have ranged skills,
whether for attack or defence.
There's no way someone like me
could cover more than one person.
Hitamuki would be the first to be attacked
even if I put her down in the rearguard.
Tokishikko would simply collapse
over long distance travelling.
Maidena would get too scared,
she'd be unable to unleash her potential.
While Noma would get a passing grade,
I couldn't just leave the main DPS or healer job to him.
Even Hanabata,
the only one I could vouch for...
This is a conundrum.
Huh?
You're dismissed now.
Tomorrow, you'll have to train on your own.
Sure!
Training on my own...
on my own initiative...
That means a day-off~
Come on, now...
Enome-san.
Hanabata-chan? What's up?
I'd like to consult with you
about something...
Consult?
I, uh...
Am I being hated by Kikuru-senpai?
Huh?
Please tell me if you've
heard anything about this.
I kind of get the feeling...
...that he's been avoiding me.
I don't think he is, though.
Even so,
I want to be more useful
during exterminations too.
I've saved my fellow colleagues
in a tight spot...
...on several occasions as well.
But...
No matter how many monsters I take down,
or how much I try to be of help,
I can't seem to gain his trust...
Oh?
Enome-san, Hanabata-san!
What are you talking about—
What a menacing aura!
This is some destructive power!
The pride of our guild...
The two-top boobs!
Picture of two soft materials!
Are you okay?
Should Hitamuki-chan make
an appearance here as well,
I might just fall to my knees.
What did you say about me?
SHOCK
Resumisu-san?! Are you okay?!
I just came here to grab
the stuff I forgot!
This guild has an unfair
rate of big breasts...
Let's go to the clinic!
I'll heal you with my physchakra!
If I were as bright as them,
then maybe I'd have just told him directly
without overthinking.
Hanabata-chan has defeated
ten monsters as well today.
HUUUUUG
Previously,
Kikuru-kun said that if he were to choose a partner,
Hitamuki would be the best match...
Have I...
...done something...
...that made Senpai hate me?
-----------------
THE FOLLOWING
DAY
That's what happened.
I see.
Well, I knew this might happen soon.
I guess we should make up our minds already.
Both me and the Nohkins guys.
Just leave the rest to me.
Oh, Enome-san.
In case anything happens to me...
Please gather my ashes, okay?
Kikuru-kun?
And that's what happened.
B-But if we tell this to her...
It'll become clear that we've
been deceiving her this whole time!
Could you not be so bent on preserving
yourselves after all you've done now?
I think this makes
for a good opportunity as well.
The important thing in a battle is
to know your enemies and yourself.
But she's definitely not doing the latter.
To keep letting her use an ultimate skill
that she can't control...
...would mean danger for herself as well.
If you really care for Hanabata,
then we should tell her the truth
about her Flower Frenzy.
Your statement indeed
hits the nail in the head.
However...
This was never about us
protecting ourselves, but...
But?
There is no way to get out of this unscathed,
without damaging her trust,
and without incurring her scolding...
You're just trying to preserve yourselves
like you do your first grandson!
If she knows the truth, then...
...she will surely seal off that skill.
She is usually very disciplined
in her appearance,
but only shows her friendly
and pampered side when she uses Frenzy.
And we all won't be
able to see that anymore.
Could you please reconsider this?!
That's not the problem here, is it?
Then, uh... Could I get the album back, please?
My album...
I have this tape over here that contains
recordings of Hanabata using Frenzy in practice...
...before I met you guys,
borrowed from Tokishikko.
My album...
Tokishikko-sama...
She's surely come and seen our lady's
battle practice many times already...
Flowery power~
Got myself a treasure trove of videos!
It also contains the recordings of our
quests so far that Tokishikko recorded.
I'll invite her to my house
and have her see this now.
My album...
I'll be there as well to make up
for my part in the lie,
if that's all right with you.
U-Understood.
Then we shall make up our minds as well.
Yes...
Okay.
We will look forward
to your report back in the mansion.
Why are you trying to go back now?
You're coming with me!
We will pay for any damage incurred...
...when our lady is going frenzy!
Still want to preserve yourselves
till the end, huh!
You really think if you just give them money,
the plebs will work for you?!
Sheesh...
It doesn't change the fact that they'll be
scolded later even if they're running away now.
SENPAI
S-Senpai?
Hello?
Oh, Hanabata.
Sorry for the sudden call,
but are you free today?
Yeah.
Then come to my house now.
Huh?! Your house?!
Oh, you're summoning the others
as well for a meeting, right?
No, just you.
It's hard to tell on the phone.
I'll explain it to you when you get here.
It's a pressing matter
that requires my presence...
In his room...
With just me?
Wait...
Could that be... No...
No way...
So he doesn't...
...hate me...?
S-So instead, he...
What am I, a fool?!
It only happened yesterday!
Enome-san must've spoken
to Senpai about this!
I'm sure Senpai invited me there
to tell me how he thinks of me...
H-How he thinks of me...
Wait, why am I cleansing myself anyway?!
Immoral Guild~!
THE
THE GREAT
THE GREAT FATHER
G-Greetings.
Yeah. Sorry to have you come visit me.
P-Pardon the intrusion, then.
Is it just me...
...or Hanabata smells
a lot more floral than usual?
Oh, Senpai.
I've baked you some cookies.
Please have them if you'd like.
Even though I've baked them,
I haven't eaten anything since last night...
That means I'm the first test subject?
But cooking is a good thing, huh?
You can immerse yourself
in the work while cooking.
I'd already imagined
a future in which Hanabata...
...would kill me by mistake
after losing her cool from watching the tape...
I see... so external factors
don't always kill you.
Wow, I can't wait to eat these~
What do you think?
They look appealing enough to you, right?
Yeah, they do look appealing.
I don't want to be thought of as a woman
who can't cook forever!
I want to clear my name.
I don't think you can do that
when I haven't even tasted them,
but I lack the courage to do so.
Anyway, the reason I called you here today...
...is that I want you to view a certain tape.
But... I want you to promise me
this beforehand.
Please don't go wild over this.
You say funny stuff sometimes, Senpai.
Are you planning to play a horror movie?
It might be horror for you, though.
B-But if it's really horror stuff,
I could just pretend to be scared
and lean in close to him...
But I thought he had something to say,
so why is he doing this instead?
The reason I got called here today...
...was clearly because I asked
Enome-san for advice, and yet...
Comin' at ya with full power!
Kaboom!
A different kind of horror
from what I had imagined is playing on the TV...
Wh-Wh-Wha—
What kind of vicious video manipulation is this?!
It's too elaborate for a prank!
Calm down, Hanabata!
That footage is not edited
nor is it a prank at all!
Enough with the jokes!
That will be a bigger problem!
This is... how you look when using Frenzy!
Huh?
I love you, Senpai!
I wuv you, Senpai!
Huuuuh?!
Sorry for keeping it quiet from you.
Don't listen to this!
Don't see it either!
So soft!
Smells so good!
I can't breathe!
Why are all my interactions with her...
TAP TAP
...always life-threatening?!
Praise me, Senpai! Pat my head!
My current reality is in sync with the screen...
THUD
I used a cookie made
by a maiden as an attack item...
Anyway, I need to get her off me quick...
Or else my "knife"
would be in trouble as usual!
A young lady who is assertive
in many ways all over her body...
You can't... touch there...
And my fingers are on the only
part of her body that's retractable.
Shit! She's going to kill me!
FALSE CHARGE
Appeal! Appeal!
He's not moving anymore...
FALSE CHARGE
Sorry...
...but could you lend me your clothes?
I...
I have one great father.
Oh... your father?
Until last year, when he took over
the company from my grandfather,
my father was a knight
as well as the company's employee.
Due to his minimal number of quests,
he didn't get to defeat a lot of monsters,
but his strength was still top-tier.
I thought no guard
could ever pass him in this city.
But one day, he praised a
19 year old new ace of the city.
He wasn't really popular
with his fellow guards,
always on his own...
The one time he was mentioned was
in a small corner of a local newspaper.
Yet my father still praised him.
My strict father, who rarely praised people.
While I was envious,
I still adored him more than that.
But then, I never thought...
I never thought I'd hurt
the very ace I adored...!
The people at home...
The must be scared of me
that they couldn't tell me the truth!
I'm sure they must be mad at me!
Not at all, Milady!
We are fools for our continuous lies
to you to see your friendly side!
If there's anyone to blame,
please blame us!
Hey, you guys just came out straight
after knowing she won't be mad at you, huh?
You...
...don't hate me?
Not at all, Milady!
We all adore you!
Let's tear this place down
and put up a statue of you!
Hey.
Then I shall issue
convertible notes in your portrait!
The servants here
don't really mind bothering people, huh?
Of course, I don't hate you, Hanabata.
I'd rather like sensible people.
That means I'm not fond of them.
L-Like...
I meant to have you seal off Frenzy
after showing you the videos,
but I changed my mind.
We should use it next time.
Why?!
That skill is so powerful, and it's true
that it's saved a lot of people beside me.
But you'll be hurt again!
I'm not saying that I want you to use it as it is
without the ability to control it.
FRENZY
Frenzy is essentially a condition of losing reason through suggestion, isn't it?
Y-Yeah...
FLOWER FRENZY
But your Flower Frenzy...
is a skill to improve physical performance as a result of the outburst...
of magical power in the body
due to mana drunkenness.
There's no need for you
to lose your reason.
That means, if you can overcome
that drunkenness,
you can use the skill
while maintaining consciousness.
But...
I've never been able
to maintain my consciousness!
So there's no guarantee
that I'll be able to overcome it!
Also, I...
I can't just trouble you any more—
Just trouble me as much as you want.
After hearing what you said earlier,
I could tell how you felt about me.
H-How I felt about you...?
You could tell...?
It's "respect", right?
I want to work hard enough
to match your admiration.
As a matter of fact, I'd thought a little
along the lines of "courtesy", too...
I might just be too self-conscious.
Senpai—
I've been embarrassed
by the same mistake before.
The word "like"...
...doesn't always mean romantic affection.
You can't just take words at face value.
I think I'm starting to get it now.
No, you're not.
You're taking her admiration at face value.
Sorry to say this out of the blue,
but do you mind sparring with me now?
No, I don't mind.
Somehow, her attacks
were tougher than usual today.
TO BE CONTINUE
To be continued.
Ijippari ni kakuzatou wo tokashitara
If you stubbornly dissolve the sugar cubes
Sunao no mahou
Magic of honesty
Doji ni wa chotto oome no shinamon
Clumsy and a little too much cinnamon
Yarisugite daddadubada
Too much daddadubada
Mata mebunryou no kimagure to yasashisa de
In addition, with the whims and gentleness of mebenryo
Himitsu no reshipi wo mou kakimidasanaide
Don't disturb the secret recipe anymore
Oh don’t call my name
Oh don't call my name
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Amai dake janai
Not just sweet
Mune no oku no tokimeki iroiro
Heart-pounding feelings deep in my chest Various things
Watashi dake no baransu wo
I have my own balance
Wakatte hoshikute
I want you to understand
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Karai dake ja iya
I don't like it
Mune no oku no tokimeki wa
just because it's spicy
Mochiron desho namida to koi no mariaaju...
Of course, if it's tears, it's a marriage of love
...Yappari wakaranaide!
…I don't know!
NEXT
NEXT EPISODE
TAKING
TAKING A
TAKING A TOLL
NEW
NEW WORLD