Kikuru Madan.
Despite looking like this,
I'm still Kikuru Madan in the flesh.
And now...
I'm dressed as a doctor for a reason.
152 cm...
Odoroki mo hentetsu mo nai
Even easy daily missions,
Iijii deirii misshon datte
That don’t involve surprises and unexpected,
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Urutora shiikuretto ruuto ga
If there was Some ultra secret route,
Sonzai shiteru to shitara kimi wa ittai
I wonder how you would break out
Dou susumu no?
through it?
Hitamuki ni hitasura ni
Even if, completely surrendering to it,
Tada ikkyo ichidou ii koto shitatte
I stubbornly did good deeds with every step,
Tanabota ni yokoku nashiteki
Unexpected luck is an unforeseen thing.
Furachi moodo ni enkaunto shitatte
Even if we was encounter in rough mode,
Shuuten wa dochira mo kitto onaji
The end point for both of us is definitely the same.
Yume no naka ja kasanari aeru futari
We were able to sneak into each other’s dreams,
Kyuuten Chokkou Konya
so we suddenly became honest.
Futoku na doa no kagi wo akete!
So open the door of immorality tonight!
Aa hotobashiru kodou ga
Ah, your gaze, dancing with a frantic heartbeat,
Samayou shisen kogashite haimawaru
Slides over my body and burns me.
Sono te de furete mukidashi no subete wo
Touch with your hand everything, which is bare in me.
Ima sugu
Pierce me
hone made
right now
tsuranuite
to the bones.
Coming up!
Mezameru sono mae ni
Before we wake up…
Before we wake up...
~MEBUKI FOREST~
It all started with a guild medical check-up...
DOCTOR
DOCTOR MURDER
...at the beginning of the year.
It seems I was the last person to be examined
---------------------
GUILD CLINIC
and the doctor went on to the next round of check-ups early.
No way!
S-Sensei!
I couldn't find Doctor...
Wh-What do I do now...
Kikuru-san, please help me!
Please do the check-up in place of Doctor!
Huh?
E
CARE
U-Umm...
NURSE
MISU CARE
RESUMISU CARE
Looks like the list of name we had...
...wasn't the latest one...
We still have four people...
...waiting to be examined...
Then why not tell Sensei to come back?
Sensei doesn't have a phone!
Then you can just do Doctor's work instead
since you're a nurse yourself,
and more knowledgeable than me.
We don't have a white coat
that fits an imp's size!
Even if we had one,
I'm still scared of being exposed.
I could say the same for myself!
I beg you! If I screw up big time again,
they said they'll fire me!
It's not your first offence?
But the examinees are the guards here, right?
That means they'll know my face.
We can cover your mouth with a mask!
They can still tell by my hair—
Then let's cover up your face in bandages!
What do you think now?
If you also change your expression...
I look like a patient instead.
Even if I'm a doctor, I look like a quack.
I'm really not familiar at all
with the technical stuff as a doctor, you know?
Oh, don't worry.
The remaining examinees
are all young'uns in their teens!
In all likelihood,
they can't have serious illnesses.
This woman...
The list of names wasn't the latest,
and the remaining four examiness
are in their teens...
Come in!
Umm... We're here for the medical check-up...
Y...Yes...
I can't...
Hey!
I definitely can't let them find out!
Thus began the medical check-up by Kikuru Madan...
A.K.A. Doctor Murder.
UNLICENCED DOCTOR
DOCTOR MURDER
U-U-Urinalysis... Urine?!
Wh-What do I do with these?!
Please calm down!
This is too much for me!
I'm not leaving those in your hands!
Raising your heels won't change the result.
I was a little shaken up at the start,
but I finished measuring their heights, weights,
eyesight, hearing, and blood
pressures without incident.
[ WEIGHT ]
[    BUST   ]
[      HIP    ]
[   WAIST  ]
Next is...
Don't worry.
This is my job as a nurse to begin with.
Resumisu-san would handle that,
so I managed to avoid further problems.
Eh, Hanabata-san's bust size...
110?!
110?
W-Wait, please don't say it out loud...
K75... 110...!
It's practically my height!
110...
Sensei...
No... Doctor Murder.
Time for auscultation.
This is inevitable.
It would be troublesome if I got distraught
and raised suspicions to them.
Expose yourself.
Sensei, you can say "please open up
the front of your shirt" instead!
Please open up the front of your shirt.
That's too shameless of me...
But... the more I think about it,
the more I question
my taking on this risky role.
What am I doing...
Isn't it actually worth the risks?!
110...
Sensei, please examine her...
If those servants of hers find out
about this, I'm so done for...
Um... Sensei...
Won't it be hard for you to listen
to my heartbeat there...?
Please stick it on the base of her chest if you can!
Excuse me.
I'm sure her size far exceed
that of Enome-san's...
I don't even think I'll ever find anything better
than this in my lifetime.
But you see, Hanabata...
Every time I auscultate you,
there's something more to the dubious
look of disdain in your eyes...
...who usually calls me "Senpai"...
Senpai!
...than the world-class bulge
that I'm forced to touch.
All good.
Next one, please!
Tokishikko, huh?
Please open up the front of your shirt.
I thought I had it all figured out.
I didn't think I'd be so easily swayed now...
...after witnessing Hitamuki, Enome-san,
and Hanabata's voluptuous nude bodies.
But it wasn't about the size.
Size has nothing to do with it, at all!
In fact, I even feel like
I've been waiting for this!
Her white skin looking so transparent...
Her well-proportioned body line...
I was unaware that I felt defeated to see her
as a woman despite her being so lazy.
Plus, she's quite a beautiful maiden!
What's wrong, Sensei?
Her hair's so shiny too...
You're so amazing, Tokishikko-san!
I can't believe you've never fallen sick for once!
I'm kind of proud of it myself.
Huh... That's kind of surprising, even though
you seem to not care about your health.
All good.
Next one, please!
Okay, all good.
In conclusion...
I auscultated Maidena from the back.
Going to sit on the fence now?
I can't do it from the front...
What will you do, then?
She'll be suspicious of you now!
E-Err... Oh, right!
Rather than your lungs,
I'm more concerned about
the bruise on your hip.
My holy crest?
The holy crest is a seal given by Lord Phoenizask
to enable the use of white magic.
Sure, mine is different
from the other white sorcerers, but...
O-Okay.
Please check for any anomalies!
Uh, you don't have to do this
if you don't want to...
Sensei!
Right... Compared to the chest,
examining the hips would be easier...
Also, well...
When she can show her skin so easily like this,
it's a little unemotional,
or perhaps it's a strange kind of familiarity.
I'm not at all interested
in her baby-fine smooth skin,
nor in her buttocks, which are small...
...but contain a certain softness.
Huh?! Hey!
This doctor's hands are trembling!
I take it all back. I feel like
I could awaken to a new one...
Sensei! Please stay calm!
P-Please be nice to me...
Please open the front of your shirt.
The last one, huh.
Well, if it's Hitamuki...
I'm used to seeing her in various predicaments,
so I can't feel anything new from this.
What's wrong?
N-No...
Um...
I'd like to check for your heartbeat, so...
What's wrong, Hitamuki?
Why are you, out of all people,
the most embarrassed here?
Why are you undressing
in a slightly amorous way?!
I never thought I'd be wavering
so much with Hitamuki—
Her heart's practically racing!
What makes you so anxious, damn it?!
Stop moaning with the stethoscope on your chest!
I know you're sensitive, Hitamuki!
However, today's not the day for that!
A-All good...
Thank you, Doctor Murder!
The check-up is done!
Um...
I don't know why you did this,
but... I don't think this is right...
Kik-kun.
Wait...
How did she...
-------------------------
SNIFF
SNIFF, SNIFF.
I
I SMELL
THE
THE VIRGIN
KIKURU
She could tell by my smell!!
S-Sensei! Sensei, please snap out of it, Sensei!
H-He's dead?!
Immoral Guild.
~AOBA PLAINS ~
---------------------------------
(A STOPOVER BETWEEN MEBUKI CITY AND MEBUKI FOREST)
BLACK
You two don't even have
the basics to start with.
BLACK AND
BLACK AND WHITE
So I decided to divide you guys
into physical and magical teams,
and set up a training menu.
I see. So today makes the training
for the thin team, eh?
Not thin, magical.
I can't teach you to cast spells.
You two are going to do a fitness menu.
Fitness?
While Tokishikko is already beyond hope,
she tends to hide herself,
you're not really good
at physical exercices too, right, Maidena?
That's true, but...
Why are we doing this
with these members, out of all?
What, you'd rather train
with Hanabata and Hitamuki?
If I'm going to train, I want Hanabata to tutor me instead of Kikuru.
She's so strong, pretty,
and well-educated...
If I'm picking a coach, I want it to be her!
Just do it at
your own pace
Hang in there!
Comin' at ya with full power!
Sh-She's tall and has good style, too...
You're turning a blind eye
to her one flaw...
S-Sure, Hitamuki might be a troublemaker,
but I respect her pure heart, okay?
LET ME KNOW
IF YOU'RE TIRED!
I'LL PIGGYBACK YOU!
She's a dedicated one, that girl.
But you two... Well...
— GOOD —
When the human spirit and way of life...
— EVIL —
...are grouped as either "good" or "evil"...
I feel that you two belong in the "evil" group.
Evil, huh...
Ah, but...
Yeah, I get you.
A perfectly fitting phrase.
She really hates us, eh?
But I like you though, Maidena.
Wha?!
How could you say something
that embarrassing?!
So, which part of me do you like?
I like that you're seemingly cheeky,
but you're actually awkward,
whiny, tiny and worth teasing.
None of those words contain any praise!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
I hate that you always
look down on people like that!
Well, duh! I ain't scratching anyone's back
if they don't scratch mine!
I'm older than you, damn it!
Show some respect, kid!
I'll do that everyday
to anyone worth my respect!
But too bad! You have nothing
that warrants my respect!
Calm down.
You're barely done with your warm-up,
but you're already this heated up?
Owww...
Right...
At times like this, I suppose I'll show
that I'm still forgiving as the older one.
Wh-What?
Enough quarreling,
time to continue our stretching.
If we don't stretch our bodies,
we might get hurt.
Got you now!
Second round?!
Apologize now! If you don't, I won't let you go!
No way! What are you doing, you dumb?!
Hey, Tokishikko, cut it—
Cry and hang your head for this!
I'm on your back now!
If you don't say "I'm sorry for earlier, Miss"...
How dare you add a condition!
I'll take you to the city like this!
Let the public see your appalling appearance!
No!
How...
Mean of you...
You sure?
Wait—
We're going all the way to the city...
I don't have the stamina to do that...
Figures.
What the hell am I looking at here?!
Why are you guys already running out of spirit
before you even start training?!
I've worked up a good sweat.
Stop acting like you've accomplished something.
We haven't even started yet.
M-Master!
I'm tired! Let's go back already!
If you still have the energy to speak,
you're still good to go.
I'm already bad to go now...
Not to mention there are monsters here,
it's so dangerous...
The monsters in the plains are docile, so don't worry.
Speaking of which, there should be a way
to sneak inside the city if you look hard enough,
but the monsters in the forest
have never once done that, right?
The monsters are wary of humans, that's why.
As long as they have no trouble finding food
in the forest, it's unlikely for them to come out.
At least while they're outnumbered
from us reducing their number.
So I guess it's safe to leave Tokishikko here.
I thought she was focusing on running,
but she ran out of stamina and couldn't speak...
Wait...
All right, time for sit-ups.
Three sets of thirty reps.
One.
Don't recoil at the waist.
Raise it from no motion.
Two.
Keep your sides open and your back straight.
Don't drop your chin.
Three.
This is tough!
Wait, I did collapse back there, didn't I?!
Aren't we supposed to just wrap it up
when that happens?!
Don't be so naive.
I did my training from the age of ten,
when I was made to stand up even when I puked.
Now that's an extreme example...
In your case,
I want to bring you up to the average fitness of your age group, even if I have to push you a bit.
F-For me to possess some stamina...
is lacking of individuality!
Throw away that individuality.
Come on, three.
I can't do this!
We're only at two...
My hips are giving in...
We can't just do this three times in a row...
Stop putting it in an ambiguous way!
This means your strength and stamina
are far from even average.
You keep blabbering about average...
Stop comparing me to guys I don't know.
You should compare me to my yesterday self!
Your yesterday self...
It's no different from you today!
I'll be training on my own, then.
~ 1 HOUR LATER ~
I'm back alive!
Sit-ups, back-ups, push-ups,
squats, shuttle run...
I'm surprised I'm still alive.
I reduced the number of reps for you, though?
I did the full reps Kikuru gave me, okay!
I win, then!
We're not even competing here...
You have to learn to relax
or you'll fall over, okay?
Unfortunately, unlike you,
there's no such word as
"lazy" in my dictionary!
We did well today!
Let's wrap it up and call it a day!
We still have another training...
Huh, what a sad loser.
I've gone to great lengths for this...
So until I'm convinced myself...
I'll...
...keep doing this...
Thanks.
Well... looks like I've surprisingly
pushed you too hard.
My bad. I'm still not used to being a coach.
Hey, I just stumbled a bit.
Did you twist your ankle?
You okay?
Them's the breaks, then. I'll just do a menu
that I can do with only my upper body.
Well, you can just heal it with white magic...
I won't.
I brought this on myself
due to my carelessness.
I can't use my white magic so conveniently.
If I do that, I won't be able to do
anything with my own power.
But magic is your own power, no?
Not that anyone would blame you
for using that, but you're so elegant.
Anyway, let's head back for now.
I'll piggyback you.
Y-You can't!
Huh?
I-If you piggyback me,
our bodies will be close together...
And touching... stuff...
Kikuru will obviously think
of something beyond help!
Which and what will touch, mind you?
F
L
A
T
Maidena, you might be elegant,
but not your body.
Don't try to tell me that!
Sheesh, you're really a handful...
Come on.
What are you doing?
I'll piggyback you.
Don't force yourself.
I can walk on my own, so you don't have to.
You're fine with me giving you
a piggyback ride instead of him, aren't you?
You were moving around so much
earlier and I got drained quickly...
But if you stay put,
I can last until we reach the city.
You're not playing tricks on me again, are you?
O-Okay, then...
In team work, it's essential not only
to have individual competence,
but also to have a trusting relationship
with your fellow party members.
I thought that was an issue for them, too.
Huh? You can use a spell that strong?
I'm quite excellent
as a black sorceress myself, you know?
I've also been told
I'm the best of all time, though!
Sure, sure.
Maybe their compatibility
isn't as worrying as I might think.
Maidena...
Sorry... It's too tiring, after all...
My head hurts!
What were you thinking, falling backwards
while holding someone's legs?!
That scared the heck out of me!
Seriously, why did you have to
fall backwards?! You dummie!
Well... I was piggybacking you,
so my centre of gravity was behind you...
Sorry... So what now?
If I rest for ten minutes, I think we can cover
the same distance as we did now.
No way!
A snail's pace every ten minutes?!
C-Cure!
Magic is a convenient thing, eh?
Ouch! To be continued!
TO BE CONTINUE
Ijippari ni kakuzatou wo tokashitara
If you stubbornly dissolve the sugar cubes
Sunao no mahou
Magic of honesty
Doji ni wa chotto oome no shinamon
Clumsy and a little too much cinnamon
Yarisugite daddadubada
Too much daddadubada
Mata mebunryou no kimagure to yasashisa de
In addition, with the whims and gentleness of mebenryo
Himitsu no reshipi wo mou kakimidasanaide
Don't disturb the secret recipe anymore
Oh don’t call my name
Oh don't call my name
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Amai dake janai
Not just sweet
Mune no oku no tokimeki iroiro
Heart-pounding feelings deep in my chest Various things
Watashi dake no baransu wo
I have my own balance
Wakatte hoshikute
I want you to understand
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Karai dake ja iya
I don't like it
Mune no oku no tokimeki wa
just because it's spicy
Mochiron desho namida to koi no mariaaju...
Of course, if it's tears, it's a marriage of love
...Yappari wakaranaide!
…I don't know!
NEXT
NEXT EPISODE
KYOKA'S
KYOKA'S SECRET
MEAT
MEAT FEAST