When the extraordinary goes on this far,
it becomes the ordinary, huh.
We're witnessing her humiliation
with the same frequency as the monster's mind.
Tokishikko, stop the thing
with your Freeze Magic.
Tokishikko?
Help me...
I can't count her as part
of our strength again!
You damned monster!
How dare you humiliate the loser!
I'll crush you with my Frenzy!
Hanabata!
Wait, wait, wait! Don't use that!
Comin' at ya with full power!
RATIO'D
TO LOVE
Odoroki mo hentetsu mo nai
Even easy daily missions,
Iijii deirii misshon datte
That don’t involve surprises and unexpected,
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Urutora shiikuretto ruuto ga
If there was Some ultra secret route,
Sonzai shiteru to shitara kimi wa ittai
I wonder how you would break out
Dou susumu no?
through it?
Hitamuki ni hitasura ni
Even if, completely surrendering to it,
Tada ikkyo ichidou ii koto shitatte
I stubbornly did good deeds with every step,
Tanabota ni yokoku nashiteki
Unexpected luck is an unforeseen thing.
Furachi moodo ni enkaunto shitatte
Even if we was encounter in rough mode,
Shuuten wa dochira mo kitto onaji
The end point for both of us is definitely the same.
Yume no naka ja kasanari aeru futari
We were able to sneak into each other’s dreams,
Kyuuten Chokkou Konya
so we suddenly became honest.
Futoku na doa no kagi wo akete!
So open the door of immorality tonight!
Aa hotobashiru kodou ga
Ah, your gaze, dancing with a frantic heartbeat,
Samayou shisen kogashite haimawaru
Slides over my body and burns me.
Sono te de furete mukidashi no subete wo
Touch with your hand everything, which is bare in me.
Ima sugu
Pierce me
hone made
right now
tsuranuite
to the bones.
Coming up!
Mezameru sono mae ni
Before we wake up…
Before we wake up...
~MEBUKI FOREST~
I've basically worked solo the whole time,
LET'S
LET'S PLAY
LET'S PLAY TOGETHER
but you see...
I believed, at the very least,
that people could compensate...
for each other's shortcomings
by coming together.
Guess I was wrong.
My burden increases in proportion
to the increased number of people.
I mean, to be honest, I'm even beginning
to see you as my real enemies.
That's awful...
I-I'm a healer, so it's you guys'
job to fight the monsters!
Still, you need to defend
yourself at the very least.
Or else I'll have to focus
entirely on saving you.
I don't want to claim too much credit, but...
I, uh, do fight the monsters properly, okay?
If it's only the monsters you take down,
I won't have anything to say about it.
You see, I'd get so scared of fighting
the monsters, my legs would give in.
You're not that sensitive.
That's awful.
I'm sorry for always dragging you down...
I'll do better tomorrow!
Nope, you all will have a day off tomorrow.
Huh?! No way!
I'm still full of energy!
Hitamuki's full of bravery and tenacity!
Where's the "energy"?
This one's also for you,
who's been fighting for five days in a row.
You should be the one
who gets the most rest.
Kik-kun...
Right... You four should hang out
and play somewhere together tomorrow.
Play?
Indeed, I do wish to bond with you all as well.
Eh... but...
If you still want to work by all means...
Then as punishment for skipping out yesterday,
I'll force you to join me, Tokishikko.
Let's play together, girls!
How long has it been
since I last hung out with my friends?!
Don't say something
that will make me pity you.
I've proposed a day off for a good cause,
All right! We'll gather at the plaza in the afternoon!
Okay.
Roger.
but the one who's going to rest,
both physically and mentally,
Sure!
on this day off, is none other than me.
HITAMUKI
Hana-chan!
Hello, Hitamuki. Good afternoon.
Good afternoon, Hana-chan!
I was so looking forward to it
and arrived an hour early!
That's so you!
I actually wanted to wait here
from yesterday too!
If you look forward to it too much,
I'd be pressured...
That's a very cute dress you have, Hana-chan!
It suits you perfectly!
D-Does it? Thanks.
Anyway, that's quite a somewhat
open outfit you're wearing...
Where I come from,
everyone wore these for PE.
It's actually assigned by the school?!
This outfit is available at a reasonable price and,
above all, is easy to move in!
There's literally nothing
to prevent you from moving...
I have ten pieces each for during my days off,
when I'm my room, and for going out!
In fact, this is all I have in my wardrobe.
Let's go buy some clothes today!
We'll be shopping for clothes now?! I can't wait!
But you're not from this
Gurin Province, are you?
Nope!
I'm from the neighbouring Buru Province,
and I live by myself!
TAMUKI
Already on your own at such a young age...
You're really a strong girl, Hitamuki.
You're stronger than me, Hana-chan!
Wow... I sure don't want to
fit myself in this Boob Club.
Stop grouping people in a strange way.
Your outfit's so cute, Toki! It's so frilly!
Thank you. Yours is so lewd.
That's a fast ball...
Is it really that strange?
But I've got my name written on this shirt,
so it's fine even if I lose it!
I don't think it'll come back to you
if someone finds out it's yours.
Only Maidena's left now, right?
She's also a student
while working as a guard, right?
K-Kept you waiting, huh?
Mede-chan!
Do you get it now?!
It's a healthy gathering of girls together!
There's really nothing to worry about!
Looks like it.
But please, try not to let loose.
Please behave with moderation as the Angel.
Those student council
people finally let me go...
You said it's hard to get permission to go out
for private business, after all, right?
That's a Phoenizaskan for you, eh?
What a strong sense of virtue.
She's a 15 year old guard by special exception.
The school will want to treat her with caution.
Let's go, then.
Sure!
By the way, miss.
They called you "Angel" back there,
but what does it mean?
Can a girl genius get such
a second name from school?
That must be because
she's as cute as an angel!
I can understand!
Mede-chan is a maiden!
Geez, if you're here to just tease me,
I'm going home!
You look like an idiot, too!
You must be poking fun at me!
SHOCK
Calm down, miss.
We can't have you leave now.
We need you to be here
to balance things out.
Hang on. What kind of balance
are you trying to maintain here using me?
Here's the document you requested, Kikuru-kun.
Much appreciated, Enome-san.
There's something that's been bothering me...
Number of guard fatalities in the province
in the last month: 17 males and 9 females.
It's indiscreet for me to say "of course",
but women are still among the casualties, right?
Did something happen?
I felt strange about the way
the monsters fought against the girls.
In particular, their obsession with Hitamuki is bizarre,
and it's not even remotely murderous.
Err...
Simply put, it's lewd.
They only do lewd things to her.
This is just a view
from a human perspective, though,
but they lick and suck her...
They treat her as more like a meal
than a mate for reproduction.
Monsters live on mana, the magical power
contained in plants and living creatures.
They attack people in order to get mana
from their flesh and bodily fluids.
The fact that they are willing
to risk her resisting...
to get the mana while
keeping her alive means...
Her mana is finer than most,
and they don't want to end it
with a one-off exploit.
That must be it.
But is there such a thing as good
or bad quality mana?
But looking back on how they did her,
that could be true...
Still, that doesn't mean I should be optimistic
that there is no risk of death, though.
I'm sorry.
But for what it's worth, you're actually worried
about the new girls, aren't you?
I don't like socialising,
but I'm still looking for connections,
and I'm still thinking about even during
the weekends when I say I'm quitting my job...
I'm contradicting myself, aren't I?
It's not uncommon for people
to behave differently than they think.
Because that doesn't go against your roots.
But still...
If I half-ass this,
Tokishikko will start calling me the "Quitter Scammer"
when I say I want to quit every time.
What are you worrying about, I wonder?
My mouth's melting!
I'd say it's pretty good.
Do you often visit this place, Hana-chan?
Yeah, I've always come here with Tokishikko.
We've been talking about cakes the whole time.
When a group of girls meet up like this,
we must absolutely talk about it!
It?
What kind?
Lo-ve-sto-ry.
I want to know about your love lives.
Love lives... I don't have such experience.
You know how strict my family is, don't you?
I also have some persistent eyes on me today.
Me too! There's no way a devout Phoenizaskan
like me would date someone!
My days were always filled with training, too...
I'm also basically a shut-in,
so I'm in the same boat!
Then why did you bring it up, anyway?
------------
FIN
Our youth is somewhat flavourless, eh...
We can't laugh at Master trying to retire
for want of a girlfriend like this.
He's quitting?!
MASTER
Who knows?
When he keeps delaying it,
he might turn into a "Quitter Scammer".
He might as well date one of us here, right?
Huh?! What are you—
Hello, Master?
Hey, I've got a question.
If you were to date one of us,
who's it going to be?
It's Enome-san.
She's not on the list.
------------
FIN
Well, I don't think we can win against her.
Huh? Wait, what?
Why did you suddenly say my name?
It's a magic spell that can silence many women.
Yes!
Thank you for today, everyone!
See you at the guild!
Bye-Bye.
The sun went down in a flash!
It was so much fun hanging out with everyone!
Maybe we should ask Key
to join too next time...
I smell Kik-kun around here!
Kik-kun.
I'm sorry!
Just get off me already...!
I've always thought about this,
but she's way too sensitive!
But... I've never been this close to her before...
She smells so damn nice!
She feels so soft too!
And what thick thighs she has.
It smells of flowers, fruits, and sun from her,
which is different from soap...
A calming scent and warmth,
as if I were surrounded by nature...
Wait, that's not it!
I'm surrounded by natural flesh,
not nature itself!
This is bad! I'm starting to feel funny!
Is this her mana's doing too?!
You're always carrying a knife
with you, I see...
That's right! Knife!
It's dangerous,
so don't move around too much!
I beg you! Please stay still!
K-Kik-kun, stop screaming...
I'll move you now.
I'm sorry...
Hey, I know exactly what's on your minds.
See you next time in court.
Their faith in me: zero.
I should've joined them
for the bonding session.
Immoral Guild.
YOU
YOU'RE
YOU'RE MY
YOU'RE MY FIRST
Sorry for suddenly asking you
to stand in for the reception.
Oh, don't worry about it.
Have a safe trip!
After Kikuru-kun told me about the monsters,
I've decided to investigate about them.
~MEBUKI FOREST~
There's no telling what could happen now...
Kik-kun, can Enome-san be allowed
into the danger zone?
As long as she has the permit
and a guard with her, she can.
I occasionally ask Kikuru-kun
to escort me during ecological surveys.
I didn't know that!
I can only use simple,
copyright-free defensive magic, so...
Your job today is to lead us away
from the stronger monsters and fight the weaker ones.
I'll do my best with dedication!
We've already encountered
most of the monsters in this forest,
so you can tell their smell, right?
Yes!
We've encountered a lot of monsters!
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
---------------
-----------------
ZIPPYRABBIT                                                                                                                      SLIME
------------------
----------------
BEARLION                                                 MADHOG                                                    ROOTCAT
A lot... of monsters...
THE TASTE OF DEFEAT BROUGHT BACK ALONG WITH THE SMELL
Just what kind of hideous experiences
has she had so far...?
Hey, about today's investigation...
We're going to investigate
the monsters' naughty behaviour, aren't we?
How do we do that...?
It's simple.
We can just present Hitamuki to them.
That's so outrageous!
Please, don't get the wrong idea.
We're not trying to tie her up
and throw her out there as a bait.
She always fights seriously, loses,
and gets teased by the monsters.
Wha—?!
We're just showing you
how we usually do things.
Don't recount such a horrible tragedy
in such a nonchalant way!
So Hitamuki's not much of a help to you?
If I were to choose a partner
out of those four new girls,
she's actually sometimes
the best match for me.
Really?
I'm the main attacker,
so I don't need more firepower.
I'm mainly a long-range attacker and rarely
get wounded, so I don't rely on a healer.
However, I direly need recon,
and I can't copy her for that skill.
A hunter and his hound, so to speak.
------------
HUNTER
HOUND
Woof!
I can't really feel delighted hearing that...
And while she may seem soft in the head,
she's always alert to her surroundings.
She's also got some stamina,
and never complains.
If she was really useless,
I would've given up on her long ago.
I see. That's great, then.
Enome-san, Kik-kun!
There might be a rootcat over there, so be ca—
Hitamuki-kun?!
While she's alert to her surroundings,
she's always careless with herself.
And that one point is always fatal.
I see...
Was this dug by a monster?
Kik-kun, something's come this way!
But I can't smell it!
Hitamuki, get out of there!
A snake?!
---------------------------------------
A HUMILISNAKE
HAS APPEARED!
So this is a hole that a humilisnake dug?
She can't smell it if it's underground.
Don't panic! It's not venomous!
Then I'll just endure and keep on
choking it even if it bites me!
Though it's not venomous,
it's got two heads!
Wait, what?!
Don't go in there!
It's creeping around my body
with its silky skin...
What do you think, Enome-san?
Isn't the monster acting strange?
Huh?! How are you staying calm?!
K-Kikuru-kun! We need to help her!
But this is what we're about to investigate.
We already know that the monsters
behave in a peculiar way!
Investigation's over!
Roger. Please stay where you are, Enome-san.
Another one?!
Kiku—
If I call him back here,
he won't be able to rescue Hitamuki...
A humilisnake attacks
by wrapping itself around its prey.
I'll be on the defensive
and buy some time!
Defuze!
She's chanting a spell?!
Coins?!
Please accept this.
Put it away!
Hey... Why...?!
I only have a tiny amount
of magic power in me...
But, come to think of it,
Hitamuki's not a sorcerer, too...
Being bound and stripped naked...
Is this hideous experience
a daily thing for you...?
I'm sorry for not noticing this...
You're my first acquaintance
that they've ever stripped naked!
I thought I was getting used to
most of the shenanigans,
but her being stripped naked still scares me!
Not to mention,
it has to be Enome-san's naked body!
I don't know where to look!
Ki-Kikuru-kun...
Yes?!
Can I say something selfish?
Go ahead!
Don't just stand there,
help me out!
Okay...
U-Um...
I might touch your skin
as I peel this off of you...
Don't worry about it.
Because I know you're sincere.
I'm the guy who never took his eyes
off your chest for a second, though...
E-Excuse me, then.
So soft!
The moist, sweaty breasts suckle
in the palms of my hands,
and I can feel the sensations all
the way down to my fingertips.
An elegant moan that leaks out
faintly and is stifled...
The sexiness and scent of an adult
messes with my reason...
What am I, a poet?!
Why did I use the diction
that I'd never thought of before?!
But, yeah...
The strongest impression right now is that...
It's so different from a slime!
Kikuru-kun, why are you crying?
I meant to take care of myself
as to not cause your any trouble...
But thank you.
I appreciate it—
I mean, don't worry about it.
Despite all that, I'm not hurt at all.
It really didn't intend to attack me after all...
Though, I feel like I've lost something precious...
Wait, what about Hitamuki?!
That's Hitamuki for you.
When someone in the east
get stripped naked, so do you.
You're also not lagging behind
in this aspect as the other one.
Hey, why didn't you call for help?
You should save Enome-san first...
...or else I couldn't call for your help...
Good grief. I forgot you're that kind of person.
Now, Hitamuki.
There's just one problem
with rescuing you now.
Should I touch your skin,
you won't sue me for se—
I won't!
PUSH FORWARD
RETURN TO CITY
~MEBUKI FOREST~
Enome-san.
You're leaving
the guild's reception to Esyne?
Esyne-san?
Oh, you're back!
Esyne-chan, thank you for looking
after the guild for me.
All went well today!
Huh? Did you change you shirt?
Y-Yeah... I did...
What a cute girl.
Mama, how was your work today?
Mama... Mother?!
Let me introduce you to her, Hitamuki-chan.
ENOME'S DAUGHTER
-------------
ESYNE
She's my daughter, Esyne.
Nice to meet you!
How old are you, Enome-san?
31.
Kikuru, it's been a week! I miss you!
Glad to see you in high spirit as always.
Knowing about Enome-san's age,
and the fact that she has a child...
I'm so surprised by all this!
Our dad hasn't passed away yet,
so I have to struggle with my mama...
W-Well, yeah, he's still around,
but it's not like we're divorced, too, just in case...
That all-year-round cheating man
is as good as gone!
I don't even know his face!
You sound like a family
with some problems, I see...
But the main problem now is
that although I couldn't help it,
I've been fondling a married woman's body
until just now, in her husband's absence.
What a guilty pleasure I'm feeling today...
I feel so...
Immoral.
To. Be. Continued!
TO BE CONTINUE
Ijippari ni kakuzatou wo tokashitara
If you stubbornly dissolve the sugar cubes
Sunao no mahou
Magic of honesty
Doji ni wa chotto oome no shinamon
Clumsy and a little too much cinnamon
Yarisugite daddadubada
Too much daddadubada
Mata mebunryou no kimagure to yasashisa de
In addition, with the whims and gentleness of mebenryo
Himitsu no reshipi wo mou kakimidasanaide
Don't disturb the secret recipe anymore
Oh don’t call my name
Oh don't call my name
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Amai dake janai
Not just sweet
Mune no oku no tokimeki iroiro
Heart-pounding feelings deep in my chest Various things
Watashi dake no baransu wo
I have my own balance
Wakatte hoshikute
I want you to understand
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Karai dake ja iya
I don't like it
Mune no oku no tokimeki wa
just because it's spicy
Mochiron desho namida to koi no mariaaju...
Of course, if it's tears, it's a marriage of love
...Yappari wakaranaide!
…I don't know!
I-It's been 12 years since my last time,
so I'm not used to it anymore...
I-I didn't moan too much back there, did it?
NEXT
NEXT EPISODE
DOCTOR
DOCTOR MURDER
BLACK
BLACK AND
BLACK AND WHITE