Master, we're at the meeting point.
Fran-chan!
Good morning! Did you sleep well?
Did you have a dream about me?
Yes. It was a nightmare.
That kinda hurts.
Gather around, everyone.
This investigation of the spider's nest
will also serve as a promotion test
for two E-rank parties.
-------------------
Name: Cruz Luzel
Age: 28 years old
Species: Human
-----
Class: Duelist
Level: 33
---------------------------------
HP: 206
MP: 175
STR: 113
AGI: 178
Skills: Malicious Sense 3, Covert 2
Avoidance 5, Court Etiquette 2
Sense Presence 4, Sword Art 4
Sword Mystery 6, Self-defense 4
Command 2, Blink 7
Cold Resistance 4, Poison Resistance 5
Trap Sense 2, Spirit Manipulation
Title: The Righteous
My name is Cruise Riouselle.
I am the leader of the Azure Guardians, a C-rank party.
Azure Guardians
A party led by a handsome blonde swordsman.
I, along with my party members,
Name: Cruz Rig
Species: Human
Class:  Water Mage
--------------
Name: Eizelle
Species: Human
Class:  Warrior
Rig and Eizelle,
will oversee this operation
and act as examiners.
I look forward to working with you all.
Now, please introduce yourselves.
My name's Krad.
----------
Name: Krad
Age: 23 years old
Species: Human
Class: Warrior
Level: 20
---------------------
HP: 27
MP: 68
STR: 67
AGI: 49
Skills: Transportation 2, Light 4
----
Detection: 3
Hunger Resistance 3
Spear Arts 1, Spear Mystery 4
Intimidation 3, Climbing 3
Spirit Manipulation
I am the leader
Dragon's Roar
of the Dragon's Roar, an E-rank party.
-------------------------
Name: Victor
--------------------
Name: Bart
------------------------
Name: Gennel
We'll sweep through this test.
We came prepared!
That's all from us.
My name's Phreon.
-----
Name: Phreon
Age: 49 years old
-----
Species: Wood Elf
Class: Elementalist
Level: 27
--------------------
HP: 71
MP: 233
STR: 36
AGI: 66
Skills: Archery 1, Collecting 2, Cultivation 4
Evil Perception 3, Tree Magic 3
Plant Knowledge 7, Drowsiness Resistance 3
Spirit Magic 5, Earth Magic 3
Water Magic 3, Herbal Knowledge 4
Protection of Spirits, Magic Manipulation
Children of the Forest
-------------------
Wood Elf
Elementalist
A wood elf elementalist like the guild master.
But he looks rather plain.
Forest Eyes
I'm the leader of the E-rank party, Forest Eyes.
The members of his party look ordinary too.
My turn.
I'm Amanda. Nice to meet you.
I knew it! That person is Amanda!
No way…
Why would an A-rank adventurer join this quest?
This is a D-rank quest, isn't it?
It's no wonder the people are talking…
No one would perceive her
to be here because of Fran.
All that's left is you, young lady.
I'm Fran.
Rank D.
I like curry.
Nice to meet you.
I don't think they know what curry is…
So it's you, after all.
The one who fawned over the guild master
to get promoted by him…
The self-proclaimed D-rank brat!
Episode 9
The A-Rank Adventurer Is A Monster
Here come the ones
trying to pick a fight with us…
I don't get you two at all.
The A-rank old lady
who just came here to amuse herself,
and the favorite brat
of that pedo guild master.
Would you care to repeat that?
What did you just say?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry! I'm very sorry…
She's fast.
Help…
She came up right behind him in a flash.
I think I see a flower field… What's this?
Huh? Have I gone to the other side?
Are you all right, Krad-san?
It's one thing for Amanda…
But I'll never acknowledge someone
who uses their connections to climb the ranks!
I did no such thing.
Huh?
Little brats like you
should go back to their mothers!
My mother is dead.
Amanda-san... is only here as an observer.
If she does involve herself,
she'll clear the quest in the blink of an eye,
and there will be no test whatsoever.
Now, I will begin the briefing.
Our objective is to investigate the dungeon
under the Alessa guild's jurisdiction,
the spider's nest,
retrieve the crystals
generated by the dungeon core,
and eliminate all monsters
we encounter in our path.
They're just F-rank monsters, right?
We might just accidentally wipe them out.
The dungeon absorbs the powers of the monsters to sustain itself.
So avoid killing all of them.
But this is a dungeon with six floors.
It won't be as easy as you think.
So caution is recommended.
Without further ado,
let us set out for our destination.
I heard this from Garrus yesterday.
He said, a dungeon without a dungeon master
will use its core to generate
monsters and crystals.
The guild  periodically sends adventurers
to the dungeon to retrieve these resources.
It's a source of profit, so other countries also have their eyes on this.
What is he doing?
Maybe he wanted to take a dip.
Shut up, you old hag!
Krad-san!
Damn you!
We made it at last.
It's because you guys kept fooling around
that we arrived much later than scheduled.
Tch.
I didn't do anything.
We'll head into the dungeon
early in the morning tomorrow.
I take it that everyone
brought their sleeping equipment and food?
As for the vigil,
Fran-san, you're on the first watch.
G-Got it.
Followed by the Azure Guardians.
Then, the Dragon Roar.
And finally, the Forest Eyes.
What about mighty Miss A-rank?
Keeping vigil is part of the test too.
If we let Amanda-san take part,
then it wouldn't be a test.
So sorry.
What is it?
Can a little brat who used her connections
to get promoted actually keep watch?
Yes.
And I didn't get promoted
because of my connections.
In that case,
prove it!
Show me if you really have
what it takes to stay in rank D!
Battle me!
Don't mind him, Fran.
It would be best not to
get involved in any trouble.
I knew it!
Are you actually scared
even with that huge sword on your back?
Or is that a toy sword just for show?
If that's true, you might as well throw that useless sword away!
I can't pretend I didn't hear that.
Fine.
I'll battle you.
Fran, are you serious about fighting him?
He mocked Master. I won't let that pass.
A practice battle?
This should be interesting.
No one's stopping this, huh?
Krad-san!
Teach her a lesson!
Of course I will.
There's no way that
brat is actually eligible for rank D.
I'll tear your facade into shreds!
Those who rely on connections
to get promoted are the worst, aren't they?
So whenever I come across someone like that…
The dragon inside me screams!
There it is! Krad-san's roar!
So cool!
I'm in awe!
I used to enjoy getting hyped up like this too…
Let's set up wind and earth barriers
so we can detect the presence
of any monsters, just in case.
You're on watch duty right now, after all.
Okay.
Wind of the sky, guide us and protect us.
Root of the forest, lend us
the perception of the earth and alert us.
What?
Wind Zone!
Earth Zone!
What? Two elements?
Even for a sword mage, that's impressive.
What did you do?
Keeping watch.
Huh?
Whatever.
Bring it on.
A sword, huh?
I've never lost against anyone
of the same rank with this spear.
A sword is no match
for a spear regarding the range.
I'll teach this shameless brat a lesson
and show her that my spear
is far superior to her sword!
Spear Technique!
The spearhead instantly drew back to his hands!
There it is! Krad-san's ultimate skill!
Double Spear!
What? She dodged both strikes!
It was probably just luck.
Spear Technique! Power Swing!
Dang it!
Double Spear!
You're short of breath.
Behold! The power of my super sword!
Be amazed!
Fran, I don't think you defeated him
with the sword per se…
That hurt…
The Back of Sword Strike!
Actually, you're hitting him with the ridge, Fran.
Krad-san!
That'll make them think twice
about challenging you.
That was fun.
That was an excellent battle, Fran-chan.
How about a practice battle with me too?
With you…
How about a mock duel with me too?
It's boring doing nothing all day.
My shoulders are getting stiff.
Okay.
On one condition.
If I win, please stop bothering me.
My, my! Aren't you confident?
Very well. If I win…
You shall call me "Mama".
T-Then… I simply can't lose!
Fran, I think you're digging
your own grave here…
She is an A-rank, after all…
Hey, hey, Looks like that little girl is going to fight Amanda-san next.
Master, don't assist me.
Fran?
I want to fight with my own strength
and see how I fare against an A-rank.
All right. Do your best, then!
Have you prepared yourself, Fran-chan?
A whip…
Not quite common, right?
Magic Whip of Celestial Dragon Beard.
Name:
----------------------
Magic Whip of Celestial
Dragon Beard
---------------------
Attack: 1030
Mana: 1800
---------------------
Durability: 1000
Mana Conductivity: A
Skills: Weight Alternation
------
Elastic
This whip and I are old friends.
OK, now. I shall start attacking.
Let's start with something easy.
Take this!
And this!
Not bad.
When blocked by a sword,
the whip would tangle it.
If Fran got careless,  Amanda might simply
pull the sword out from her hands.
Did Fran rely on her survival instincts
to dodge her attacks within seconds?
Good call, Fran! Well done!
I wonder how...
you'll handle this?
Krad-san!
That brat…
Look!
That little girl is something!
What?!
She used the handle!
That was close.
You might actually get a hit in.
I can't find a single opening to break through!
Now, then,
I think it's time for me to
get a little more serious.
Mana flow!
Whip Technique.
Mizuchi Strike!
So she can control the movements
of the whip with her mana flow.
What's with those crazy movements of that whip!?
It's as if that thing's alive and after its prey!
You're incredible, Fran-chan!
This is my one-hit-KO move!
It has been a long time
since someone was able to dodge this!
Oh, no!
The power of the whip increased significantly
after it was infused with mana.
It'll be bad for us if we drag this out.
I know.
Wind Magic. Wind Foot.
A wind magic-based skill
that boosts your speed, I see.
Parallel Thought!
Fran is using Parallel Thought?
Is she planning to cast
different spells simultaneously?
Unleash the flames of
the red lotus brighter than fire,
and burn everything it touches!
This has been most delightful, Fran-chan!
But it'll be over with this.
Mizuchi Strike!
She's still dashing forward!
Air Burst!
You used a blast of compressed air
to accelerate your speed even further!
There isn't enough time
for her to pull her whip back.
Amanda is now defenseless!
Wind Shield.
I'm not finished yet…
The spell she cast with Parallel Thought…
Flare Blast!
Oh, my…
What…? Amanda-san!
It can't be!
An A-rank adventurer was…
What the hell was that battle?
You're magnificent, Fran-chan!
I didn't expect you to do that!
What? No damage?
Spirit's Affection.
No way…
I'm not done yet…
Fran-chan!
I'm sorry! Forgive me!
I overdid it…
You did land the hit.
But my unique skill: Spirit's Affection,
was activated by itself.
------------------
Unique Skill: Spirit's Affection
Render an attack up to a certain
------------------
Power level ineffective once.
-----------------------
Counldown: 24 hours.
A skill that can render an attack
completely null? That's too cunning!
They're both monsters…
Rig, use your water magic
to extinguish the flames!
Everyone else as well. Put out the fire!
That said, it's not good to use fire magic
in a place surrounded by trees.
I'll need to have Fran apologize
to everyone later.
You forced yourself to use Parallel Thought
that you dislike
just to get Amanda to stop playing around and fight you seriously.
Besides Whip Technique and Wind Magic,
you even forced her unique skill to activate.
I suppose you could say
you've made your telling response.
Fran…
My dear Fran…
For the future of the Black Cats
and yourself,
you must work hard, Fran…
What? Huh? Mama...
Oh, you're awake.
Amanda?
You've been unconscious
for nearly two hours.
Master...
It's all right. You should rest a little more.
Cruise and the others
will keep watch in your stead.
But…
Your wounds have been healed,
but mentally, you're still fatigued.
You're still a child.
You should act spoiled
with adults every now and then.
You're really strong, Amanda.
You're not half bad yourself.
But I fainted… It's my defeat…
How honest.
Do you still remember our agreement?
Ah, that's right!
Now, let's hear you call me "Mama", Fran-chan.
Ma…
Fran wants to keep her end of the deal,
but she can't seem to bring herself to say it.
Ma…
I went a little too far with my teasing.
I know
your mother is still with you in your heart.
I don't expect you to trust me right away,
but I'll always be here for you.
You can rely on me.
I've used Truth of Falsehood
to check several times.
Not a word she said to Fran is insincere.
She smells nice…
So this is the Guardian of Children…
I think I might be a little jealous.
The best thing that ever happened to me
Was my unforgettable first meeting with you
I'm sorry for using fire magic around a forest.
ture
na
ni
ka
waru
Until then, my future had looked so grim
Well... it's all right.
But deep down, I always knew
We didn't expect the battle
to get that intense, either.
Those awful days that I lived through—
So we're responsible as well.
Those heavy chains that weighed me down
Thank you for keeping watch for me too.
Are now but a distant memory
Not at all. Don't mention it.
You're hurt…
Because I have you in my hands
Actually, after watching that battle,
everyone was all fired up,
You gave me a reason to live
and we challenged Amanda-san too.
The strength to face forward—
But no one managed to last as long as you did.
Courage to take the scary way
Thanks to this, everyone knows
just what you're capable of now.
With you in my hands, I can...
We'll be counting on you
in the dungeon investigation.
Face
up!
Stro
ng
ly!
Face up strongly!
goku
March straight on forward into the depths of Hell
I'll do my best!
As you know,
the spider's nest dungeon is
under the jurisdiction of the Alessa Guild.
Every last one of our scars
Proves we fought to the bitter end
So
chan
ging
the
world
So let's change the world!
Only the executives of the guild
razu
My tears that shine as brightly as your blade
or adventurers holding a permit
may enter this dungeon.
Now, let's go.
Are proof of the happiness we earned!
Fran, let's take care of this
and get the permit to take on the next dungeon!
Next Time
The Trap of the Trap Spiders