Kikuru!
Help me, Master!
Don't look at me, senpai!
Uh... Master!
Kik-kun...
Is this really the youth I want?
Odoroki mo hentetsu mo nai
Even easy daily missions,
Iijii deirii misshon datte
That don’t involve surprises and unexpected,
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Dokidoki no ura ibe zenkai
Are revealed to us by events,
exciting from the inside out.
Urutora shiikuretto ruuto ga
If there was Some ultra secret route,
Sonzai shiteru to shitara kimi wa ittai
I wonder how you would break out
Dou susumu no?
through it?
Hitamuki ni hitasura ni
Even if, completely surrendering to it,
Tada ikkyo ichidou ii koto shitatte
I stubbornly did good deeds with every step,
Tanabota ni yokoku nashiteki
Unexpected luck is an unforeseen thing.
Furachi moodo ni enkaunto shitatte
Even if we was encounter in rough mode,
Shuuten wa dochira mo kitto onaji
The end point for both of us is definitely the same.
Yume no naka ja kasanari aeru futari
We were able to sneak into each other’s dreams,
Kyuuten Chokkou Konya
so we suddenly became honest.
Futoku na doa no kagi wo akete!
So open the door of immorality tonight!
Aa hotobashiru kodou ga
Ah, your gaze, dancing with a frantic heartbeat,
Samayou shisen kogashite haimawaru
Slides over my body and burns me.
Sono te de furete mukidashi no subete wo
Touch with your hand everything, which is bare in me.
Ima sugu
Pierce me
hone made
right now
tsuranuite
to the bones.
Coming up!
Mezameru sono mae ni
Before we wake up…
Before we wake up...
I'LL
I'LL DO
I'LL DO MY
I'LL DO MY BEST
I'LL DO MY BEST WITH
I'LL DO MY BEST WITH DEDICATION!
You want to quit your job?
Why so sudden?
GUILD OFFICER
ENOME
You can talk to me
if there's something troubling you...
HUNTSMAN
KIKURU MADAN
I learned of a classmate's marriage
in a New Year's greeting card
HAPPY NEW YEAR
We have just gotten
married and from
now on we will try
our best to create
a happy family.
I received at the beginning of the year...
Oh, that's certainly worth celebrating!
But is that the reason?
I'm only 20,
and I know marriage
is still a long way off for me,
but then I realised this...
That I've never...
...had a relationship
with someone in the first place.
All I'd been doing since I was a kid in order
to obtain the skills to defeat monster...
...was always training and training
until I reached eighteen.
Since I got the job as a hunter, I've been
constantly killing monsters for practice...
My teenage years were anything but glamorous!
I've heard that the guys who joined
the Hunter Club at my university...
...are hunting for females
day and night for some reason.
I don't think that's where you
should compare yourself to them!
But you've only been with us for two years,
so you can't get severance pay, you know?
You've worked hard so far,
so just try to...
I mean, I've worked my butt to earn so much cash,
yet I never had the time to use it.
This may put you off a bit,
but I've got more cash other than
for hunting party search.
That's so creepy...
Anyway, we've got a pretty cute new recruit
coming to the guild! What do you think?
You're saying it as if you're
attracting people to a cabaret...
Hello, Laia-san and Leia-san!
Hello, Enome-san!
Speak of the devil.
Hello, Hitamuki-chan!
So she's the new recruit?
MARTIAL ARTIST
HITAMU KYAN
Nice to meet you!
I'm Hitamu Kyan, a martial artist!
Please call me Hitamuki!
Name's Kikuru.
A martial artist... I've heard of that job,
but this is the first time I've seen one in person.
Right, so today will be Hitamuki-chan's first sortie.
Kikuru-kun. How about completing
a quest together with her?
Together?
Right... If you say so, then...
I'll do my best with dedication!
HITAMU KYAN HAS JOINED YOUR PARTY!
He's staring at the girl so intensely...
Could she be his type?
Depending on her ability,
I wouldn't mind letting her take over my place.
Kikuru-kun?!
~MEBUKI FOREST~
Kikuru-kun...
Drop the formalities. Calling me Mister
would be too long and affect the battle.
But I can't just...
Anyway, I see you're a veteran
in hunting monster, right, Kik-kun?
Kik-kun?
I've only landed this gig for two years.
Are you a high school graduate?
Yes! I'm 18!
You're still in your youthful days, aren't you?
Don't you feel empty doing bloody work...
...like this?!
YOUTHFUL DAYS
BLOODY WORK
DON'T YOU FEEL EMPTY?
Th-This is bad... I'm about to be defeated
by myself even before an actual battle...
I don't feel empty at all!
And you shouldn't too, considering you've
been of help to so many people so far!
Also, I feel happy and proud that
I'm about to continue your job as well!
You're too bright...
There's a monster over there!
SLIMES HAVE APPEARED!
CHANCE FOR A PREEMPTIVE STRIKE!
We're pretty far away,
but she can detect them already?
So this is a human beast's ability, huh?
Where'd she go?!
Heya! Nice to meet you!
What are you doing, miss?!
Martial arts begin and end with a bow!
Stop indulging youself and look ahead!
I told you!
Owwie...
It's so squishy, my fists won't do a thing...
You... can't...
If you... touch me there...
Noooo!
What the hell...
Hitamuki, slimes are the lowest
of the lowest tier of monsters, you know?
Uhh... I'd love to get rid
of those slimes for you,
but I'll have to touch your body for that.
So you're not going to sue me
for sexual harassment, right?
I'm not! I won't even think about it!
Also, no one would seriously believe
in a stumpy person like me...
...even if I caused a commotion...
I believe in you. You're underestimating
your potential too much.
Here I go...
P-Please do...
M-My bad! It wasn't on purpose!
It feels so elastic and chilly like a slime...
And it also fits like a slime... Is this...
Um... You're touching a slime,
for your information...
I can't even tell!
Sorry... for troubling you...
A slime's body is hard
to penetrate with blunt attacks,
but its core is fragile
and can be destroyed for an easy kill.
So you can finish it off with a piercing attack.
You're not carrying any weapons with you?
Nope!
A martial artist's whole body is their weapon,
so I shall protect everything with my own body!
You can't even protect yourself
with your own body...
There's a monster up ahead!
Only her recon ability is excellent, huh...
You've defeated a lot of monsters,
but you're still so careful, huh?
I can defeat a lot of monsters
because I'm careful.
It would be reckless to confront a large
monster head-on, let alone a small fry.
I've only ever done
head-to-head sparring in the dojo...
You should unlearn that
fighting style real quick.
You should fight like me,
luring the monsters into a trap,
stabbing them from the back,
and shooting them from a distance.
An ambush?!
I can't do such an unfair thing...
Feels like emotional damage alone
is already enough to knock me out today...
A BEARLION HAS APPEARED!
CHANCE FOR A PREEMPTIVE STRIKE!
A bearlion?
I'll go for the first strike.
You'll be the diversion in case I miss.
Yes! I'll do my best with dedication!
It spotted me!
My party member is the worst enemy!
I'll take responsibility and hold it off!
Get out of here, Kik-kun!
Idiot! Don't!
Don't worry! My Beast Karate
won't lose to that monster!
What are you charging in for?!
That was so baseless!
I... wanted to be of help to you...
My body moved on my own
before I could think...
Even though... I was actually so scared...
This girl...
She's so different from me fundamentally!
KIKURU
TACTICS  BASED ON
THE SITUATION
ALWAYS PREPARES
FOR AN AMBUSH
LOGICAL
HITAMUKI
DEVOTED TO BARE
FISTFIGHTS
FAIR AND SQUARE
IMPULSIVE
Mister Bear...
Did you just let out a pheromone
that could make monster go in heat?!
Normally, you'd be chopped meat!
Well, you've proved yourself a nice
bait for that thing, though...
PUSH FORWARD
RETURN TO CITY
Doing this gig alone...
...would've been much easier...
~MEBUKI CITY~
You've eliminated two slimes
and one bearlion on your first quest!
Way to go, Hitamuki-chan!
Yeah, I'd say she did
a fair job for her first gig.
Come on, you should look happier, Hitamuki.
I'm sorry...
What happened?
Enome-san.
Actually,
I have decided to quit my current job
and set my course for an unknown campus life.
You've already thought that far...?
But...
Unless I could find a proper successor first...
I let them outside!
The city would possibly perish if I quit.
Hitamuki.
Are all martial artists like you?
My mentor always said I was
"pure, for better or worse."
I see I'm not the only one
having trouble with you.
Hey, Kikuru-kun.
Hitamuki-chan's still a novice,
so please take the long view of her.
Even if you say so...
Oh, right! I have good news for you!
Good news?
Surprise! Looks like another
new recruit girl is joining your party!
Aren't you getting
the wrong idea about me?!
Also,
she's as cute as Hitamuki-chan!
Stop treating me like one of those
"uncontrollable date seekers"!
I-I can't be cute...
You're exaggerating...
Stop blushing every time, will you?
Come in, Maidena-chan!
She's here already?!
It's kind of awkward meeting her face-to-face
after she's heard about this exchange!
WHITE SORCERESS
MAIDENA ANGERS
Hello, I'm a white sorceress,
Maidena.
What do I do with this atmosphere...?
She's smaller than Hitamuki, too.
Can she even fight?
You're so cute!
Maidena-chan's still a novice too,
so please look after her.
Me again?!
Name's Hitamuki!
H-Hello...
You're our reliable ace, after all!
Raising a successor...
Would that be
the shortest path to retiring...?
I am a devout Phoenizaskan.
So, I can't work with a lustful guy who
only wants a "date with a girl" like you.
And I don't want to!
Wait! You're getting
the wrong idea about earlier.
Also, calm down.
You look like a kid,
so I don't feel anything about you.
FLAT
You're the worst!
B-But why...
I think you should start from
getting used to handling girls first...
Immoral Guild!
GOBUZAKI HIGH CULTURAL FESTIVAL
A youthful event for students,
THE
THE WORLD
THE WORLD THE
THE WORLD THE GIRL
THE WORLD THE GIRL DOESN'T
THE WORLD THE GIRL DOESN'T KNOW
THE WORLD THE GIRL DOESN'T KNOW OF
the cultural festival.
While the lovers, or those
who were in a similar relationship,
were amiably enjoying the entertainment...
I was guarding the premises all day long.
You don't need a Mage Masher...
A dagger that can cause people
to keep silent when hit.
Very suitable to sever people connection
...in a cultural festival, do you?
I wanted to silence those
idiot couples flirting with each other!
Thank you so much!
TEACHER
TRUE OPINION
With you being here,
we can cut down the security cost—
It's so reassuring!
FACADE
I can mostly hear your true opinion, sir.
I've wasted my one and only youth on things
that were always about helping others...
But I can still make it, as long as I can
raise a successor and retire...
To prepare for next year's
college entrance examinations...
Well, if I call in a handful of skilled people,
I can save myself the trouble of training them.
Sorry if I'm a handful novice.
Kik-kun! Looking forward to
another good hunting today!
Yeah...
You have quite a festive party now, Kikuru-kun!
I mean, they're just kids...
Yeah, you're right.
I find them charming.
You pervert!
I can't really dig her.
You're about to clear a quest now,
but will you be okay?
I'll do my best to bring them
closer to each other!
Anxiety!
MAIDENA HAS JOINED YOUR PARTY
Huh? Where's Kikuru?
Gone already?
Looks like you're a tad too late.
I see. That's a bummer.
I'm off too, then!
Safe trip, Esyne-chan!
~MEBUKI FOREST~
I'm sure you know about this,
but we hunters, martial artists,
knights, and sorcerers,
are all called "guards".
And our job is to protect the city
and its people from monsters.
We mainly go on a patrol like we did today
and hunt the assigned monsters.
And then...
We also transport and escort VIPs, right?
You know a lot, don't you, Mede-chan?
It's common sense.
You learn that at school.
Wait, did you just call me Mede-chan?
Yes!
School, huh? Even though she looks small,
she's still a college student, after all.
Hitamuki, I want to avoid
danger as much as possible today.
I also want to hunt some slimes,
but do you remember how they smell?
Yes, I do!
Uhh...
They did such hideous things to me...
Of course I can't forget...
My bad, of course you want to forget
anything about them, even their smell.
Wh-What do you mean hideous things?!
What are you going to do to me?!
You've got it wrong.
Even though it's mostly as you'd imagine,
you're getting the wrong idea.
That's barely convincing!
A SLIME HAS APPEARED!
CHANCE FOR A PREEMPTIVE ATTACK!
This will be your revenge match, Hitamuki.
Sure! I'll do—
I'll do my best with dedication.
Maidena, you wait here with me.
Aren't you being too cautious
over a mere slime?
Sure, a slime is a small fry.
But there are some guys that will
go toe-to-toe with the small fry.
Heya!
Nice to meet you!
It attacked me when I was greeting again!
Why would she even greet it?!
We need to save her!
The back line shouldn't
reveal themselves so easily.
It's also necessary to "calmly" assess
whether the front line can recover.
Besides, today is also a training exercise
for my level-headedness.
Because yesterday I was very distraught
by the unexpected actions of my party member.
So your party member was troubling you
instead of the enemy?
The enemy is still predictable.
She went head-to-head again and blew
her chance to make the first move today...
But I must keep my cool now...
Kik-kun told me to strike your core
with a piercing attack!
Piercing attack...
That means...
A spear hand!
SNAP
Owww!
PINCH!
PINCH
Need to keep my cool, even if her...
...stupidity makes me want to look away...
Aren't you doing that now?
Owww... Gotta endure...
Another one?!
So its friends spotted me
because I screamed a lot?!
What a grand blunder!
Does she even want to recover?!
Even if I want to say that,
need to keep my cool...
The word doesn't even have substance anymore!
It has become "hot"!
I can't get it off me!
You're attacking there again?!
Why?!
I'm losing again...?
Sorry, Maidena.
The hideous thing  imagined has happened.
Wait, I never imagined this!
I never even knew about the world
I've just witnessed these past few seconds!
Nooooo!!
Stop moaning!
In the end, all we've got was only
my great degree of level-headness, huh?
Liar. You were in a panic.
Also, what are you blushing for, you pervert?
Per—
Hitamuki, show me your injured fingers.
Okay... They really hurt...
Wow... They're very swollen.
They might be broken.
Cure!
Wowzer! The injury's gone in a flash!
I've worked with many
white sorcerers a few times before,
but this is the first time
I've seen one of them heal this fast.
It's only a given! For they say I'm one
of the greatest geniuses of all time!
You're so amazing, Mede-chan! Thank you!
Surprisingly, my retirement
might just come earlier, huh.
The invoice for your treatment will be sent
to your house by the end of the month.
Don't forget to pay up, okay?
Sure!
Huh?
You're charging people for healing magic?!
Well, duh! If I cured you for free, hospitals
and drug companies would be out of business.
Now that you mentioned it...
The cost of treatment varies
from sorcerer to sorcerer,
but compared to high-end remedies, my magic...
If I break my fingers again,
please don't charge me money...
You'll have insurance, so calm down.
Fighting is so beyond me,
so be sure to protect me, okay?
W-Woof!
I'm here too, mind you.
You...
You're a pervert!
Do you hate me enough now
to turn to Hitamuki after that tragedy?
Another slime!
It's so big!
It's a Megaslime!
Megaslime!
Be careful. With its large size,
it'll be difficult to strike its core.
I see. It's my turn to shine now, then!
That might be the case, I think!
What...
How...
Why...
...do you even think
it's your turn to shine now?!
Just like white sorcerers
with their white magic,
us martial artists have "artes"!
It's called Counter!
ARTE
COUNTER
I can see through my opponent's attack,
and strike a powerful blow!
A both offensive and defensive ultimate!
Why didn't you use it from the start?
This arte has one weakness.
The range of counterattacks is very limited,
and in addition, I can't drop
my stance while it is in effect!
That's two, not one.
Hence, if the enemy ignores me,
I won't be able to do anything!
IGNORE!
Huh?
Noooo!
M-Mede-chan!
Do you really have to fail
in every move you make?!
Are you hurt?
I see.
Deep inside, I don't think I'm cut out for this.
I've always fought solo in the first place,
but I'm an amateur at leading a group.
And with a non-functioning front line...
I'm sorry!
And a stubborn healer...
This is too much for me.
Umm... Should we go after the Megaslime?
PUSH FORWARD
RETURN TO CITY
I guess my retirement...
...is still a long road ahead.
Let's call it a day.
So you've defeated two slimes,
but didn't encounter any other monsters?
I had two novices with me,
so we couldn't risk it.
Would that be okay with you?
I'm sorry...
What happened?!
Umm... I...
I want to say thank you
for saving me earlier.
Kikuru.
Oh, looks like you two are getting along now!
Kik-kun and Mede-chan have saved us from danger!
We're all buddy-buddy now!
Nooo!
GRRRRR
I-I was the one causing the danger...
In a sense, you've done what you said
you would do in bringing them together.
How was your quest with
Kikuru-kun and Hitamura-chan, Maidena-chan?
Uh... Well...
We had a lot of dangerous moments,
but that just made me realize
how important a healer is...
I thought I'd help them again
when there's no school...
Which college are you attending, Maidena?
College?
My friend, I'm still a first-year high school girl.
Which makes me 15.
15?
Wait, I thought you had to be 18
to get a job as a guard?
Mine's a special case!
I told you already that I'm a genius, didn't I?
15... First-year...
She was just a middle school student
a few days ago...
E-Enome-san...
Please make it the requirement for future members
to be "18 years old or older".
What's with that sudden rating system?!
"Hitamuki the Movie" would bad
for cultivation of aesthetic sensibility...
What happened out there...?!
I can't disclose the details myself...
To be continued!
TO BE CONTINUE
Ijippari ni kakuzatou wo tokashitara
If you stubbornly dissolve the sugar cubes
Sunao no mahou
Magic of honesty
Doji ni wa chotto oome no shinamon
Clumsy and a little too much cinnamon
Yarisugite daddadubada
Too much daddadubada
Mata mebunryou no kimagure to yasashisa de
In addition, with the whims and gentleness of mebenryo
Himitsu no reshipi wo mou kakimidasanaide
Don't disturb the secret recipe anymore
Oh don’t call my name
Oh don't call my name
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Amai dake janai
Not just sweet
Mune no oku no tokimeki iroiro
Heart-pounding feelings deep in my chest Various things
Watashi dake no baransu wo
I have my own balance
Wakatte hoshikute
I want you to understand
Shugaa shugaa supaisu
Sugar sugar spice
Karai dake ja iya
I don't like it
Mune no oku no tokimeki wa
just because it's spicy
Mochiron desho namida to koi no mariaaju...
Of course, if it's tears, it's a marriage of love
...Yappari wakaranaide!
…I don't know!
NEXT
NEXT EPISODE
A
A BOLT
A BOLT OUT
A BOLT OUT OF
A BOLT OUT OF THE
A
A BOLT OUT OF THE BLUE
A DYING
A DYING HUNTER